Earth
Fire
Air
Water
When I was a boy,
my father, Avatar Aang
told me the story of
how he and his friends
heroically ended the 100 year war.
Avatar Aang and Firelord Zuko
transformed the
Fire Nation colonies
into the
United Republic of Nations
a society where benders and
non-benders from all over the world
would live and thrive together
in peace and harmony
They named the capital of this
great land Republic City
Avatar Aang accomplished many
remarkable things in his life
but, sadly, his time in
this world came to an end
and like the
cycle of the seasons
the cycle of the
Avatar began anew
The White Lotus has
honored my family by coming
Thank you.
Welcome.
We have investigated many claims
both here and in the
Northern Tribe
all of them turned out to be false.
Then you should be happy to know,
your search has come to an end.
What makes you so sure
your daughter is...
the one?
Korra! please come in here
I'm the Avatar!
You gotta deal with it!
She's strong.
But she lacks restraint.
Hey! Why all the doom
and gloom, people?
We should be celebrating!
Three elements down, one to go!
You are getting ahead of
yourself as usual, Korrra.
We haven't decided if you
passed your fire bending test yet.
Ever since you were a little girl you
excelled at the physical side of bending
but completely ignored
the spiritual side.
The Avatar must master both.
I haven't ignored it, it just
doesn't come as easy to me.
But that's why I should start
training with Tenzin immediately
he's "Mister Spiritual".
If anyone can teach her
what she needs to learn,
it's Tenzin.
Very well, Korra.
It's time for you to begin
your airbending training
Yes! Finally!
I mean... ahem!
Thank you all for
believing in me.
Naga! You should have seen it.
I kicked some firebending butt,
and I passed!
Tenzin will be
here in a few days.
Just taking Naga out for a stroll.
Don't worry, we're not going far.
Naga, go!
Are we there yet? Are we
there yet? Are we there yet?
It looks like we're there,
I know cause it's very familiar.
Are we here yet?
Are we there yet?
- Ooooh please tell me we're here!
- Yes, Ikki.
As I've been telling you
for the last 15 minutes
we are, FINALLY, here.
Hello, Mother.
I can't tell you how
happy I am to see you.
Please, help me.
Unhand me, strange woman!
That's your grandmother, Milo.
It's so good to see all of you.
Gran Gran, I've been reading
all about your old adventures.
and I've been dying to ask you
What happened to Zuko's mom?
Well, Jinora,
it's an incredible tale.
Gran Gran, you look old.
How old are you?
And why is it so cold in the South Pole?
Can we make a campfire and and all huddle around it
and tell scary stories
and make snowmen?
And then can you make the snowmen
move with Waterbending and chase us?
Wouldn't that be fun? Huh?
Wouldn't it?
Pema, let me help you.
Careful now. Careful.
Stop doting on me.
I'm not helpless
I'm just pregnant!
The baby is strong.
I see another airbender
in your future.
All I want is one child like me!
A nice non-bender who doesn't blast
wind at my face every five seconds.
Mommy, look!
I'm a snowbender!
Were Tenzin and his
siblings this crazy
when they were kids?
Kaya and Bumi certainly were
but Tenzin has always been...
rather serious.
Mother... please.
Korra?
Look at you,
so big and strong.
You've grown into
quite the young Avatar.
Master Tenzin,
I'm so glad you're here.
I can't wait to get started.
Yes.. well...
You're going to have to
tell her sooner or later.
Tell me what?
You're not staying, are you?
I'm afraid not.
We're only visiting
for the night.
Then, I have to
return to Republic City.
But... you're suposed to move here!
You're suposed to teach me!
I'm sorry, Korra.
Your airbending training
is going to have to wait.
So, how long until you're
ready to teach me airbending?
A week? A month?
It could be much longer.
I don't understand.
Why are you making me wait?
I have a responsibility to
Republic City.
I'm one of it's leaders,
and the situation there
is very unstable right now.
But you also have a
responsibility to teach me.
Believe me! I'd be happy
to find another airbending master.
But you are the only one.
We're stuck with each other.
I wish there were another way
Wait! there is!
If you can't stay here, then
I'll go back to Republic City with you!
It's perfect!
Absolutely not.
The city is far too dangerous!
Avatar Aang tasked us
with keeping you safe
while you master
the four elements!
I get that, but
I don't think keeping me locked up
in this compound like a prisoner
is what he had in mind.
I know this is difficult to accept
but it's not the right time
for you to come to the city.
Whatever!
Goodbye, Gran Gran!
Hoogie, yip yip.
Nice night for an escape, isn't it?
I have to leave.
I have to find my
own path as the Avatar.
I know you do.
Aang's time has passed.
My brother and many of
my friends are gone.
It's time for you
and your generation
to take over the responsibility
of keeping peace
and balance in the world
and I think you're going
to be a great Avatar.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Korra.
Mom, Dad...
I'll miss you.
We love you so much.
Naga! we're here!
Thanks for the ride!
Wow!
Look at this place!
I've never seen so
many Satomobiles!
Airtemple Island
That's were Tenzin is.
Ready for a little swim, girl?
Okay, okay!
Food first, then Airtemple.
Watch it, Naga! Look out!
Excuse us!
Coming through!
Heads up!
Sorry!
Naga, wait.
We'll take one of
everything, please.
That'll be 20 Yuans.
Err... I don't
have any money.
Then what good are you to me!
Don't worry, girl.
The city is huge!
I bet we can find a place
to rustle up something to eat.
Uh... say!
Think I can get one of them
tasty smelling fishies?
Oh! err... Yeah, sure!
You... live in that bush?
Yes! Presently that is
what I do call "home"
Took me a while to
procure a bush that beauty.
This park is quite popular
with all the vagabonds.
So there are a lot
of you out here?
I thought everyone in
this city was living it up?
You got a lot to
learn newcomer.
Welcome to Republic City.
Hey you!
Stop! You can't fish here!
You best skedaddle!
Are you tired of living
under the tyranny of benders?
Then join the Equalists!
For too long the bending elite
of this city have forced
nonbenders to live as
lower class citizens!
Join Amon!
And together we will tear down
the bending establishment!
What are you talking about?
Bending is the coolest
thing in the world!
Oh yeah?
Let me guess
you're a bender.
Yeah, I am.
Then I bet you'd love to just knock me off
this platform with some Waterbending huh?
I'm seriously thinking about it.
This is what's wrong with the City!
Benders like this girl only use
their powers to oppress us!
What?!
I'm not oppressing anyone!
You...
You're oppressing yourselves!
That didn't even make sense!
Excuse me, I think I'm lost.
How do I get to
Air Temple Island from here?
Just head down this street
You should get moving young lady.
It isn't safe!
Mr. Chung,
please tell met
that you have my money
or else I can't guarantee that
I can protect your fine establishment.
I'm sorry! Business has been slow!
Please! Take one of my phonographs.
My friend here is not a music lover.
Give me the money or else
Or else what, hoodlum?
Since you're obviously
fresh off the boat,
let me explain a couple things.
You're in
Triple Threat Triad territory
and we're about to
put you in the hospital.
You're the only ones who
are gonna need a hospital.
And for your sake I
hope there's one near by.
Who do you think you are?
Why don't you come and find out?
- What just happened?
- Did she just Earthbend?
Can she Firebend too?
Could she be...?
Got an idea about who I am now?
Chumps
Come on!
You're not getting away!
Police! Freeze where you are!
Cool, Metalbenders...
I caught the bad guys
for you officers.
Arrest them!
You're under arrest too.
What do you mean I'm under arrest?
Those are the bad guys over there!
They were smashing up a shop.
From the looks of it, you
smashed up a lot more than that.
Wait! You can't arrest me!
Let me explain!
You can explain
yourself all you like
down at headquarters.
Let's see...
Multiple counts of destruction
of private and city property
not to mention resisting arrest.
You're in a whole mess
of trouble young lady.
But they were some thugs
threatening a helpless shopkeeper and I
Can it! You should have called the
police and stayed out of the way.
But I couldn't just
sit by and do nothing.
It's my duty to help people.
See, I'm the Avatar.
Oh, I am well aware
of who you are.
And your Avatar title
might impress some people
but not me.
All right, fine.
Then I want to talk
to whoever's in charge.
You're talking to her.
I'm Chief Bei Fong.
Wait...Bei Fong
Lin Bei Fong?
You're Toph's daughter!
- What of it?
- Well then why are you treating me like a criminal?
Avatar Aang and your
mother were friends,
they saved the world together.
That's ancient history.
And it's got diddlysquat to do
with the mess you're in right now.
You can't just waltz in here and dole out
vigilante justice like you own the place.
Chief, Councilman Tenzin is here. You can't just waltz in
here and dole out vigilante justice like you own the place.
Chief, Councilman Tenzin is here.
Let him in.
Tenzin...sorry,
I got a little side tracked
on my way to see you...
Lin you are looking
radiant as usual.
Cut the garbage, Tenzin.
Why is the Avatar in Republic City?
I thought you were supposed to be
moving down to the South Pole to train her.
My relocation has been delayed.
The Avatar, on the other hand, will be
heading back to the South Pole immediately
where she will stay put.
- But-
- If you would be so kind as to
drop the charges against Korra
I will take full
responsibility for today's events
and cover all the damages.
Fine, get her out of my city.
Always a pleasure Lin.
Let's go Korra.
Tenzin please
don't send me back home.
You blatantly disobeyed my wishes
and the Order of the White Lotus.
Katara agreed with
me that I should come.
She said my destiny
is in Republic City.
Don't bring my mother into this!
Look, I can't wait any
longer to finish my training.
Being cooped up and hidden away from the world
isn't helping me become a better Avatar.
I saw a lot of the city today
and it's totally out of whack.
I understand now
why you need to stay,
Republic City does need you
but it needs me too.
You...
Is this your
polar bear-dog, miss?
Korra!
Are you coming to live
with us on the island?
No, I'm sorry Ikki.
I have to go home now.
Wait.
I have done my best to
guide Republic City
towards the dream
my father had for it.
But you're right, it has fallen
out of balance since he passed.
I thought I should put off your training
in order to uphold his legacy.
But you are his legacy.
You may stay and train
Airbending here with me.
Republic City needs
it's Avatar once again.
Yes! Thank you! You're the best!
Hello...
I'm Korra,
your new Avatar.
Does this mean you've
moved to Republic City?
Were you trying to send a message
to the Triads yesterday?
Will you be fighting crime or the
anti-bending revolution or both?
Will you be working with
Chief Bei Fong and the police?
Uhh...yes I am
definitely here to stay
but honestly... I don't
exactly have a plan yet...
See I'm still in training but...
Look,
all I know is Avatar Aang
meant for this city
to be the center of peace
and balance in the world
and
I believe we can make
his dream a reality.
I look forward to serving you!
I'm so happy to be here!
Than you Republic City!
All right that's all
the questions the Av-
Amon, how do you
want to handle this?
So, the Avatar has arrived early.
It looks like we'll have
to accelerate our plans.
"And in the final round the Buzzard Wasps
won with a decisive knockout."
What do you say we
go to the arena tonight?
Catch a few Pro-Bending matches?
That sport is a mockery of the
noble tradition of bending.
Come on Tenzin!
I dreamed about seeing a
Pro-Bending match since I was a kid
and now I'm just a ferry ride
away from the arena.
Korra, you're not here
to watch that drivel.
You're here to finish
your Avatar training,
so for the time being I want
you to remain on the island.
Is that why you're keeping the
White Lotus sentries around
to watch my every move?
Yes. In order to
learn Airbending
I believe you require a
calm, quiet environment
free from any distractions.
Alright.
You're the master.
So
my mother informed me you've
never been able to Airbend before.
Yeah but I don't know why.
The other elements
came SO easily to me
but every single time
I've tried Airbending
nothing.
That's perfectly all right.
We just need to be patient.
Often the element that's the most
difficult for the Avatar to master
is the one most opposite
to the Avatar's personality.
For Aang it was Earthbending.
Yeah well, I'm about as opposite
an Airbender as you can get.
Let's begin your first lesson.
Korra's gonna Airbend!
What is that contraption.
A time-honored tool
that teaches the most
fundamental aspect of Airbending.
Jinora would you like
to explain this exercise.
The goal is to weave your
way through the gates
and make it to the other side
without touching them.
Seems easy enough.
Jinora forgot to say you have to make
it through while the gates are spinning.
The key is to be like the leaf.
Flow
with the movement of the gates.
Jinora will demonstrate.
Airbending is all
about spiral movements.
When you meet resistance
you must be able to switch
direction at a moment's notice.
Let's do this.
Don't force your way through!
Dance! Dance like the wind!
Be the leaf!
Airbend!
What is wrong with me?
Maybe I'm just not cut out
to be an Airbender, huh, Naga?
Ladies and gentlemen!
I'm coming to you live
from Republic City's
Pro-Bending arena
where tonight the
best in the world
continue their quest for a spot in
the upcoming championship tournament.
Grab your snacks
and grab your kids
because this next match
is gonna be a doozy!
This Mako's got moxy!
He fires to quick shots.
Yomo is hammered
back to zone 3.
Clock is winding down,
can Yomo hold on?
He's teetering on the
edge of the ring now.
The Fire Ferrets—
Korra come down here, please.
You shut it off at the best part!
I thought I made myself clear,
I don't want you listening to
this distracting nonsense
But it's their radio.
And technically you said I couldn't watch a match.
You didn't say anything about listening to one.
You...-
you know what I meant.
Anyway shouldn't you-
shouldn't you be in bed by now!
I think I'm doing it wrong.
There's nothing to do.
Let your mind and
your spirit be free
for Air is the
element of freedom.
Is something funny?
Yeah, you're telling me to embrace freedom
but you won't even let me listen to the radio.
And forget about leaving this island.
Please Korra. Look at Meelo.
He's able to meditate peacefully.
Actually, I think he's asleep.
What?
Well, at least he has
the relaxing part down.
Whatever,
none of this Airbending stuff
makes any sense to me.
I know you're frustrated
but these teachings
will sink in over time
then one day
they'll just click.
Yeah it's not sinking in yet.
I'm gonna go get a
glass of leechee juice.
Korra!
The meditation's not over yet!
Daddy can I have
some leechee juice too?
No.
Hey!
What are you doing in my gym?
I was just looking for a
bathroom and I got lost.
Oh the old "I had to pee excuse".
You know, I'm sick and tired of
you kids sneaking in without paying.
I'm taking you to security.
- No wait...!
- There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
It's alright Toza, she's with me.
Yeah, I'm with him.
So you see, we're together.
Well not "together together",
more like friends.
- Right friends, no, no I didn't mean to imply...
Oh you implied it.
I don't care what you are!
I've got work to do.
Right this way miss.
Why thank you sir.
Seriously thanks.
What do you think?
Best seats in the house, huh?
Whoa...
Unbelievable!
this place is even more amazing
than I imagined.
Name's Bolin, by the way.
Korra
- Pssst, Bolin!
- Yeah?
I told you, you have to stop bringing your
crazy fangirls in here before the matches.
Get her out of here.
Ah come on Mako!
I kinda promised her,
she could stay
but man I got a good feeling.
There's something special about her
I know it. Come here, I want
you to meet my brother
Mako
Mako?
Wow I heard you
play on the radio.
Come on Bolin we're up.
Or I could meet him later.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
My brother gets real
focused before a match.
Well I gotta go.
Wish me luck.
Not that I'll need it.
Good luck!
Knock 'em out!
Introducing the Fire Ferrets!
Ahhhh!! I love you Bolin.
The rookie Ferrets
came out of nowhere
and have made it further
than anyone expected this season.
But tonight they face
their toughest test yet folks.
And they're off.
The two teams waste no time
trying to blast each
other out of zone 1.
Hasook is the first to feel
the heat of the Tigerdilloes,
he tries to return the favor
but they're too fast for him.
While Mako showcases his trademark
cool under fire style.
And the Tigerdilloes score
with a walloping one-two combo.
Can their teammate...
Guess not.
Mako's over the line.
The Tigerdilloes get the green line
and advance into Ferret territory.
Come on, Ferrets!
Look's like Hasook's
in trouble.
He's in zone 3 teetering
over the drink.
And Hasook takes a dip.
He'll be back for round two.
Assuming the fabulous bending brothers
can hold their ground until he next round.
Round 1 goes to the
Golden Temple Tigerdilloes!
Come on, Hasook
get your act together!
The Fire Ferrets are knocked into zone 2
and the Tigerdilloes advance.
The Fire Ferrets sinch the round
in the closing seconds.
That's one a piece. Still anyone's match
as we go into the third and final round.
Hasook stumbles
and now he tumbles right
into his teammate.
He and Bolin better untangle quick
if they don't want to—
Oh too late!
Oh no!
It's all up to Mako now,
he's bobbing and weaving,
but he's not hitting back!
If he's knocked out the
Ferrets' fabulous season is over.
He is dancing on the
edge of the ring
withstanding the
three on one barrage.
It seems his plan is to let the
Tigerdilloes punch themselves out.
And his plan is working.
Han is in the pool!
They've got nothing left in the tank
and Mako's on the offensive!
It's two on one,
scratch that it's one on one.
And it's an Earth and Fire slugfest!
There's so much smoke and dust
I can't even see where the Fire Ferret is.
It's a knock out!
What a win they had a hat trick folks!
Mako pulls off the upset of the season
winning the match for the Fire Ferrets!
Yes!
One more win and we're in
the championship tournament!
So, what'd ya think Korra?
Bolin's got some moves, huh?
What did I think?
That was amazing!
You did more harm
than good out there.
You almost cost us the match.
We won didn't we?
- Barely
- Get off my case pal.
Useless.
You guys were
incredible out there.
Especially you Mr. Hatrick.
Oh you're still here...
Oh you're still a jerk...
anyway,
I've been immersed in
bending my entire life
but I never learned
to move like that.
It's like there's a
whole new style here.
Think you could
show me a few tricks?
Absolutely!
Right now?
Come on Bolin.
Just ignore him.
Yeah I could show you the basics.
I'm just not sure how my Earthbending
would translate to your Waterbending
but we'll figure it out.
Won't be a problem,
I'm actually an Earthbender.
I'm sorry! No, no
I didn't mean to assume—
I was just figuring,
with your Water Tribe get up
that you are a Water Tribe gal.
No you're right.
I'm a Waterbender
and a Firebender.
Hmm... uhhmm.
I'm very confused right now.
You're the Avatar
and I'm an idiot.
Both are true.
No... way...
The Avatar!
Alright. Let's see what you got.
That was great!
Good power!
But in a real match you'd
be a sitting turtleduck.
Not so upright and flatfooted.
Stay light on your toes
up until the moment
when you need to dig in and strike.
Then—
Okay, let me try it again.
Wow! Nice adjustment.
You're a natural at this!
- Not bad.
- What's it take
to impress this guy?
What? I said not bad.
You know what, it's getting late.
I think I'm gonna turn in.
You kids have fun.
Nice to meet you, Avatar Korra.
Yeah, real pleasure.
See you upstairs bro.
Upstairs? You guys live here?
Yeah, in the attic.
It's nothing fancy
but we have great views.
But back to bending.
Why don't you throw
that combination one more time.
Patience Korra!
That was a 2000-year-old
historical treasure...
what...
what is wrong with you?!
There's nothing wrong with me!
I've been practicing
just like you taught me!
But it isn't sinking in okay!
It hasn't clicked
like you said it would!
Korra this isn't
something you can force.
If you would only listen to me...
I have been!
But you know what I think?
Maybe the problem isn't me,
maybe the reason I haven't
learned Airbending yet
is because you're
a terrible teacher.
Yeah you're a terrible teacher, Daddy!
Okay!
Everyone here?
Wait...
where's Korra?
Honestly Pema, I am at my
wit's end with that girl.
I don't know how to
get through to her.
Dear, the best thing
you can do right now
is to give Korra some space.
You must promise me that your
teenage years won't be like this.
I will make no such promises.
I didn't miss your match did I?
You guys look like
you lost already.
- We might as well have.
- Hasook's a no good no show.
You got two minutes
to come out ready to play
or you're disqualified.
Well there goes our shot
at the tournament
and the winnings.
Couldn't you ask one of
those guys to fill in?
Nah, the rules say you can
only compete on one team.
Well then... how about me?
I'm a topnotch Waterbender
if I do say so myself.
But you're the Avatar...
isn't that cheating?
It isn't cheating if
I only do Waterbending.
No way.
I'd rather forfeit
than look like a
fool out there.
Wow
thanks for the
vote of confidence...
Time's up
you in or out?
- We're in.
- We are?
- Yes!
- Hey, I didn't agree to this!
You can thank me later.
This girl is crazy...
Looks like the Fire Ferrets
have ferreted out a last
minute replacement Waterbender.
Let's see if she's another
diamond in the rough
like the brothers
from the school of hard knocks.
Don't do anything too fancy
or aggressive.
In fact, don't do anything.
Just try not to get knocked
off the ring.
You got it captain.
Players
are you ready?
Whoo! Man overboard!
Fire Ferret Waterbender penalty,
move back one zone.
What? Why?
You're only allowed to knock
players off the back of the ring,
not over the sides.
Oh...whoops.
And we're back in action
after that hiccup. But I'm not so sure this
replacement player knows what she's doing.
Foul! Over the line!
Move back to zone three.
Ugh! I'll show you over the line.
The Platypus Bears take round 1.
The Platypus Bears know a
green player when they see one
and they are focusing the brunt
of their bending on this poor girl.
What a minute,
did that Waterbender
just Earthbend?
Foul!
I think.
Did I see that right?
Hold on folks we're just waiting
for the Referee's official call
but I think this replacement
player could be...
Pardon me everyone, has
anyone seen Korra this evening?
She's not in her room.
You've gotta be kidding me!
She's the Avatar, folks
playing in a Pro-Bending match!
Can you believe that?
I'll get her myself!
The Avatar will be
permitted to continue
so long as she solely bends water.
This girl may be the Avatar
but she's no Pro-Bender
and the Platypus Bears are intent
on exploiting that weakness.
They're giving her their best
and her best ain't
good enough to stop it.
Aaaaaannd...-
she's in the drink.
Oh hey Tenzin...
I thought you didn't like
coming to these matches.
Once again you have
flagrantly disobeyed my orders.
You were to stay on the island.
Let's go.
No!
I'm kind of in the
middle of something.
I have tried my very best
to get through to you
by being gentle and patient
But clearly the only thing
you respond to is force.
So I am ordering you to come
back to the temple. Right now!
Why? So I can sit around and meditate
about how bad I am at Airbending?
You know I'm beginning to think there's
a reason I haven't been able to learn it,
because maybe I don't
even need it!
What!?
That is a ludicrous suggestion!
The Avatar needs to learn
Airbending, it is not optional!
No, THIS is what I need to learn!
Modern styles of fighting!
Being Avatar isn't all
about fighting, Korra!
When will you learn that?
I have a match to go finish.
The Platypus Bears win round 2!
Round 3!
The Platypus Bears come out of the gate
and quickly go after the Ferret brothers.
They're corralled in the corner, wedged in the edge
of zone 1 unable to come to the Avatar's rescue
and boy does she need it.
Looks like the Avatar's Pro-Bending
debut is gonna be cut short
as she's pushed back to zone 3
and the water is calling her name.
It's only a matter of time before—
Hold the phone, stop the presses!
She's still in the game folks!
And she's moving like an
entirely different player!
All of a sudden the Platypus Bear
strikes are only striking air.
How about that...
The Platypus Bears
have no juice left
but Mako and Bolin are
still fresh and juicy.
Knockout!
The Fire Ferrets come from
way behind and steal the win!
What an upset folks!
The rookies, Avatar in tow,
have nabbed a place in
the championship tournament!
I cannot believe it!
Korra, what can I say?
You really came alive
in that last round.
The way you dodged
their attacks...
you are a natural.
Thanks
but I can't take
all the credit,
someone else taught
me those moves.
I'm really sorry
about everything I said.
I was really frustrated
with myself and
I took it out on you.
I think I owe you
an apology too.
I was trying to teach
you about patience
but I lost mine.
No hard feelings?
Of course not.
By the way, you were really
good out there tonight.
You moved, just like an Airbender.
Wait?! You stayed and watched?
I did. Pro-Bending turned out to be
the perfect teaching tool for you.
I'll see you tomorrow for
Airbending practice bright and early!
And by the way I kinda
permanently joined the Fire Ferrets
and we're playing in the tournament
in a couple of weeks!
Sync by: HerrySis
IDFL Sub Crew IDFL.us
Subscene uploaded by: valoe11
NEW Sync, Timed & corrected by petala for
The.Legend.of.Korra.S01E01E02.Welcome.to.Republic.City-
A.Leaf.in.the.Wind.720p.WEB-DL.AAC2.0.H.264 released to Subscene
www.tvsubtitles.net