Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Republic City is at war.
After discovering that her father,
Hiroshi Sato, is working with the enemy,
Asami turns against him.
And following another defeat
at the hands of the Equalists,
Lin Beifong resigns
as Chief of Police.
With the Equalist
army growing stronger...
Who will help the Avatar stop Amon
and restore balance to the city?
Original version by
--Patrick of Addic7ed.com--
Correction and Sync by
*Laksmi of Addic7ed.com*
You're finally here.
Welcome to Air Temple Island.
Your new home.
Yes, welcome to my domain.
Well, aren't you sweet, little monk child?
What's that fuzzy creature?
That is a fire ferret,
an arboreal mammal common to the bamboo forest
south of the Central Earth Kingdom.
Aw, he's cute!
Hip hip, fly sky bison, fly!
Thanks for sending the Air
acolytes to help us with the move.
Yes, they've been amazing.
Such tireless workers.
Thought you were only bringing a few things.
Trust me, it could have been worse.
No problem.
Everyone here wants you guys to feel welcome.
You're pretty, can I
have some of your hair?
Looks like I have some competition.
And now for the grand tour!
The flying bisons live in those caves down there,
and that's the temple grandpa Aang built
and that's the greenhouse where
we grow the vegetables we eat.
I have a couple of questions.
Is this an all-vegetarian island?
And final question:
How many trees are on this island?
Yes; yes; no; no; 10,552.
So, where are we gonna be staying?
You're a boy, boys have
to stay on the boys' side.
I'll be happy to show you
to the men's dormitory.
I'm a boy.
Meelo, why don't you go with the boys too?
We shall meet again soon,
beautiful woman.
Ikki and I will take you
to your room. This way.
Asami, did you know Korra likes Mako?
Oh, uh, no, I wasn't
completely aware of that.
Hey!
Run along, Ikki.
So... here's your room.
I know this is a little rustic
compared to what you're used to.
I think it's really charming.
And the best part about it?
Nothing here reminds me of my father.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Ikki, I swear, if you don't leave us alone,
I'm gonna...
Tenzin! Come right in.
Good day, ladies.
Asami, welcome to the island.
Thank you for having me.
Beifong's replacement's Saikhan is going to
be inducted as the new Chief of Police later.
I think we should both be there.
It was an honor serving under
Chief Beifong for so many years.
And I wish her a
speedy recovery.
It is with great humility that I take
her place as the new Chief of Police.
Republic City is facing a threat like
none the world has ever seen.
But there's one man who has been effective
against Amon's revolution, Councilman Tarrlok.
That is why for all the matters involving the
Equalists, I will report directly to him.
The Police Department will hand any and all available
resources to the councilman and his task force.
Until we quell this insurgency.
What is that weasel-snake Tarrlok up to now?
Tarrlok, I don't know what you did to
get Chief Saikhan in your pocket,
but I highly doubt it was legal.
Oh, Tenzin, always the conspiracy theorist.
Did you ever consider Saikhan
simply recognizes my talents
and wants what is best for the city?
Well, Avatar Korra.
Long time no see.
Now that your little pro-bending
distractions are over,
I look forward to your return to my task force.
Forget it, there's no way I'm
rejoining your vanity project.
That is unfortunate to hear,
but I'm sure you'll come to
your senses as you have in the past.
Don't hold your breath, bub.
You know, Tenzin's been right about you all along.
You played me, you played Beifong...
and now you're playing the new Chief too.
Well, I got news for you:
You need me, but I don't need you.
I'm the Avatar.
You are not, in fact ,the Avatar,
you are merely a half-baked Avatar in training.
Which reminds me...
How is your airbending going?
Made any significant progress with that?
I didn't think so.
If you will not be part of my task force,
then you'd best stay out of my way.
I don't understand
what's wrong with me.
I've memorized nearly all
of the practice forms,
but I still can't produce
a single, measly puff of air!
I'm a failure.
No, you're not.
You just need to work through this airbending block.
Amazing advice. I'll get right on that.
I wasn't finished yet.
You see, Aang not only had
his bending teachers,
but also his past lives
to call upon for guidance.
Have you ever made contact
with your past lives?
No, of course I haven't.
Didn't you get the memo
from the White Lotus?
I'm a spiritual failure, too.
You may have made a connection
without realizing it.
Perhaps something you mistook as a dream?
Maybe...
I had a few weird hallucinations,
but I hardly even remember them.
Did you see any of the previous
Avatars in these visions?
I saw Aang.
It seemed like he was in trouble.
What do you think it means?
I don't know. But I urge you
to meditate on these visions.
I believe Aang's spirit must be
trying to tell you something.
Korra. Are you out here?
Korra!
There you are.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come on, what's wrong?
You can tell us.
How am I supposed to save this city,
when I can't even learn airbending?
I'm the worst Avatar ever!
I just feel... alone.
No, that's non-sense, you're amazing.
Yeah and remember,
Aang hadn't mastered all the elements
while he was battling the Fire Nation.
He was just a little kid.
And he wasn't alone, he had
his friends to help him.
Look, the arena might be shut down,
but we're still a team, the New Team Avatar!
We got your back Korra and we
can save the city together.
Yeah, let's do it.
Yeah, let's do it!
What are we doing?
Get ready, Republic City.
You are about to be patrolled by Team Avatar.
Asami, you always know how to accessorize your outfits.
I figured one way to fight Equalists is to use an Equalist weapon.
Alright, let's ride.
Naga away!
Alright, scratch that. Any other ideas?
I think I have the answer.
You think this will do?
I like the New Team Avatar's style.
Unit 2-16, cancel that 10-58 in Harmony Tower.
Come back to the station. Over.
My dad had police scanners
installed in all of his cars,
I guess now I know why.
Calling all units. Level Four Alert.
Jailbreak at Headquarters.
Officers down. Electrocuted.
Chi-blockers and Equalist convicts are still
at large armed and dangerous.
Last seen heading east. I repeat
Level Four Alert. Equalist Jailbreak.
Chi-blockers! That's them!
Let's get them!
Korra, Bolin, give me a ramp! Now!
Help me out! We've got to make this turn!
They don't know we made the turn.
Ok. Get ready...
Avatar Korra, what do
you think you're doing?
Oh, hey, Tarrlok, nice for you to show up finally.
Here, we captured these escaped convicts for you.
What you did was tear up the city,
and impede the real authorities
in their pursuit of these criminals.
That's funny.
I didn't see your little task force or the cops the whole time.
If it wasn't for Team Avatar,
they would have gotten away.
This is your last warning:
Stay out of my way!
Republic city stands as
a beacon of freedom,
but the Equalists are using
that freedom to tear it down.
The law I have proposed would make it illegal
for anyone to be a member of the Equalists
or even be associated with them.
It also puts into effect a curfew
insuring all non-benders are
in their own homes by nightfall.
This is going too far, Tarrlok.
You can't punish all non-benders for the actions of a few.
That kind of cowardice will cause
our city to fall into Amon's hands.
We must pass this law.
All in favor?
All available units. Please respond to the
50-600 block at Dragon Flats Borough.
Equalists have been taken to the streets.
Consider them armed
and dangerous. Proceed with caution.
I call front.
After you.
What a gentleman, thanks.
Why is the power out?
Wait a second, these people
aren't armed or dangerous.
It sure doesn't look that way.
All non-benders, return to
your homes immediately.
Yeah, as soon as you
turn our power back on.
Disperse or you will all be arrested.
You benders can't treat us this way!
Mommy, look! It's the Avatar.
Please, help us!
You're our Avatar too.
Everyone please stay calm,
I'm gonna put a stop to this.
Tarrlok!
You need to turn the power back on
and leave these people alone.
Avatar Korra, you and your
playmates have no business here.
We're not going anywhere.
You don't have the right to treat
these innocent people like criminals.
This is an Equalist rally,
there's nothing innocent about it.
They're not Equalists,
they're just normal people
who want their rights back.
They are the enemy!
Round up all these Equalists!
Stop!
Hey! Let me go!
You're under arrest.
What? You can't do that.
Actually, I can.
She's a non-bender out past curfew
and her father is a known Equalist conspirator.
Let her go.
Arrest him and his brother.
Tarrlok!
Unless you want to join your friends in prison,
I suggest you put those down
and go back to the Air Temple.
Korra, listen to him.
It's not worth it.
We'll be alright.
Don't worry, I'll call Tenzin.
He can get you out.
It's so sad to see your little Team Avatar broken up.
You had a good run.
This isn't over, Tarrlok.
Oh, I believe it is.
Take them away!
Hey!
I came as fast as I could.
Are your friends alright?
I don't know, these knuckleheads
won't tell me anything.
I'll take care of this.
Saikhan, a word please?
Councilman Tenzin. I'm pretty swamped at the moment.
Can this wait?
No it cannot.
Three of Avatar Korra's friends
were wrongly arrested tonight.
I'd like you to release
them immediately.
They're not going anywhere.
They were interfering with police business.
Your so-called police business was
rounding up innocent people
and claiming they were Equalists.
They should be released too.
All Equalist suspects are
being detained indefinitely.
They'll be freed, if and when the task force
deems they are no longer a threat.
Those people are entitled to
due process under the law.
You'll have to take that with
councilman Tarrlok.
Oh, I plan to.
At the council meeting, first thing in the morning.
You're officially the worst
Chief of Police ever!
Calm down, Korra.
I'll get this sorted out,
we just need to be patient.
But you really are the worst.
Ever.
Wake up, Naga.
Let's go.
Wait for me here, girl.
Don't worry, I'll be alright.
You and I need to talk.
Are any of the other
council members here?
I believe everyone has
gone home for the night.
Then you should do the same.
Are you sure, sir?
Leave us.
You obviously have
something on your mind.
Spit it out.
Don't you see?
You're doing exactly what Amon
says is wrong with benders.
You're using your power to
oppress and intimidate people.
And you don't?
Of... of course not!
Isn't that what you came here to do?
Intimidate me into releasing your friends?
See? That's what I admire
about you, Korra.
Your willingness to go to extremes
in order to get what you want.
It is a quality we both share.
You and I are nothing alike.
Look, I'll make you a deal.
You fall in line and do what I say,
and I'll release your friends.
That's why you arrested them?
To get to me?
I need your answer.
No.
You might be able to manipulate
Chief Saikhan into following you,
but it won't work on me.
You will regret that decision.
You need to be stopped.
You're just as bad as Amon.
I've tried to work with you, Korra,
but you've made it impossible.
Still think I'm a half-baked Avatar?
What are you gonna do now?
You're all out of water, pal.
You're in my way, Avatar.
And you need to be removed.
You're...you're a...
bloodbender?
Very observant.
It's... not a full moon.
How...how are you doing this?
There are a lot of things
you don't know about me.
Where are you taking me?
Somewhere no one will find you.
Say goodbye to Republic City, Avatar Korra.
You'll never see it again.
You can't do this!
Let me out!
Original version by
--Patrick of Addic7ed.com--
Correction and Sync by
==*Laksmi of Addic7ed.com*==
www.tvsubtitles.net