Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Korra and Mako have discovered
the truth about Amon's identity.
He's a waterbender,
a bloodbender, and
brother to Tarrlok.
Now Korra and Mako plan to
infiltrate the Equalist victory rally
and expose Amon as a fraud.
Meanwhile Asami, Bolin and General Iroh
head toward Hiroshi's secret airfield
where Asami intends to
take down her father.
One Book: Air, Episode 12,
"Endgame"
I think we found
our secret airfield.
Bolin, once we get down there.
I need you to tear up
those runways.
We can't let those
aircraft take off.
Oh-Yeah!, captain.
Uh!, General.
General.
All right, you guys wait here
until we get back, okay?
Stay.
Why would there be fence
posts but no fence?
Thank you all for joining me on this historic occasion.
When I was a boy,
a firebender struck down my entire
family and left me scarred.
That tragic event
began my quest,
to equalize the world.
That's a lie, Amon.
Or should I call you "Noatak"?
You want her taken out?
No.
Everyone, calm down.
We have nothing to fear
from the Avatar.
Let's hear what she has to say.
Amon has been lying to you.
The spirits didn't give him the power
to take people's bending away.
He uses bloodbending to do it.
Amon is a waterbender.
What is this nonsense?
You're desperate, Avatar.
Making up stories about me
is a pathetic last resort.
Your family wasn't killed
by a firebender.
is councilman Tarrlok.
An amusing tale.
But I will show you the truth.
This is what a firebender
did to me.
What?
The Avatar is lying!
I'm telling you he's a waterbender.
They don't believe me.
- It didn't work.
- We said what we had to.
Let's get out of here.
I wouldn't leave yet Avatar.
You'll miss the main event.
No.
They got away.
We saw them get away.
Asami.
Asami, I know I have hurt you
and I am sorry.
But I believe that one day you
will come to your senses and
we can be a family again.
Are you insane?
How can we be a family after
everything you've done?
Mom would hate you for
what you've become.
How dare you!
I am avenging her death!
The airplanes are ready
for takeoff, sir.
Good.
Annihilate the fleet.
That's right, general.
I intercepted your message
to Commander Bumi.
I know exactly,
where they're hiding.
How are we gonna
get out of here?
I don't suppose you know
how to metalbend?
That is a negative, sir.
Naga!,
over here.
Who needs a metalbender?
We got naga!,
Yeah!
I'm going after
those airplanes.
No, Naga!
What do you know. Just like
a future industries forklift.
Tonight, I rid the world
of airbending,
Forever.
Amon, let them go.
You're welcome to come down
here and try to stop me.
He's trying to bait you.
I don't care.
We have to save them.
The Avatar needs to be reminded
of the power I possess.
Where are Pema and the baby?
In prison.
Beifong?
I don't know.
Follow me, kids.
Get them out of here.
We'll create a diversion.
Let's go get your mother
and the baby.
Prison break!
Let her go!
No!
Korra!
I told you
I would destroy you.
Thanks for
looking out for me, aang.
Thanks!,
Naga.
Asami!
What do you think
you're doing?
You are aiding the very people
who took your mother away!
You don't feel love
for mom anymore.
You're too full of hatred.
You ungrateful
insolent child.
I now see there is no
chance to save you!
Mr. sato, you are
a horrible father!
You really are
a horrible father.
Finally,
you are powerless.
Amon!
Everything the Avatar said
is true, isn't it?
I just saw you bloodbend her.
You traitor.
I dedicated my life to you.
You served me well
Lieutenant.
Mako.
My bending,
Everything will be all right.
We just need to
get out of here.
I'm impressed.
No one has ever gotten the
better of me like that.
It is almost a shame to take the
bending of someone so talented.
Almost.
No!
Impossible.
I-I can airbend?
I can airbend!
No,
You... Don't!
Did you see what happened?
No.
Who was that?
Can you see him?
Could that be...?
- You bending tyrant!
- Evil Avatar!
What did you do to our
leader?
- He's waterbending.
- What?
- He is a bender!
- The scar is fake!
The Avatar
was telling the truth!
Noatak.
It's over, brother.
I'm sorry for what
I had to do to you.
Our father set us
on this path.
Fate caused us to collide.
I should have left with you
when we were boys.
Leave with me now.
We have a second chance.
We can start over together.
Please, you're all I have left
in the world.
I can't believe
Amon got you too.
Hey, at least you unlocked
your airbending.
Bro, not the time.
Right, right.
I'll just stand over here.
Quietly,
In silence.
You saved Republic city.
But Amon got away.
Yay!, Uncle Bumi's here!
Great.
Now I have
to entertain my brother.
The two of us
together again.
There's nothing we can't do.
Yes, Noatak.
Noatak...,
I'd almost forgotten
the sound of my own name.
It will be just like the
good old days.
I've tried everything
in my power
but, I cannot restore
Korra's bending.
But you're the best healer
in the world.
You have to keep trying!
I'm sorry, There's
nothing else I can do.
Korra can still airbend,
but her connection to the other
elements has been severed.
It's going to be all right, Korra.
No,
it's not.
Korra!,
Wait.
Go away.
I will,
but I just want you to know,
I'm here for you.
No, I mean go away
back to Republic city.
Get on with your life.
What are you talking about?
I'm not the Avatar anymore.
You don't need to
do me any favors.
I don't care if you're
the Avatar or not.
Listen.
When Tarrlok took you I was
losing my mind at the thought
of never seeing you again.
I realized.
I love you, Korra.
I...
I can't.
Korra!
We need to be patient with her.
It will take time for her to accept
what has happened.
Not now, Tenzin.
I just want to be left alone.
But you called me here.
Aang.
You have finally connected
with your spiritual self.
How?
When he hit our lowest point,
we are open to the greatest change.
I love you too.
Thank you.
I am so proud of you
Avatar Korra.
www.tvsubtitles.net