Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master
all four Elements
and bring balance to the world.
The Legend of Korra
A chance encounter turns Korra
from pro-bending spectator
to pro-bending star!
With her new teammates,
Mako and Bolin,
the Fire Ferrets earn a place
in the championship tournament.
But meanwhile, an anti-bending revolution
brews in Republic City.
Who are the Equalists,
and what nefarious plan
does the mysterious man behind the mask
have in store for our hero?
Season 1, Episode 3
"The Revelation"
Subs by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
What's the big idea with making me train
this early in the morning?
The morning is evil.
We're the rookies, so we get
the worst time spot in the gym.
And you're the rookiest of us all.
We gotta get you up to speed
if we want to survive in the tournament.
Deal with it!
- You deal with it!
- Ooh! Oh...
There are my little hard working
street urchins!
It's an honor to finally meet ya,
Avatar.
- And you are...?
- Butakha.
I run this whole pro-bending shebang.
Here's your winnings
from the last match.
Ah, ah, ah!
Not so fast...
First you owe me
for the Avatar's new gear...
Gym and equipment rentals
for the last month...
Ah, ah!
Rent on your apartment...
Aa... and the personal loan,
for groceries.
What?
I'm a growing boy!
Oh, and one more
small item of business...
The Fire Ferrets need to ante up
30,000 yuans,
for the championship pot.
30,000 yuans?!?
Sorry, kids.
You've got till the end of the week
to come up with the dough, or else...
You're out of the tournament.
I got nothing.
I've never really needed money.
I've always had people
taking care of me.
Then I wouldn't say
"you've had nothing".
- Sorry I didn't mean...
- No, it's alright. It's just...
Ever since we lost our parents,
we've been on our own.
I'm so sorry, I didn't know.
So, anyway...
How are we gonna come up
with the money?
Oh, oh!
I got it! I got it!
I've been training Pabu
to do circus tricks...
Now, people would pay
good money to see that.
Come on Bolin...
We need serious ideas.
I was serious...
Don't worry about it.
I'll figure something out.
I always do.
Come one, come all!
See Pabu,
the fantastic fire ferret,
as he crosses the ladder of peril...
Ooh!
Upside down!
Psst, psst!
Big finish buddy.
Stick the landing!
Ta-da!
Thank you,
ladies and gentlemen!
You are too kind.
Seriously, too kind!
You can come back here
and put money right in this...
Okay. That's fine.
That's fine.
One yuan down...
29,999 to go.
Hey, Bo-lin!
Is that you?
Oh... Hey there,
Shady Shin.
Heard you're a big time
pro-bending player now.
Not bad.
Uh... Thanks?
So listen...
I got an offer for you.
Lightning Bolt Zolt is looking to hire
some extra muscle.
Uh... I don't know, Shin
Mako told me
to stay away from the Triple Threats.
Pff! Your brother
ain't the boss of you!
It's just a little security work.
Nothing crooked...
[Kiddie shows goofy onomatopoeias]
You game?
Bo'...! I'm back!
Picked up your favorite dumplings...!
Hey, I found some work
down at the power plant!
Made some decent money.
Bolin?
You here, bro?
Huh...
I bet that little lovebird
is making a house call.
Good! Light on your feet!
Ooh, he's cute!
Korra, is that the handsome Fire bender boy
that drives you crazy?
Does he drive you crazy
in a bad way?
Or does he drive you crazy
like you like him...
Oh! Hey, Mako.
- You seen Bolin?
- Nice to see you, too.
And, no.
I haven't seen him since practice.
- Think something's wrong?
- I don't know...
Bolin has a knack
for getting into stupid situations.
- Hm... See you later.
- Wait!
I could... help you look for him.
- Nah, I got it.
- Hey, "cool guy"...
Let me help you.
We can take Naga.
- Who's Naga?
- My best friend...
And a great tracker.
Your best friend is a...
polar bear-dog.
Somehow, that makes perfect sense.
I'll take that as a compliment,
city boy.
Well, this is his usual hangout.
You guys seen my brother
around here today?
Perhaps...
My memory's a little...
Foggy.
Maybe you can help
clear it up.
You're good Skoochy...
A real pro.
Yeah, I seen him.
- When?
- 'Bout noon.
What was he doing?
He was performing some
kinda monkey-rat circus.
And then...
And then, what?
Why did he leave?
Shady Shin showed up
and flashed some serious cash.
Bo took off with him
in his hot rod.
The Triple Threats,
the Red Monsoons,
the Agni Kais...
All the triads are muscling up
for something real big.
Now that's all you're getting
outta me!
- What's he talking about?
- Sounds like there's a turf war brewing.
And Bolin's about to get caught
right in the middle of it.
- So where are we headed?
- The Triple Threat Triad's headquarters.
Hopefully Bolin's there
and nothing's gone down yet.
Triple Threat Triad? I beat up
some of those yahoos when I got into town.
Why would Bolin
get tangled up with...
Whoah, Naga!
- That's Pabu!
- No, Naga.
Pabu's a friend,
not a snack.
We gotta hurry!
Something's not right.
There're usually thugs
posted out front.
We better be cautious.
Bolin, you in here?
Bolin!
Naga, come!
I can't bend.
- I can't bend!
- Calm down.
It'll wear off.
Those guys were chi-blockers.
- They're Amon's henchmen.
- Amon?
That anti-bending guy,
with the mask?
Yeah. He's the leader
of the Equalists.
What do they want
with the Triple Threats?
Whatever it is...
Can't be good.
I can't believe
Bolin got himself into this mess!
Mako, we are going
to save your brother.
I promise you that.
We've been out all night.
- No sign of him.
- We've gotta keep looking...
But where?
I have an idea!
The first day
I got into town,
I ran into an Equalist protestor,
over there.
- You think they'll know where Bolin is?
- It's our only lead right now.
So, why is Bolin running around
with the Triple Threat Triad, anyway?
Well, we... we used to do
some work for them, back in the day.
What? Are you
some kind of criminal?
No! You don't know
what you're talking about.
I just ran numbers for them
and stuff.
We were orphans
out on the street!
I did what I had to do to survive
and protect my little brother.
I'm sorry.
It must've been really hard.
Can I ask...
What happened to your parents?
They were mugged,
by a fire bender.
He cut them down
right in front of me.
I was eight.
Mako...
Bolin's the only family
I have left.
If anything happened to him...
Equality now! Equality now!
We - want - equality - now!
I, uh...
Non-benders of Republic City!
- That's the guy.
- Amon calls you to action!
Take back your city!
It's time for the...
It's you again!
You can not silence me,
Avatar!
Shut your yapper and listen up.
My friend got kidnapped by some
chi-blockers. Where'd they take him?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Oh, I think you do.
"Witness the Revelation tonight,
9 o'clock."
What's this "Revelation"?
Nothing that concerns
the likes of you two!
You better believe
it concerns us.
Spill it.
No one knows
what the Revelation is.
And I have no idea
what happened to your friend.
But, if he's a bender...
then my bet is, he's getting
what's coming to him!
Where's it happening?
Hey! What's going on
over there?
The Avatar's oppressing us!
Help!
Let's scram.
Why didn't the Equalists
put a location on these?
Probably because they don't want just
anyone waltzing into their big "Revelation".
Whatever that is...
I'll bet the information
is hidden on here, somehow.
Look at the backs.
There's four different images.
So... it's a puzzle?
Yeah... of a map!
Bingo! That must be
where it's going down.
This is the place.
- What are you doing?
- We'll attract less attention this way.
This is a private event.
No one gets in without an invitation.
Uh... invitation?
You mean, this?
The Revelation is upon us,
my brother and sister.
I knew
a lot of people hated benders,
but I've never seen so many
in one place.
Keep your eyes out for Bolin.
Please welcome your hero,
your savior,
Amon!
My quest for equality
began many years ago...
When I was a boy, my family and I
lived on a small farm.
We weren't rich,
and none of us were benders.
This made us very easy targets for
the Fire bender who extorted my father.
One day,
my father confronted this man.
But when he did...
That Fire bender
took my family from me.
Then... he took my face.
I've been forced to hide behind a mask
ever since.
As you know, the Avatar has
recently arrived in Republic City.
And if she were here,
she would tell you
that bending brings balance
to the world.
But, she is wrong.
The only thing bending
has brought to the world
is suffering.
It has been the cause
of every war,
in every era.
But that
is about to change.
I know you have been wondering,
"What is the Revelation?"
You are about to get your answer.
Since the beginning of time,
the Spirits have acted
as guardians of our world.
And they have spoken to me.
They say
the Avatar has failed humanity.
That is why
the spirits have chosen me,
to usher in a new era of balance.
They have granted me a power
that will make equality a reality.
The power to take
a person's bending away...
Permanently.
That's impossible. There's no way...
This guy's insane...
Now, for a demonstration.
Please welcome Lightning Bolt Zolt,
leader of the Triple Threat Triad,
and one of the most notorious criminals
in Republic City.
Oh, boo yourself!
- There's Bolin.
- Wait!
We can't fight them all.
We need to be smart about this.
Then come up with a game plan,
team captain!
Zolt has amassed a fortune
by extorting and
abusing non-benders,
but his reign of terror
is about to come to and end!
Now, in the interest of fairness,
I will give Zolt the chance
to fight
to keep his bending.
You're gonna regret doing that,
pal!
Wh...
What did you do to me?
Your Fire bending is gone.
Forever.
The era of bending is over.
A new era, of equality,
has begun!
No, ah!
Any ideas yet?
I think so.
See those machines?
They're powered by water and steam.
If you create some cover,
I can grab Bolin without anyone seeing.
- Then, we duck outta here.
- Works for me!
Mako...
- Good luck.
- You too.
It's not enough...
Hey, you!
Is there a problem, my brother?
What are you doing back here?
Uh, looking for the bathroom?
Come on...
Thanks!
This should be enough.
Uh, hello, Amon, sir?
I think there's been
a big misunderstanding.
- Bolin, you alright?
- Yes! Mako!
I love you!
You benders need to understand...
There's no place in the world for you
anymore.
I wouldn't count us out,
just yet.
Naga!
Stop!
I want - to be - on - your back.
The Avatar! That's her!
Let her go.
She's the perfect messenger
to tell the city of my power.
Thank goodness!
I was just about to send out
a search party. Are you alright?
Uh-uh.
Korra? What happened?
- Did you find your friend?
- Yes, but...
I was at an Equalist rally.
- I saw Amon.
- What?
He can take people's bending away.
- For good.
- That's...
That's impossible.
Only the Avatar
has ever possessed that ability.
But I saw him do it.
I believe you.
I don't know how Amon
has achieved this power.
But this means the revolution
is more dangerous than ever.
No bender is safe.
Subs by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net