Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master
all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
The Legend of Korra
Love is in the air!
Since Avatar Korra has arrived
in Republic City,
she's only had eyes for one fella:
Mako.
The feeling seemed mutual
until a fateful accident intervened.
Now, Mako's affections have fallen
right into the arms
of the beautiful Asami.
Will love prove to be
Korra's most formidable foe yet?
Season 1, Episode 5
"The Spirit of Competition"
Sync by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
Text: avatar.wikia.com
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's been great having you at so many
back-to-back practices, Korra.
Feels good to be back,
although Tarrlok isn't too happy
about my leave of absence.
Hey, you joined the Fire Ferrets
before you joined his taskforce.
Okay, come on,
team huddle time!
It's our first match of the tournament
tonight,
I know the three of us haven't been
a team for very long, but even so,
the Fire Ferrets have never been
this good.
- Are we ready?
- We're ready!
Not quite...
You'll need these!
- Hey, Asami.
- Good morning, Sweetie!
- These new uniforms look great!
- You look great, champ!
Well, teammates...
I'll see you before the match tonight,
Asami and I have a lunch date.
Okay, we'll check you guys later,
you know, we see you when we see ya.
So... Korra.
There they go, here we are,
alone in the gym.
Just you and me...
Two alone people.
Together...
- Alone.
- Uh...
I gotta head back to the Air Temple
to train with Tenzin. See ya!
So...
What do you think of Korra,
in a...
Girlfriend sort of way?
She's great!
But I think it makes more sense for me
to go for Asami!
I was talking
about a girlfriend for me!
Leave some ladies
for the rest of us!
I know, that's what I thought
you meant.
Well, I don't know, Bo.
It doesn't seem like a good idea
for you to date Korra.
You just said she was great,
two seconds ago.
Yeah, Korra is a great athlete,
and Avatar and stuff, but...
I don't know if she is really
"girlfriend material".
- She's more like a pal.
- Bro, you're nuts!
Korra and I
are perfect for each other!
She's strong, I'm strong;
she's fun, I'm fun;
she's beautiful, I'm gorgeous!
Okay, I don't care what you think;
I'm gonna ask Korra out.
Look, it just isn't smart
to date a teammate.
Especially during the tournament.
Keep your head out of the clouds
and your priorities straight.
- Okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I know, duh!
You know what I'm talking about,
Pabu.
Talkin' 'bout real love...
So how's it going
with the tall, dreamy Firebender boy?
You've been spending
a lot of time together lately!
Oooh, yeah, tell us all
about the magical romance.
What? Ha!
Listen to you two,
I-I'm not interested in Mako,
or any romantic stuff.
Besides, he's all into that pretty,
beautiful, elegant, rich girl...
But let's just pretend for a second
I am interested in him...
- What would I do?
- Ooh!
I just read a historical saga,
where the heroine fell in love
with the enemy general's son,
who's supposed
to marry the princess.
- You should do what she did.
- Tell me!
She rode a dragon into battle
and burned down the entire country,
then she jumped into a volcano...
It was so romantic...!
- Uh...
- No, no, no!
The best way to win a boys heart is to
brew a love potion of rainbows and sunsets
that makes true lovers sprout wings and
fly into a magical castle in the sky,
where they get married
and eat clouds with spoons,
and use stars as ice cubes
in their moonlight punch.
For ever and ever and ever!
The volcano is starting
to make more sense to me now.
[laughs, somewhere in the back]
Oh, hey, Pema.
Hm...
- Uh, how long were you standing there?
- Hm...
Long enough.
But trust me,
I know what you're going through.
Years ago I was
in the exact same situation...
With Tenzin.
Daddy was in love with someone else,
before you?
- That's right.
- So what did you do?
Well, for the longest time,
I did nothing.
I was so shy
and scared of rejection...
But watching my soul mate
spend his life with the wrong woman...
Became too painful.
So I hung my chin out there
and I confessed my love to Tenzin.
And the rest is history.
Wooow...!
Folks, after a year of waiting,
the pro-bending championship tournament
is finally here.
Tonight is the first set of matches
in our single elimination
sixteen team bracket.
And I gotta tell ya,
these are the most tenacious and talented
bending trios this arena has ever seen.
Introducing our first team,
the Future Industries Fire Ferrets!
[Cheers and booing by the crowd.]
And their opponents,
the Red Sands Rabbiroos.
[Cheers by the crowd.]
What an explosive opening volley!
Both teams quickly recover
and unleash a barrage of bending.
I am astonished
with the level of improvement
displayed here
by the Fire Ferrets.
No wonder the Avatar has been absent
from the papers lately.
She's obviously had her nose
to the grindstone in the gym.
The Ferrets advance
into Rabbiroo territory,
and they're holding nothing back.
Nice prowl there by Mako,
Bolin strikes, Uma dodges...
and all three Rabbiroos are down!
The Fire Ferrets
easily take round one.
Round two!
The Rabbiroos are looking
for payback,
and they go straight after Bolin.
Korra comes to his defense,
and she Water whacked Uli
back into Zone Two!
The Ferrets are on fire tonight,
and they win round two.
Round three!
With the Rabbiroos down two rounds,
they'll need a knockout to win,
and with the way
the Fire Ferrets are playing,
I don't see that happening.
These Ferrets are working together
like a well-oiled bending machine.
Bolin passes Ali
back into Zone Two,
and the Ferrets get the green light
to advance. [Cheers by the crowd.]
The Rabbiroos are just fighting
to stay at their feet at this point.
Down goes Ali, and Uma,
and Uli!
All three rounds go to
the Future Industries Fire Ferrets,
to win the opening match
of the tournament!
- U-hu! - Yes!
- That's what I'm talking about!
- Thank you, thank you very much!
- Wow, we were really connecting,
- ...out there, in that ring!
- Yeah!
You know, I feel like the two of us
have been connecting really well
- ...out of the ring, too!
- Uh...
- Sure! - So, I was thinking
we should spend some time together.
We've been spending
lots of time together!
I mean, outside of the team.
And not while searching for kidnapped
family members or fighting chi-blockers!
I don't now...
- Asami and I...
- Look, I really like you,
and I think we were meant
for each other!
Korra, I'm really sorry, but...
I just don't feel the same way
about you.
Forget I've ever said anything.
Congratulations guys!
You were so amazing
out there...
So... Korra...
I was thinking...
You and me, we could get
some dinner together...
- Sort of a date situation...
- Oh...
That's really sweet,
but I don't think so.
- I don't feel very date worthy.
- Are you kidding me?
You're the smartest, funniest,
toughest, buffest, talentedest...
- ...incrediblest girl in the world!
- Hm-hm-hm-hm!
Ah, you really feel that way
about me?
I felt that way
since the moment I saw you.
Trust me, I know we're gonna have
so much fun together.
You know what?
I could use some fun.
- Okay, sure.
- Yes!
Who's the luckiest guy in the world,
right here, Bolin!
- So how'd you like it?
- Hmm, it's delicious!
And totally authentic.
I didn't realize how much I missed
Water Tribe grub.
That's great,
cause this is my favorite joint.
See? You love Water Tribe food,
I love Water Tribe food,
just another reason
we are so great together.
They are good noodles!
Hey who's that creepy guy over there
who keeps glaring at us?
That's Tahno, and the Wolfbats.
Reigning champs,
three years running.
Don't make the eye contact!
Uh-oh, here he comes...
Now don't mess with this guy,
he's a nasty dude.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't the Fire Ferrets...
Pro-bending's saddest excuse
for a team.
Tell me, how did a couple of amateurs like
you luck your way into the tournament?
Especially you, Avatar.
You know, if you'd like to learn
how a real pro bends,
I could give you
some private lessons.
You wanna go toe-to-toe with me,
pretty boy?
Go for it.
I'll give you the first shot.
Korra, don't.
He's just trying to bait you. If you
hit him, we're out of the tournament.
Wohoho, I've never seen
someone harass Tahno like that.
You are one of a kind, Korra.
[burps]
[and the burping contest begins...]
- Ha-ha...
- Ha-ha!
- What kind of game are you playing?
- Uh... pro-bending?
- We've got the quarterfinal match...?
- No, I mean with Bolin.
You've got him all in a tizzy and I know
you're only using him to get back at me.
I am not,
we're just having fun together.
- What do you care, anyway?
- I'm looking out for my little brother.
- I don't wanna see his heart get broken.
- Wait a second...
You're not worried about him.
You're jealous!
- You do have feelings for me!
- What? "Jealous"?
Tsch!
Don't be ridiculous.
Admit it: you like me.
No! I'm with Asami!
Yeah, but when you're with her,
you are thinking about me, aren't you...
- Get over yourself!
- I'm just being honest!
- You're crazy!
- You're a liar!
Hey, Ma-ko-oh...!
Eight teams have been eliminated
and eight advance
into the quarter finals,
which get on their way tonight.
The rookies are about to take on the
former and longest reigning champs,
the Boarcupines.
Youth bashes against experience,
in a battle for the ages,
or rather of the ages.
Korra dodges and, ooh,
slams right into her teammate!
Down goes Mako, and Bolin,
and Korra!
Round one goes to the Boarcupines!
You were supposed to defend,
while I attacked!
I had an opening, so I took it!
What is up with you two?
Alright, whatever,
just pull together guys.
The Ferrets looking to mount
some offence here, in round two.
Bolin lets fly a flurry of attacks
He's a one man bending battalion.
The Ferrets have a tough time
finding their rhythm tonight,
but thanks to Bolin,
they narrowly nudge round two.
Not sure what's eating them,
but this is not the same team
who took out the Rabbiroos.
Round three is a tie!
We go to a tie-breaker,
to decide the match.
The Fire Ferrets win the coin toss!
- Which element do you choose?
- I got this.
I know you usually handle this,
but frankly, your head's not in the game.
I'm gonna take this one.
We choose Earth.
Looks like the Earthbenders will collide,
in the tie-breaker faceoff.
Bolin goes in for the grapple...
Chang reversed it.
Bolin strikes from midair,
knocking Chang to the edge of the circle.
Another strike from Bolin,
and Chang is in the drain!
The Future Industries Fire Ferrets
win their quarter final match!
That was a close one, folks!
Youth trumps experience tonight.
We need to talk.
Look, sometimes you can be
so infuriating. I-
Save your breath.
You've already made it clear
how you feel about me.
No I haven't.
What I'm trying to say is...
As much as you drive me crazy...
I also think
you're pretty amazing.
- So... you do like me?
- Yes! But...
I like Asami, too.
I don't know, things are complicated.
But feeling really confused an-
Bolin, this isn't what you think.
- Great! Look at what you did!
- You're blaming me?
- You're the one who kissed me!
- You kissed me back!
"Well-played", Korra...
'Morning, Narook.
My brother here?
Thanks.
Come on... wake up.
Takin' you home, bro.
Don't call me that...
You're not my brother!
You're a brother-betrayer!
The only one I can trust anymore...
Is Pabu...
Pabu loves me...
You're a mess, and we've got
the biggest match of our lives tonight.
- Let's go.
- No!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
You, traitor!
Guess I'll have to do this
the hard way.
O-o-oh, why...?
I told you dating a teammate
was a bad idea.
You're a bad idea!
Put me down...!
Put... me... down...
You can't find two teams
more evenly matched
in age, size and strength
than the Fire Ferrets
and the Buzzard Wasps.
Believe me, I've looked!
This should be a pulse-pounding
semi-final, folks!
The Buzzard Wasps open with a
flawlessly executed combo!
All three Ferrets take an early visit
to Zone Two!
And Mako's knocked
all the way back to the Zone Three!
The Fire Ferrets have been struggling
to stay alive since the opening bell.
All three players
are totally out of sync tonight!
Uh! That has got to sting!
And Bolin loses his noodles.
Literally! Which reminds me.
This match is brought to you
by our sponsor:
"Flameo Instant Noodles".
Noodliest noodles
in the United Republic!
The Buzzard Wasps fly deeper
into Ferret territory.
And Mako plunges into the pool!
Can the Fire Ferrets hold on?
The Wasps have the Ferrets
backed up to the edge now,
and the Ferrets are bailed out
by the bell!
They had better pull themselves together,
folks, for round two,
otherwise they can kiss the finals
good-bye!
Hey! Watch it!
The Wasps take advantage
of Mako's unforced error
and Bolin's in the pool!
Ooh, and a blatant hold
by the Avatar!
Unnecessary roughness!
Move back one zone!
I'll "unnecessarily" rough you up!
And the Avatar is slapped
with the yellow fan!
The Ferrets are their own worst enemy
right now.
It's just sad to watch.
With the Buzzard Wasps leading
two rounds to zilch,
the Ferrets' only hope of winning
is with a knockout.
Well, I guess
there's always "next year".
Come on, we still have a chance!
Even if it is a slim one.
The way we're playing, we don't even
deserve to be in the finals.
Look, if we don't pull together
and work as a team,
- ...we'll never forgive ourselves.
- Let's just get this over with.
The sooner, the better.
Bolin's knocked into Zone Two,
followed quickly by his brother.
And Bolin takes a zinger,
to the shoulder.
Looks like it's a clean hit.
Owww!
Bolin!
Mako's in the drinker
and out of the match.
And Bolin keeps playing
with one good arm!
I gotta hand it to him,
this kid's got grit.
But how long can he keep it up?
Apparently, not very long.
The Ferret's dream
of making it to the finals
now rests in the Avatar's hands.
But with three on one,
I don't like her odds.
Are you OK?
- How's your shoulder?
- Aah...
It's messed up pretty bad.
But I think I'll be all right.
Are we... gonna be all right?
Of course we are.
We're brothers.
We'll get through this mess.
- I'm sorry...
- Me too.
- Girls...
- Seriously.
What an unbelievable effort here,
by Korra.
She's dodging every Element
the Wasps throw at her.
The Avatar
finally gains some grounds,
but with only ten seconds remaining,
it's likely too little, too late.
It's the big kabosh!
What a knockout!
- Yes!
- We did it!
Yeees!
It didn't seem possible, folks, but
the Fire Ferrets are headed to the finals!
Ha-haaa!
- Shoulder, shoulder!
- Sorry!
That... was pretty much
the coolest thing I've ever seen.
Thanks for not giving up on us.
We never would have made it
this far without you.
I owe you. Big time.
You're welcome.
So...
I know things are confusing
right now...
- But I hope we can still be friends.
- Definitely.
Ooh...
You boys smell something in here?
Wait, I know what that is...
Yeah, that's the scent of losers.
I hope we see you in the finals.
- Then we'll see who the losers really are.
- Yeah...
I'm peeing in my pants over here.
And now, the defending champs,
the White Falls Wolfbats!
Great job!
What a comeback, Korra!
- I've never seen a hat trick like that.
- Oh, thanks.
But, if it hadn't been
for you and your father,
we wouldn't have had
the chance to play.
So, thank you.
Uh, if everyone's done
with the little "thank you" party...
- I need some medical attention over here!
- Oh, let me help!
Ow! Haven't you hurt me enough,
woman?
Relax, I'm a healer.
I learned from Katara,
the best there is.
No, no, no, no...
Oh-o-o...
That's the stuff...
Bolin...
I'm sorry I hurt your feelings.
I didn't mean to let things
get so out of hand.
Ah... I'll be alright.
- But we had fun together, didn't we?
- I had a great time, honestly!
You are one of a kind, Bolin.
Please, go on...
I enjoy praise.
Your winners!
The Wolfbats!
What?
How is it over already?
With a brutal round one knockout,
the defending champs
secure their spot in the finals.
I hope the Ferrets know a good doctor,
because they're gonna need one!
Sync by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
Text: avatar.wikia.com
www.tvsubtitles.net