Water.
Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony.
Then, everything changed when the Fire Nation attacked.
Only the Avatar, master of all four elements, could stop them.
But when the world needed him most, he vanished.
A hundred years passed, and my brother and I discovered the new Avatar...
...an airbender named Aang.
And although his airbending skills are great.
He has a lot to learn before he's ready to save anyone.
But I believe Aang can save the world.
Book One: Water
Chapter Fourteen: The Fortuneteller
Look!
He is taunting us. You are so gonna be dinner!
Hey! Where's the fishing line?
Oh, I didn't think you would need it, Sokka.
Aahh, it's all tangled!
Not tangled... woven. I made you a necklace, Katara.
I thought since you lost your other one...
Thanks, Aang. I love it.
Great, Aang.
Maybe instead of saving the world you can go into the jewelry making business.
I don't see why I can't do both.
Stop taunting me!
So, how do I look?
You mean all of you or just your neck? I mean, uh, both look great.
Smoochie, smoochie, someone's in love.
I... well...
Stop teasing him, Sokka. Aang's just a good friend. A sweet little guy... just like Momo.
Thanks.
Someone's being attacked by a platypus bear!
Well, hello there. Nice day, isn't it?
Make noise, it'll run off!
No, play dead, he'll lose interest!
Whoa! Close one.
Run down hill, then climb a tree!
No, punch him in the bill!
And then run in zigzags!
No need. It's going to be fine.
Whoa there!
Mmm! Lunch! Lucky for you we came along.
Thanks, but everything was already under control.
Not to worry, Aunt Wu predicted I'd have a safe journey.
Aunt who?
No, Aunt Wu. She's the fortuneteller from my village. Awful nice knowing your future.
Wow, it must be. That explains why you were so calm.
But the fortuneteller was wrong!
You didn't have a safe journey, you were almost killed!
But I wasn't. All right, have a good one!
Oh, and Aunt Wu said if I met any travelers to give them this.
Maybe we should go see Aunt Wu and learn our fortunes. It could be fun.
Oh come on, fortunetelling is nonsense.
What do ya know, an umbrella!
That proves it.
No it doesn't... you can't really tell the future.
I guess you're not really getting wet then.
Of course she predicted it was gonna rain. The sky's been gray all day.
Just admit you might be wrong and you can come under the umbrella.
Look, I'm going to predict the future now... "It's going to keep drizzling."
See!
Not everyone has the gift, Sokka.
Aunt Wu is expecting you.
Really?
My name is Meng and I'm Aunt Wu's assistant.
Well hello there.
Hello.
Can I get you some tea, or some of Aunt Wu's special bean curd puffs?
I'll try a curd puff.
Just a second. So what's your name?
Aang.
That rhymes with Meng! And you've got some pretty big ears, don't you?
I... guess...
Oh, don't be modest. They're huge!
Well Aang, it is very nice to meet you. Very nice.
Likewise.
I can't believe we're here in the house of nonsense.
Try to keep an open mind, Sokka.
There are things in this world that just can't be explained.
Wouldn't it be nice to have some insight into your future?
It would be nice to have some bean curd puffs.
Oh Meng! Aunt Wu says I'm going to meet my true love!
He's going to give me a rare panda lilly.
That's so romantic. I wonder if my true love will give me a rare flower.
Good luck with that!
Is that the big eared guy who Aunt Wu predicted you'd marry?
Enjoy your snack.
Welcome young travelers. Now, who's next? Don't be shy.
I guess that's me.
Not bad. Not bad.
I'm good on puffs.
So... what do you think they're talking about back there?
Boring stuff, I'm sure. Love.
Who she's going to marry. How many babies she's gonna have.
Yeh... dumb stuff like that... well, I've gotta find a bathroom!
Your palms are so smooth... do you use moisturizer?
Actually, I have this special seaweed lotion. I could get you some if you want.
So, do you see anything interesting in my love line?
I feel great romance for you. The man you're going to marry...
Tell me more!
I can see that he is a very powerful bender.
Looks like someone had a pretty good bathroom break.
Yeh, when I was in there...
I don't even wanna know!
Who's next?
Okay, let's get this over with.
Your future is full of struggle and anguish, most of it self-inflicted.
But, you didn't read my palms or anything!
I don't need to... it's written all over your face.
You then, come with me.
This is the most reliable method of telling your fortune. The bones never lie.
Go on, pick one.
Now throw it on the fire.
The heat makes cracks in the bones and I read the bone cracks to tell your destiny.
Wow, that's a big crack.
I've never seen this before.
Oh my!
The old destiny, this is incredible! You will be involved in a great battle,...
...an awesome conflict between the forces of good and evil,...
...a battle whose outcome will determine the fate of the whole world!
Yeh, yeh, I knew that already, but did it say anything about a girl?
A girl? You want to know about love?
Yes!
I'm sorry, but I didn't see anything.
Oh look! I must have missed something.
Right here... it says, "trust your heart and you will be with the one you love."
Really!? Thank you, Aunt Wu!
Well, now you got to see for yourselves that fortunetelling is just a big, stupid hoax.
You're just saying that because you're going to make yourself unhappy your whole life.
That woman is crazy! My life will be calm, and happy and joyful!
That doesn't prove anything!
Well, I liked my predictions. Certain things are going to turn out very well.
They sure are.
Why, what did she tell you?
Some stuff. You'll find out.
What's with the sky?
We are waiting for Aunt Wu to come and read the clouds...
...to predict the fate of the whole village.
That cloud looks like a fluffy bunny.
You better hope that's not a bunny...
...the fluffy bunny cloud forecasts doom and destruction.
Do you even hear yourself?
The cloud reading will tell us if Mount Makapu...
...will remain dormant for another year or if it will erupt.
We used to have a tradition once a year of going up the mountain...
...to check the volcano ourselves, but ever since Aunt Wu moved to the village...
...twenty years ago we have a tradition of not doing that.
I can't believe you would trust your lives to that crazy old woman's superstition.
Shhhh!! She's coming!
Hey Aang, doesn't that cloud look like a flower?
Huh? Sure, I guess.
Hey Katara, don't you think that cloud looks like a flower?
Shh!!
Bending arrow cloud... good crops this year, nice big harvest!
Arg! Good news!
Wavy moon shape cloud... let's see? gonna be a great year for twins.
Yes!
And a cumulus cloud with a twisted nob coming off the end of it...
...the village will not be destroyed by the volcano this year!
Since I got you here, uh, there's something I want to tell you.
I like you, but more than normal.
Never mind.
Hi, Aunt Wu. Sorry to bother you.
Anytime.
About this man I'm supposed to marry...
...is he gonna be handsome? Oh, I hope he's tall!
Ahh, you want another reading.
Yes, please!
I can't believe all these saps. Someone really needs to scream some sense at them.
They seem happy, Sokka.
Not for long. I'm gonna prove Aunt Wu's predictions are nonsense.
Hey, you. I bet Aunt Wu told you to wear those red shoes, didn't she?
Yeh, she said I'd be wearing red shoes when I met my true love.
Uh-huh. And how many times have you worn those shoes since you got that fortune?
Everyday.
Then of course it's going to come true!
Really? You think so? I'm so excited!
...and then you'll have your third great grandchild...
...before quietly passing away in your sleep. Is that enough information for you?
Wow, thanks Aunt Wu. Oh, wait, one more thing.
How warmly should I dress tomorrow?
You want me to do a reading for that?
I don't care what Aunt Wu told you, you have to take a bath sometime!
So, Sokka, you know some stuff about ladies, right?
Some stuff? You've come to the right place. What can I do you for?
Well, there's this girl...
I think I know who you mean.
You do? And you're ok with it?
Of course I am. And, to tell you the truth,...
...I've been picking up the subtle vibe that she likes you too.
She does!?
Oh yeh, she's crazy about ya. All ya have to do now is not mess it up.
Well, how do I do that?
The number one mistake nice guys like you make being too nice.
You can be too nice?
Yup. If you want to keep her interested you have to act aloof,...
...like you don't really care one way or the other.
Well... okay.
Hey Aang, I was wondering...
See ya later.
Wow, that kid is good.
...and you'll be fine as long as you've got a scarf. Bye bye now.
Okay, okay, but, one more thing.
All right, what is it?
Should I eat a mango or a papaya for breakfast tomorrow?
Papaya!
Ohhh, I hate papaya.
Oh, hey Katara. I didn't see you there.
Hey Aang.
That's ok, I'm busy with my own stuff.
Ugh. Papaya please.
So... papaya.
Uh-huh. Would you like some?
You know me. I don't really care what I eat.
Ok then. See you later.
Maybe aloof isn't my style.
Oh! A panda lilly!
Did you see that?
Excuse me. Where can a guy find one of those things?
I can't believe you're dragging me all the way up here for a stupid flower.
Not just any flower... a panda lilly. I've seen it in action and boy does it work.
Flowers are fine once you're married,...
...but at this early stage it's critical that you maintain maximum aloofness.
But my heart is telling me to get this flower,...
...and Aunt Wu said if I trusted my heart I would be with the one I love.
What? Don't tell me you believe in that stuff too.
Well, Aunt Wu hasn't been wrong yet.
Why should she be wrong about love?*
There, on the rim!
Oh no! Aunt Wu was wrong.
Those people all think they're safe. We've got to warn 'em.
There's no time to walk. Grab on.
Hi, Katara.
Can you believe she won't let me in? And after all the business I've given her?
But, she doesn't even charge.
I know, but still.
Well, we have other things to worry about. Aunt Wu was wrong about the volcano.
Sokka, you tried to convince me she was wrong before.
It's going to take an awful lot to change my min...
Oh, no!
Everyone! That volcano is gonna blow any second. Aunt Wu was wrong!
Yeh, yeh, we know you don't believe in Aunt Wu, "Mr. Science and Reason Lover."
If you won't listen to him, maybe you'll listen to me.
I want to believe Aunt Wu and her predictions as much as you do,...
...but my brother and Aang saw the lava with their own eyes.
Well I heard Aunt Wu's prediction with my own ears.
Please listen to us! You are all in danger! And we have to get out of here.
You can't rely on Aunt Wu's prediction. You have to take fate into your own hands.
Look! Can your fortunetelling explain that?
Can your science explain why it rains?
Yes! Yes, it can!
They just won't listen to reason.
But they will listen to Aunt Wu.
I know, that's the problem.
Well, it's about to become the solution. We're taking fate in our own hands.
First, I need to borrow Aunt Wu's cloud reading book.
Shh... we don't want anyone to hear us.
Oh, oh! I didn't see you there.
You don't like me. Do you?
Of course I like you.
But not the way I like you.
Oh. I guess not.
It's ok. It's just really hard when you like someone,...
...but they don't think of you that way.
I know what you mean.
She's beautiful, by the way.
Huh?
That water tribe girl. I can see why you like her so much.
She's sweet, she's a bender, and her hair seems so manageable.
Don't worry.
You're gonna meet a great guy who's gonna completely fall for you. I know it.
Thanks. Wait! Don't you want this?
How did you know?
I've kind of been stalking you... heh!
Oh, thanks. I... I guess.
Clouds are made of water and air so between the two of us...
...we ought to be able to bend them into any shape we want.
I found it. The symbol for volcanic doom.
Aunt Wu, look! Something is happening in the clouds.
That's very strange. It shouldn't... Oh my!
We can still save the village if we act fast. Sokka has a plan.
Lava is gonna flow downhill to this spot.
If we can dig a deep enough trench...
...we can channel all the lava away from the village to the river.
If any of you are earthbenders come with me.
I'm an earthbender!
I'm not!
Everybody else grab a shovel... come on, we've gotta hurry!
Dig faster! Dig faster!
Everyone needs to evacuate! We'll come for you when it's safe!
It's too much! It's gonna overflow!
Man, sometimes I forget what powerful bender that kid is.
Wait, what did you just say?
Nothing, just that Aang is one powerful bender.
I suppose he is...
By the way, we kind of borrowed your book.
So you messed with the clouds did you!
Very clever!
No offense, but I hope this taught everyone a lesson...
...about not relying too much on fortunetelling.
But Aunt Wu predicted the village wouldn't be destroyed, and it wasn't.
She was right, after all.
I hate you.
It's ok, Sokka. Everything's gonna be all right.
Can I ask you something?
Of course, honey.
You didn't really see love in my fortune, did you?
You just told me what I wanted to hear.
I'll tell you a little secret, young Airbender. Just as you reshaped those clouds,...
...you have the power to reshape your own destiny.
Goodbye everyone! It was so nice to meet you! Take care, Meng.
Take care!
Floozy.
Subtitle by rendy1287 [at gmail dot com]
Thanks to Acastus for The Transcript.
http://www.avatarspiritmedia.net/
www.tvsubtitles.net