Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all
four elements
and bring balance to the world.
The Legend of Korra
Although the Hundred Year War has long passed,
we are not living in a time of peace.
These revolutionaries who call themselves "Equalists"
are not interested in equality at all.
They just want to wage war against benders.
Chief Beifong was supposed to protect Republic City,
but she was powerless to stop
Amon's attack on the arena.
She has failed us all.
If we are to survive these dire times,
our law enforcement needs new leadership.
Book one
Chapter Seven : The Aftermath
I still can't believe they're
shutting this place down.
Yeah. We had some good
memories here, didn't we?
Guys! Great news. You don't
have to go back on the streets.
I talked to Tenzin and made
all the arrangements.
You can come live on Air
Temple island with me!
Oh, we'd love to, but...
Asami already invited us to
live in her dad's giant mansion!
From here on out, it's gonna
be the lap of luxury for us.
Hey Korra, I was hoping
you would stop by.
I was just leaving.
So, I guess I'll see you
guys around, some time.
Why not tomorrow? I'd love to
have you come visit the estate.
I don't know, I have some ...
Avatar stuff to do.
Come on Korra.We all deserve a little rest
and relaxation after all this craziness.
We could swim in Asami's pool.
It'll be fun!
All right Pabu.
Great, we'll see you tomorrow.
Looks like our intel was good.
There's enough evidence here to
bury Cabbage Corp for an eternity.
This is an outrage! I'm innocent!
Yeah, yeah. That's what they all say...
Is it true that Cabbage Corp is
conspiring with the Equalists?
No! Not my Cabbage Corp!
Hey, Korra.
Tahno?
Listen, I know we're not
exactly best friends,
but I'm sorry Amon took your bending.
I've been to the best healers in the city.
Whatever Amon did to me, it's permanent.
You gotta get him for me.
Mr. Sato, if you remember anything else
about what you saw during Amon's attack,
be sure to let us know.
I'm happy to help any way I can.
I want these Equalists to pay for what they've done.
We're ready for you now.
See you around... Avatar.
Earth bending bomb!
Avatar Korra ... has arrived.
Hey Korra! Glad you made it!
Welcome to paradise!
Looks like you guys settled right in.
Pretty much, except someone forgot to
ask her father if we could stay here.
Yeah, but I smoothed it over with him. It's
easier to ask for forgiveness than permission.
This is the greatest place in the world!
Watch this, watch this.
Fetch me my towel, good sir.
Yes, Master ... Bolin.
Master Bolin! Ha, I love this guy.
Now pat me dry.
As you wish.
Don't forget Master Pabu.
Wouldn't dream of it, sir.
So, what do you have
planned for us today.
Let me guess, shopping, makeovers...
Ouh, Ouh. I want makeovers!
I have something a little
more exciting in mind.
Pretty cool, huh?
Way cooler than a makeover.
This is where Future Industries test-drives
their Satomobiles.
Ever been behind the wheel?
The only thing I know how to
drive is a polar bear dog.
You want me to take you for a spin?
Let's do it!
That was amazing! I didn't
think we'd make it.
Well, you can't be afraid
to mix it up some times.
I gotta admit, I had you pegged wrong.
I thought you were kind of... prissy.
Eh-No offense!
It's alright, people usually assume
that I'm daddy's helpless little girl,
but I can handle myself.
I mean, I've been in self-defense
classes since I was this high.
My dad made sure that I would
always be able to protect myself.
Smart guy.
Emergency, emergency
coming through, beep beep!
Is there another bathroom I can use?
We have a lady's powder room upstairs, first door
on your right. You can freshen up in there.
Thanks.
No, no! No, I assure you, everything
is going exactly as planned.
Yes... Luckily, the Cabbage Corp
investigation has bought us enough time.
Trust me, by the end of the week...
we'll be ready to strike!
You're leaving? But I-I thought...
Uh, sorry! I forgot, I'm supposed
to airsit, I mean babybend,
I-I mean babysit the air bender kids.
See you later!
So, you think Mr. Sato manufactured those gloves
for the Equalists, then framed Cabbage Corp?
That's a bold accusation,
but what proof do you have?
Well, I don't exactly have proof but I know
what I heard.
Sato's up to something.
He does have the means...
and he has a motive.
That's right.
A motive? What is it?
Twelve years ago, the Agni Kai
Triad robbed Sato's mansion.
A Firebender killed Sato's
wife during the break in.
That's terrible.
It was tragic. It's possible he's been
harboring anti-bending sentiment all this time.
Maybe we should look at Mr. Sato
a little more closely.
What's going on? Why are they
asking Hiroshi more questions?
I overheard him on
the phone yesterday.
Asami, I don't know how to tell you this, but I think
your father might be involved with the Equalists.
What? I don't believe this.
You spied on Hiroshi?
What's your problem?
Mr. Sato, we just have a few
follow-up question for you.
My father is innocent.
Just because we're not benders doesn't
mean we support those awful Equalists.
Equalists!? Is that
what this is about?
I can assure you I have nothing
to do with those radicals.
You don't know what you're
talking about, Korra.
I overheard you on the phone.
You said the Cabbage Corp investigation bought
you time, and you're getting ready to strike.
Explain that.
This is all just a
misunderstanding,
resulting from the young
Avatar's overactive imagination.
My number one competitor was
knocked out of the game,
it's providing me an opportunity to strike
the market with a new line of Satomobiles.
It's just business. Nothing nefarious.
In order to put all
suspicions to rest,
might we have a look into your
factories and warehouses.
If you feel it's necessary you're welcome
to search all of Future Industries.
Is it possible, the presidents of Cabbage Corp
and Future Industries both have Equalist ties,
or did Hiroshi Sato frame his
long time rival, Lau Gan-Lan.
Or did chief Beifong just
plain arrest the wrong man,
so far the investigation has yielded
no evidence to incriminate Sato.
I can't believe, we
didn't find anything.
It would appear Hiroshi is innocent.
Ok you did your search,
now you can all leave.
So, I hope you're convinced now.
No, I'm not. I don't care how cooperative
Hiroshi has been, I know he's lying.
Why are you doing this?
Are you that jealous of me and Asami?
What? Don't be ridiculous, that
has nothing to do with it.
If you don't drop this,
consider our friendship over.
I'm sorry, Hiroshi is not
the man you think he is.
I think you guys
should hear this.
If you want to find the truth, meet me under
the North end of Silk Road bridge at midnight.
Psst. Over here.
Listen I joined the Equalists
because I believed in what Amon said,
I thought he could make life
better for us, non-benders,
but I didn't sign up
for this, this war.
What do you have on Hiroshi Sato?
He manufactured those gloves for the Equalists.
I knew it!
And there are rumor he's working on something
even bigger, some new kind of weapon.
We searched all of Future
Industries and found nothing.
That's because he has a secret factory.
Where?
It's right underneath
the Sato mansion.
Raiding the Sato mansion is a risky move
with Tarrlok breathing down your neck.
- If we're wrong...
- I know, I can kiss my job good bye,
but protecting Republic
City is all I care about.
We can't let Amon get his hands on this new weapon.
What are you doing here?
We have reason to believe there's a
factory hidden below the mansion.
I think I would have noticed if there
was a factory underneath my house.
The lies you people come up with
just to persecute my father.
Where's your father?
In his workshop
behind the house.
Dad? Hello?
Chief, the estate's been secured. No one
has left the workshop since we arrived.
Perhaps we just couldn't
see him leaving.
There's a tunnel beneath the workshop
running deep into the mountain side.
What? There's no tunnel.
Do you think your Dad
knows about this tunnel?
I don't understand, there
must be an explanation.
Maybe you don't know everything
about your father. I'm sorry.
Officers, into the tunnel, be cautious.
You three, stay up here. Officer
Song keep an eye on them.
Not your average backyard workshop.
And I'm guessing those are the new weapons.
Hiroshi was lying alright,
but where is he?
What was that? We need to get down
there and see what's going on.
Absolutely not, you're staying
put until the chief comes back.
Alright, we'll stay put, but can
we wait outside or something?
It's so dusty in this workshop.
No! We're waiting right here.
Ok, but don't blame me if I start...
if I start snee...snee...snee...
What's your problem bud?
I'm about to...
Sorry pal, we now you're
just doing your job.
Yeah, just stay put until
the chief comes back.
That sounds very familiar, doesn't it?
Why? Because you said it.
Asami, you should stay
here, we'll check it out.
I have to find out the
truth about my father.
I understand, that's why I'm
going down to find out for you.
Please.
Alright.
Be careful.
I'm afraid, you won't be able to
metal bend that wall chief Beifong.
It's solid platinum.
My mecha tanks are platinum as well.
Not even your renowned mother could
bend a metal so pure.
Hiroshi, I knew you were a
lying-no-good Equalist.
Come out here and...
And do what, young Avatar?
Face the wrath of your bending?
No. I think I'll fight from inside
here, where my odds are a little more "equal".
That source was a setup,
you lured us down here.
Guilty as charged.
Korra!
Well, I'd say that was a
near flawless test run.
Load everyone into the transport
and deliver them to Amon.
Oh no!
Korra was right. We gotta
do something. Quick.
Not so fast, boys.
Hello Mr.Sato. Wow!
What a really swell scary factory, you
have here under your giant mansion.
Sponsoring our team, supporting the
Avatar, it was all just a big cover.
Yes and the most difficult part,
was watching my daughter traipse around
with a firebending street rat like you!
Dad, stop!
Why?
Sweetie...
I wanted to keep you out of
this for as long as I could,
but now that you
know the truth...
please, forgive me.
These people...these benders...
they took away your mother.
The love of my life.
They ruined the world,
but with Amon we can fix it and
build a perfect world together.
We can help people like us everywhere.
Join me, Asami.
No.
I love you, Dad.
Let's get out of here!
My metal benders are on their way
to Amon and it's all my fault.
Tarrlok's right. I
failed as chief.
First thing in the morning, I'm
handing in my resignation.
No! You can't give up like this.
I'm not giving up, I'm gonna find
my officers and take Amon down.
But I'm gonna do it, my way!
Outside the law!
I'm sorry, I didn't believe you,
but Asami's dad being an Equalist
is not an easy thing to believe.
Even now.
I know, I'm sorry this
whole thing happened.
So does your offer to live at
the Air Temple still stand?
Of course, it does.
And Asami's welcome too.
Thank you so much.
After everything she's been through,
she's going to need you Mako.
Transcribed then subtitled then synced
by Patrick of Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net