Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
The equalists are on the attack.
The Lieutenant and his chi-blockers
invaded air temple island
and forced Tenzin
and his family to flee.
In the daring escape
lin beifong sacrificed herself
and saved the airbenders.
But she was captured
and Amon took her bending away.
Now team Avatar is in hiding
as they await help
from General Iroh
and the united forces.
One Book: Air, Episode 11
"Skeletons in the Closet"
It is a glorious day my equalist
brothers and sisters.
Amon has torn down the tyrannical
bending government!
He has declared
bending, illegal!.
And he has the Avatar
on the run.
Our great leader has a
vision for the future.
One day soon bending
will no longer exist
and we will live in a world where
everyone is finally equal!
The united forces are on their way
right now to try and stop that dream
but we will prevail!
Can you believe Hiroshi?
"The Avatar's on the run".
I'm not running from anyone.
Let's go back up there
and knock some heads.
They'll never know
what hit them.
Relax.
General Iroh's coming with an
entire fleet of battleships.
Then Amon will be the
one who's running.
I hate this "being patient"
stuff.
You two were gone a while.
We were doing reconnaissance.
Whatever.
Welcome back!
Hope you worked up an appetite
because dinner is served.
Thanks so much for letting us hide
out with you the past few days.
Honored to oblige.
My associates and I heartily
oppose Amon's so-called
"equalist" policies.
We got benders and non-benders
living together down here
You are a wise
and noble hobo.
This is the best-tasting street
gruel I've ever had.
Seriously.
I culled it from the finest dumpsters
the city has to offer.
Can't sleep either?
No, I have this awful
pit in my stomach.
Me too.
It's so crazy.
A few months ago,
I was in the South pole practicing
for my firebending test
and now I'm in the middle
of an all-out war.
I know.
We didn't even
know each other then.
And now, I can't imagine
my life without you in it.
You're the most loyal brave, and
selfless person I've ever known.
I think you're pretty
incredible too but
you already knew that.
I should probably
try to get some sleep.
Me too.
Good night.
You will now be cleansed
of your impurity.
Next.
Coast is clear.
Once the united forces arrive we
need to be ready to help
in any way we can.
They're here.
Amon had to know
we were coming.
So why aren't we meeting
any resistance?
Wait a second.
Where are the equalist
airships?
I don't see any mecha-tanks
either.
Something's not right.
It's a trick!
Water and earthbenders
detonate those mines!
What is that sound?
What now?
Where does Hiroshi find the
time to keep inventing
new evil machines?
Incoming!
It's all right.
I've got you.
Avatar Korra...
You saved my life.
Thank you.
I was prepared to deal with
sato's mecha-tanks
but not these new
high-speed aircraft.
I know.
Every time we think we have an
advantage Amon outsmarts us.
No matter what our plan is
he always has a better one.
Amon is winning so far but we're
not out of the fight yet.
I like this man's confidence.
So, How are we not
out of the fight?
A second wave of reinforcements
is on the way.
But I need to warn them.
Do you still have a way
to get a message out?
I know just the
man for the job.
And who is the recipient
of this top-secret message?
Commander Bumi.
Second division of
the united forces.
Tenzin's brother?
Yes.
A bit of a wild man
but the bravest Commander
you'll ever meet.
Ready, sir!
Fleet ambushed and destroyed
by equalist aircraft.
Retreat to red sand island
until my signal.
Do not approach city until
you receive the all-clear.
Now comes the hard part.
We need to ground those aircraft,
otherwise Bumi's fleet will never
be able to retake the city.
They flew in from
this direction.
The airfield must be somewhere
over this Mountain range.
Everyone get ready.
We leave at dawn.
It's time to take
down my father.
Wait.
I'm sorry, but
I'm not going with
you tomorrow.
What?
Why not?
I'm sick and tired of
hiding from Amon.
It's time I face him.
That's not a good plan.
We need to stick together.
I'm not waiting for him
to hunt me down.
My gut's telling me
it's time to end this.
On my terms.
Korra, this is not a mission you
should be handling alone.
She won't be.
I'm going with you.
You don't have
to do that.
Yes, I do.
My grandfather would respect
the Avatar's instinct.
So will I.
Love you, little bro.
Love you back, big bro.
Korra, Amon is a nasty dude.
Be careful.
I will.
Good luck.
If you're going into the mountains,
you should bring naga.
Take good care
of bolin for me.
Asami.
I'm sorry things got
so messed up between us
but whatever happens today.
I want you to know how
much I care about you.
I care about you too.
Good fortune and success
to you, Valiant heroes!
There's Amon!
We need to get into the temple.
Then, when he returns...
We ambush him.
What are you two
doing here?
Uh..., We were
just transferred.
Well, you're getting
transferred again.
Amon wants extra security
at the arena today.
The arena?,
For what?
The rally.
You should have been
briefed about this.
We'll be there, sir!
I know another way in.
Let's hide in the attic.
Uh...!,
we're not alone up here.
Tarrlok?
I don't suppose
you're here to rescue me?
We had no idea
you were here.
Are there other prisoners
on the island?
No,
I'm the only one.
And what makes you so special?
I'm Amon's brother.
Amon is from the northern
water tribe.
He is a waterbender
and a bloodbender,
just like I was.
What?!
Did you know this all along?
No, not until after he captured me.
How did your brother end
up becoming Amon?
It all began with my father,
Yakone...
With the help of his former gang,
he escaped prison
and underwent surgery
to change his appearance.
He assumed a new identity
and settled down in the
northern water tribe.
That's where he met my mother,
a warm caring woman.
Before long, they started
a family together.
Amon was the firstborn
under the name Noatak.
I was born three years later.
Noatak was a good-natured kid,
always looking out for me.
Those were the good years,
before my brother and I discovered
we were waterbenders.
At first, we were excited
by our new abilities
but our training brought out
a different side of my father.
Tarrlok!
You better shape up or you'll be out here
in the cold all night until you get it right.
I'm trying, but...
Try harder!
Your brother was never this sloppy.
Dad, he'll get it.
He just needs time.
Don't talk back to me, son.
Ever!
Even back then,
my brother wanted everyone
to be treated fairly and equally.
When I was seven,
my father took me and Noatak
on a hunting trip,
far away from our home.
He told us his true identity
was Yakone,
Republic city's most
notorious crime boss
and that he was once a
bloodbender of rare skill.
What's bloodbending?
The most powerful and feared
form of bending in the world.
It was declared illegal
thanks to that coward, katara.
Our family has the strongest
line of bloodbenders in history.
You boys have this power
inside of you
and I will teach you
to master it.
What happened
to your bending, dad?
The Avatar stole it from me.
That's why I brought
you out here,
to learn your destiny.
You two will become bloodbenders
of the highest order.
When the time is right you
will claim Republic city
and you will
destroy the Avatar.
You must avenge me.
That is your purpose in life.
The good days
were behind us.
Every full moon,
our father took us on another
supposed "hunting" trip.
where he secretly trained
us in bloodbending.
We kept the truth
from our mother.
Stop! You're hurting it!
Toughen up!,
Tarrlok.
You'll need a thicker
skin for this.
Very good, son.
Very good.
A few years later,
my father taught us to
bloodbend anytime,
without the need
of the full moon.
We practiced constantly
and I hated every minute of it.
I had no stomach for
manipulating helpless animals.
My brother however,
seemed to revel in his
new found power.
He was a prodigy,
mastering my father's psychic
bloodbending technique by
the time he was 14.
That's the way it's done.
That's what you need
to strive for.
Even though Noatak was my
father's favorite it wasn't
any easier for him.
He carried the burden of all Yakone's
expectations and demands.
Something changed in
Noatak over the years.
The loving brother I once
knew became cold
and detached.
Our father pushed us
to extremes
and one day he made us
bloodbend each other.
Noatak,
Go.
Excellent.
Tarrlok!
Your turn.
No,
I won't do it.
Bloodbend your
brother Tarrlok!
That felt awful!
I don't want to
do that to anyone!
I never want to
bloodbend again!
You're a disgrace,
a weakling.
I'll teach you a lesson
you insubordinate,
Stay away from him.
How dare you bloodbend me?
What are you going
to do about it?
You're the weak one.
You always say bloodbending
is the most powerful thing
in the world,
but it isn't,
The Avatar is.
He took your bending away.
What could be more
powerful than that?
I made you,
What you are!
You're mine!
We're your sons,
Not your tools of revenge!
Let's go.
We can run away
from him, forever.
Run away?
But, What about mom?
We can't just leave her.
He was right about you.
You are a weakling.
Noatak!
Don't leave, please!
My father and I searched
for days,
but we never found
a sign of Noatak.
We thought he perished
in that storm.
My mother was never the same,
after the loss of my brother.
My father stopped training me.
With Noatak gone his hopes
for revenge withered
and he passed away a few years later.
That's one of the saddest
stories I've ever heard.
Avatar Korra,
I am truly sorry for all
that, I did to you.
I thought, I was better
than my father,
but his ghost still
shaped me.
I became a soldier of revenge
just like he wanted me to be
and so did my brother.
The revolution,
may be built on a lie,
but I think Amon truly believes
bending is the source of
all evil in the world.
How did you figure out
Amon is your brother?
When he took my bending,
the sensation
was somehow familiar.
I later recognized it as
my brother's bloodbending grip.
So, He somehow uses bloodbending
to take people's bending?
I don't know how
he does it,
but then again, I've never encountered
a bender as strong as Noatak.
How in the world
do we beat him?
We can't.
Any attack we throw at him
he'll redirect with his mind.
That's how he's been able
to challenge any bender.
So much for our ambush.
If we stay here,
we're toast.
But there's another way
to beat him.
How?
This whole time,
Amon has been
one step ahead of us.
But finally we have
the advantage,
we know the truth about him.
If we expose him as a bender
in front of all his supporters,
At the rally.
We could take away
his true power.
And undermine
this whole revolution!
Thank you, for your help.
We can't just leave him here.
Go.
Amon can't know anyone
spoke with me.
Defeat him.
Put an end
to this sad story.
www.tvsubtitles.net