Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master
all four Elements
and bring balance to the world.
The Legend of Korra
Benders, be on alert!
After coming face to face with Amon,
leader of the Equalists,
Avatar Korra discovers
a terrifying truth:
This masked madman
has the ability
to take away a person's bending.
Permanently!
Benders of Republic City
are counting on their young Avatar.
But is she prepared
to face such a frightening foe?
Season 1, Episode 4
"The Voice in the Night"
Sync by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
Text from the internet
After I take your bending away,
you will be nothing...
It's...
It's alright, Naga.
I just had a bad dream.
There is a madman
running around our beloved city,
threatening to tear it apart.
We need to create taskforce
whose sole mission
is to find Amon
and bring him to justice.
Absolutely not!
A move so aggressive will only
further divide benders and non-benders.
Tarrlok, I'm inclined to agree
with your proposal,
but who would even head up
such a taskforce...
It would be my honor,
and privilege
to accept such a duty.
This is just another one of your ploys
to gain more power, isn't it?
All I'm trying to do is help!
Think back...
Forty two years ago,
Republic City was threatened
by another dangerous man.
Yukon.
Your father wasn't afraid
to deal with him head on.
This is a completely different situation,
with the Bending Triads.
Eventually, he will come
for all us, benders.
Our friends, our families...
Vote for this taskforce,
and I will stop Amon...
Before it's too late.
All in favor?
Good evening, my fellow Equalists.
This is your leader, Amon.
As you have heard,
the Republic Council has voted
to make me
public enemy number one...
Proving once again
that the bending oppressors
of this city
will stop at nothing
to quash our revolution...
But we cannot be stopped.
Our numbers grow stronger
by the day.
You no longer have to live in fear...
The time has come
for benders
to experience fear.
Oh no, I'm so sorry!
I didn't see you!
How could you not see me?
I mean I was ju-uh...
I was... I, I...
Wow! Hm-hm.
I was... Hm-hmm.
Are you okay?
Did I hurt you?
Oh, I'm such an idiot!
Don't worry, I'm fine!
My brother hits me harder than that,
every day in practice.
Wait, I recognize you.
You're Mako, right?
You play for the Fire Ferrets!
Yeah, that's me.
I am so embarrassed...
My name's Asami.
Let me make this up to you somehow.
Uh...
How about I treat you to dinner?
Tomorrow night, eight o'clock,
Quong's Cuisine?
Erm... "Quong's"?
I don't have any clothes nice enough
for a place that classy.
I'll take care of that.
All you need is show up.
So... it's a date?
Ahh... Yeah, I guess so!
I'll see you tomorrow night!
We are grateful
for this delicious food,
for our happiness,
for our compassion and…
I'm not interrupting...
Am I?
This is my home, Tarrlok!
We're about to eat dinner.
Good, because I'm absolutely famished.
Airbenders never turn away
a hungry guest, am I right?
I suppose...
You must be
the famous Avatar Korra.
It is truly an honor.
I am councilman Tarrlok,
representative
from the Northern Water tribe.
Nice to meet you.
Why do you have three ponytails?
And how come you smell like a lady?
You're weird.
Well, aren't you…
Precocious.
So, I've been reading all about
your adventures in the papers.
Infiltrating Amon's rally...
Now that took
some real initiative.
Aw, thanks.
I think you are first authority figure
in this city who's happy I'm here.
Republic City is much better off now,
that you've arrived.
Enough with the flattery, Tarrlok.
What do you want from Korra?
Patience, Tenzin.
I'm getting to that.
As you may have heard,
I am assembling a taskforce
that will strike
at the heart of the revolution
and I want you to join me.
- Really?
- What?
I need someone who will help me
attack Amon directly.
Someone who is fearless
in the face of danger.
And that someone is you.
Join your taskforce?
I can't…
I must admit,
I'm rather surprised.
I thought you'd jump at the chance
to help me lead the charge against Amon.
Me too...
I came to Republic City.
to finish my Avatar
training with Tenzin.
Right now,
I just need to focus on that.
Which is why
this opportunity is perfect!
You will get 'on the job' experience,
while performing your
Avatar duty for the City.
Korra gave you her answer,
it's time for you to go.
Very well, but...
I'm not giving up on you
just yet!
You'll be hearing from me soon.
It has been a pleasure,
Avatar Korra.
Bye-bye, ponytail man!
Aah, welcome to Quong's Cuisine,
master Mako.
Uh… "master"?
The scarf stays.
As you wish, Sir.
This way, please.
I am such a big pro-bending fan.
I caught all of your matches
this season.
All of them? Wow!
Honestly, there are few
I wish you hadn't seen.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
You're amazing.
I can't wait to see you
play in the tournament.
Yeah, well.
Uh... maybe next year.
What do you mean?
You made it in.
It just isn't in the cards for us,
right now.
Tell me, what's the problem?
We don't have the cash to ante up
for the Championship pot.
So, it looks like
we're out of the running.
That's not fair!
Pardon me, Miss Sato,
your main course.
"Miss Sato"?
You wouldn't happen to be related
to Hitoshi Sato,
creator of the Satomobile?
- Yeah, he's my dad.
- Get out of town!
I'm serious.
You wanna meet him?
Meet the most successful captain of industry
in all of Republic City?
Yeah, I'll take you up on that!
Hello, fellow teammate!
Hey, Bolin.
Missed you at practice, this week.
Yeah, sorry about that.
That's alright,
we're probably out of tournament, anyway.
Unless some money miraculously
drops out of the sky by tomorrow.
Anyway, reason I came by
was to give you this.
Ta-da!
Wow, thanks.
What's this for?
Uh… Oh, I can't remember now.
Aw, yeah. Now I remember!
You saved me from Amon...
Oh, that? It was no big deal.
"No big deal?"
Are you serious?
I was totally freaking out when he was
coming at me with this creepy mask, all...
"I will take away your bending
forever!"
I mean, that is scary stuff,
I still can't sleep well!
- M-hmm.
- Delivery, for Avatar Korra.
Tarrlok sends his complements
and urges you to reconsider his offer.
Tell him I haven't changed my mind.
M-hmm...
Who's this Tarrlok guy?
Is he bothering you? Huh?
Because I can have a word with him.
Ha! No...
It's not like that.
He's just some old guy
who works with Tenzin on the Council.
Oh, good.
Good, that sounds better.
I like that better.
What do you think
of my little operation here?
It's... very impressive, Mister Sato.
Please, call me Hiroshi.
So, I understand you're dirt poor.
Wh... uh...
Young man, it is nothing
to be ashamed of.
I too came from humble beginnings.
Why, when I was your age,
I was a mere shoe shiner,
and all I had to my name
was an idea.
The Satomobile.
I was fortunate enough
to meet someone
who believed in me
and my work ethic.
He gave me the money I needed
to get my idea off the ground.
And I built the entire
Future Industries empire
from that one selfless loan.
Dad, stop bragging.
Just tell Mako the good news.
Ha-ha-ha...
What "good news"?
Well, my daughter
passionately told me
all about your harder and
success in pro-bending arena.
And about your team's current...
Financial stumbling block.
Now, I'd hate to see
you lose your chance.
at winning the Championship,
just because you're short
a few yuans.
That's why I'm going to sponsor
the Fire Ferrets in the tournament!
Are you serious?
He's serious, my dad's going to cover
your ante for the championship pie.
That… That is good news!
There's just one catch.
You all have to wear Future Industries logo
on your uniforms.
I'll tattoo it on my chest
if you want, Sir!
A-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Thank you both so much!
I promise the Fire Ferrets will
make most of this opportunity.
Outta way daddy,
we're driving here!
I see Tarrlok's gifts are getting
more and more extravagant.
Yeah, that guy doesn't know
how to take 'no' for an answer.
Korra, are you...
Doing alright?
Yeah, I'm fine...
Why don't you take a break?
I'm glad you turned down Tarrlok,
but I just wanted to make sure
your decision was for the right reason.
I'm just really focused
on my Air bending right now, that's all.
Right, that's...
What you said.
You know, it's okay to be scared.
The whole city is frightened
by what's been going on.
The important thing
is to talk about our fears,
because, if we don't,
they can throw us out of balance.
I'm always here for you,
if you want to talk.
Avatar Korra,
I have something for you.
It doesn't matter how many gifts
Tarrlok sends,
I'm not joining his taskforce!
It's not a gift, it's an invitation.
To what?
Tarrlok is throwing a gala
in your honor.
All of Republic City movers and shakers
will be there.
The councilman humbly requests
your attendance.
Can't believe this is all for me.
I'm not sure what Tarrlok's plotting,
but keep your guard up.
It's not like him to throw a party
just for the fun of it.
So glad you could make it,
Avatar Korra.
If you'll excuse us...
The City awaits its hero.
Milo, no! That is not a toilet!
Oh, dear…
Korra, it is my pleasure
to introduce Republic City's
most famous industrialist,
Hiroshi Sato.
Nice to meet you.
We're all expecting
great things from you.
Right...
Greatness.
Hey, Korra!
This is my daughter,
Asami.
It's lovely to meet you.
Mako told me so much
about you.
Really?
Because he hasn't mentioned you at all.
- How did you two meet?
- Asami crashed into him on a moped.
What? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
More than fine!
Mr. Sato agreed to sponsor our team.
We're back in the tournament!
Isn't that great?
Yeah. Terrific.
Chief Beifong, I believe
you and Avatar Korra have already met?
Just because this city's throwing you
this big to do.
don't think you're something special.
You've done absolutely nothing
to deserve this.
If you'd be so kind,
they just have a couple of questions.
But I…
Avatar Korra, you witnessed
Amon take away people's bending
firsthand.
How serious a threat does he pose
to the innocent citizens of Republic City?
I think he presents a real problem.
Then why have you refused
to join Tarrlok's taskforce?
As the Avatar,
shouldn't you be going after Amon?
Well, I…
Why are you backing away
from this fight?
What? No, I've never backed away
from anything in my life.
You promised to serve this city.
Aren't you going back on that promise now?
Do you think pro-bending is more important
than fighting the revolution?
How do you think
Avatar Aang would have handled this?
Are you afraid of Amon?
I'm not afraid of anybody.
If the City needs me, then...
I'll join Tarrlok's taskforce
and help fight Amon.
There's your headline, folks.
My fellow taskforce deputies,
tonight we will execute a raid on
an underground chi-blocker training camp,
located in the Dragon Flats borough,
According to my sources,
there is a cellar
underneath this book store,
where Equalists
train chi-blocking in secret.
I'm going after those two.
Nice timing, thanks Tarrlok.
We make a good team, Avatar.
Yeah, we do.
No Korra for practice, again?
Doesn't look like it.
Avatar Korra has bravely answered
the call to action.
With the two of us
leading the charge,
Republic City has nothing to fear
from Amon and the Equalists.
Question for the Avatar.
Amon remains at large.
Why have you failed to locate him?
You wanna know why?
Because Amon is hiding in the shadows,
like a coward.
Amon, I challenge you to a duel!
No taskforce, no chi-blockers...
Just the two of us,
tonight at midnight,
on Avatar Aang
memorial island.
Let's cut to the chase
and settle this thing.
If you're man enough to face me.
I know it sounds weird
to say this,
but I'm really glad
I hit you with my moped.
Ooh… me too!
I forgot to ask...
Why didn't you accept the new silk scarf
I bought for you last week?
- You didn't like it?
- No, it was really nice, but…
This scarf was my father's...
And it's all I have left of him.
I just feel like...
Like it keeps me safe.
I'm so sorry.
I lost my mother
when I was very young.
I feel so safe with you.
Korra, this is madness.
Don't try to stop me
and don't follow me.
I have to face Amon alone.
This is all your doing!
I tried to talk her out of it too,
but she's made up her mind.
We'll be watching the island closely.
If anything goes wrong,
I have a fleet of police airships
ready to swoop down.
Guess you're a no show, Amon.
Who's scared now?
I received your invitation,
young Avatar.
Our showdown, while inevitable,
is premature.
Although it would be
the simplest thing for me
to take away your bending
right now...
I won't.
You'd only become a martyr.
Benders of every nation
would rally behind your...
untimely demise,
but I assure you,
I have a plan...
And I'm saving you for last.
Then, you'll get your duel...
And I will destroy you.
- Aang?
- Korra!
Korra, are you alright?
What happened? Was Amon here?
Yeah...
He... ambushed me.
Did he…
Did he take your bending away?
No...
- I'm okay.
- Oh, thank goodness!
I was so terrified!
I felt so helpless.
It's alright.
The nightmare is over.
You...
You were right.
I've been scared this whole time.
I've never felt like this before,
and...
And I don't know what to do!
Admitting your fears
is the first...
And most difficult step
in overcoming them.
Sync by mko_ro
www.addic7ed.com
Text from the internet
www.tvsubtitles.net