Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can master
all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -
the Red Lotus is
the world's newest threat.
After confronting Zaheer,
Korra learned he is part
of a secret society
whose mission is to take out all the
nation's leaders and destroy world order.
But before Korra
could warn anyone,
she and Asami were apprehended
by the Earth queen's forces.
And the Red Lotus
nabbed Mako and Bolin.
Now both parties are headed
toward Ba Sing Se.
-
you have to let me out.
The Earth queen is in danger
from a group of terrorists
calling themselves
the Red Lotus.
I talked to one of them
in the spirit world yesterday.
He's insane.
Screaming about terrorists
in the spirit world?
You're the one
who sounds insane.
Do I have to be chained
to the floor the whole way?
It's going to be
so uncomfortable.
Sorry, ma'am.
I'm under orders.
Can't you just chain me
to that railing?
I mean, where am I gonna go?
Please.
Well, as long as you're chained up, I
guess it doesn't make a difference.
Thank you, Sir.
- Can I have some water?
- No water.
We're also not gonna bring you
any rocks or fire, so don't ask.
I guess there's air, but there's
nothing we can do about that.
We're not opening your compartment
until we reach Ba Sing Se.
I hoped Mako and Bolin would
have shown up to save us by now.
I wonder if they're okay.
If you think
holding us hostage
will give you some leverage
to use against the Avatar,
you're gonna be
very disappointed.
Can't we just enjoy our time
together in silence?
And why did you need
Korra alive back in Zaofu?
You had her paralyzed.
Why didn't you just take her out
when you had the chance?
Look, all you need to know is that the
world is about to change, for the better.
So you guys were, like,
locked up for 15 years, huh?
That must have been, like,
crazy boring.
Actually, it was only 13
years, but it felt like 30.
I mean, what did you do
with all that time?
Did you sing songs,
work on crafts?
Not a lot of craft supplies
in a volcanic prison cell.
And I must have renamed the
constellations about a thousand times.
When it rained,
that was a big event.
Oh, I would've killed
for some rain.
Mostly I just made up stories
about the guards.
Who was having trouble
with his girlfriend?
Which one secretly wished
he'd become a pastry chef?
Ooh, okay, that sounds like fun.
Let me try that on you guys.
You were raised
by an older sister.
Your mustache grew in
when you were ten.
And I'm sensing... just sensing...
An unspoken attraction
between you two.
Two out of three. Not bad.
Bolin, will you stop making
friends with the bad guys?
Sorry.
Ghazan, gag those two.
We're almost there.
We have to find a way out of this prison
before we get to the Earth queen.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
These airships that Cabbage Corp
sold to the Earth kingdom
are way cheaper than the ones
Future Industries built.
Now, that's just
shoddy workmanship.
There's no way I can get
these locks off.
I need the keys.
Give me five minutes,
then start yelling for help.
When is the Avatar
scheduled for delivery?
The airship already left fort Bosco and
should be arriving in a few hours.
Excellent.
Bring her to me
as soon as it lands.
Yes, your majesty.
But first there are some people here who
captured two of the Avatar's friends.
They would like to present them
to you personally.
You know I don't meet
with bounty hunters.
And of course
I told them that,
but they say they have some
information that might interest you
about the location
of your stolen airbenders.
Really?
Fine, send them in.
Ah, yes.
I remember these two.
We'll find an acceptable home for you in
prison with the rest of the dissidents.
Now I'm told you have
some information for me.
I hope this isn't just some ruse
to try to increase your bounty.
We don't want any bounty,
your majesty.
You can consider these two
a thankyou gift
for simply taking the time
to talk to us.
How very magnanimous.
So where are my airbenders?
I'd be happy to tell you once
you hand the Avatar over to me.
Who told you
that we have the Avatar?
How I know is not important.
But if I found out,
others will too.
And that could put you
in a difficult position.
Is that so?
Your Majesty,
imprisoning the Avatar
will cause the other nations to turn
against you and demand her freedom.
Before long, you'll be in the midst
of a sticky international incident.
But if you let me
take her today,
no one need ever know
she was here,
and you can get your airbenders
back without interference.
We both win.
And what do you plan to do with the Avatar,
should I see fit to grant your request?
All I can say is that
I have business with her.
But she won't
be bothering you again.
I can assure you of that.
I find these terms agreeable.
Gun, escort them to the Antechamber
until the Avatar's arrival.
Send these two to the dungeon.
Guard! Get in here!
Something happened to my friend!
She needs help!
Where is she?
Nice work.
Now let's take control
of this ship.
Mayday, mayday.
The Avatar has escaped.
We're going down in quadrant
four of the Si Wong desert.
I think you might have been a little
overaggressive with the airbending.
The controls are busted.
Also, you broke the radio.
Sorry, but it's not my fault
this airship's a hunk of junk.
Hang on to something!
Well, they say any landing you can
walk away from is a good landing.
But given our location,
I'm not so sure about that.
You're the engineer.
What do you think?
Can we get it flying again?
It doesn't look good.
I mean, even if you metalbend
the propellers back into shape,
we'd have to dig this
whole thing out of the sand.
Is everyone all right?
Like you care.
What the heck happened?
She said
her friend needed help.
Then they knocked me out!
I'm sorry, but I couldn't let you take
me to the Earth queen as a captive.
There are dangerous forces at work
that you don't know anything about.
More dangerous than being
stranded in the desert?
Don't worry, Kong.
I radioed Ba Sing Se
before we went down.
We just need to sit tight.
Someone will be here soon
to rescue us.
I'm not waiting around
for that.
We need to get out of here now.
If we all work together, we might be
able to get the ship up and running.
Not likely.
I just tunneled out of the engine room.
It's like a sandbox in there.
This ship
isn't going anywhere,
and neither are you.
You're our prisoners, and it's our duty
to transport you to the Earth queen.
You realize
that I'm the Avatar, right?
You don't wanna fight me.
I'm afraid you aren't
giving us much of a choice.
We have our orders.
Wait, did that sand dune
just move?
It was probably just a mirage.
The desert will play
tricks on you.
That's no mirage.
Look.
I heard that since all the spirits came
back, this desert has been haunted by them.
Oh, right, so I guess
that's my fault too.
Do you want to help us
get this ship up and running,
or do you wanna wait around
and meet that thing?
We wanna fix the ship,
right, Cap?
Mm, let's get to work.
Everybody, stand back!
We have to find
a way out of here
before Zaheer gets
his hands on Korra.
Take me with you.
I haven't seen my wife
and five kids in four years.
Four years?
The first few months
were great.
I could finally get some sleep.
But now I really miss them.
Listen, Bolin,
this is up to you.
I know you can metalbend.
You can metalbend?
No.
Yes, you can.
I believe in you.
I believe in you too, Bolin!
I appreciate that,
Mako and fellow prisoner man,
but I've been trying
and trying and trying,
and I've never been able
to do it... not even a little.
You've always had
the ability deep down.
You just haven't had
the right motivation.
But this is your time.
Get us out of here
to save Korra.
You can do it!
Bolin! Bolin!
Bolin! Bolin! Bolin! Bolin!
You're right. Okay.
Here I go.
Metalbending!
Aghh!
I can't metalbend.
Aww.
Hey, you guys didn't happen to
bring any toilet paper, did you?
First you scare the life out of
me, now you want to lick me.
Here. Chew on this,
and leave me alone.
- Tonraq, you read me?
- Yes. We copy.
I found Korra's jeep,
but the kids aren't here.
Meet me
at the Misty Palms Oasis.
How's it looking in there?
I just airbent all the sand
out of the engine room.
I think it's clean.
It hasn't been that clean since it
floated off the showroom floor.
How's it going out here?
Well, she's still
pretty banged up,
but I think she might be able
to limp out of the desert.
Kong, you want to see if you can
get the engine started?
Aye, aye.
All right!
Aah!
That's no spirit.
I think it's gone for now.
Kong, are you all right?
What are we gonna do?
All of our supplies were on the ship.
We've got no food, no water.
Easy, Arik.
Another ship is on the way.
We just need to hold
our position for a few hours.
We might not have a few hours.
How far are we
from the edge of the desert?
Too far to walk,
if that's what you're thinking.
We can't just wait around for that
thing to pick us off one by one!
You'll do as you're told,
airman.
Now get ahold of yourself!
Maybe we can still build something
to get us all out of here.
You wanna make some wings out of
scrap metal and flap real hard?
No, but we might have enough material
to construct a makeshift sandsailer,
like the sandbenders
use to get around.
All we need is a sail and some
kind of sled to attach it to.
It's worth a try.
Gather every piece
of metal you can find.
We'll give that sandy beast
a run for his money yet.
Looks like he's in a hurry.
Wait here.
Your Majesty, we received a distress signal
from the airship carrying the prisoners.
We believe the ship crashed
in the Si Wong desert
and the Avatar may have escaped.
This is outrageous!
Send another airship to retrieve
the Avatar immediately.
It's already on its way,
your majesty.
What are we going to do now?
There's no way we can track her down in
the desert before the queen gets to her.
You really think they'll be lucky
enough to capture her again?
She'll be long gone
by the time they arrive.
It doesn't matter.
We're through chasing her.
It's time to make her
come to us.
What is this riffraff doing
in my throne room unannounced?
Apologies, Your Majesty,
but I couldn't help overhearing that
the Avatar won't be joining us today.
The Avatar is still
in my custody.
However, eavesdropping on royal
conversations will land you in a cell
right next to those boys
you brought in.
Now, if you value your freedom,
you'll tell me where
the airbenders are right now.
That wasn't the deal.
I will not bandy words
with bounty hunters.
Seize these hoodlums
and throw them in prison
until they decide to show
proper respect for the crown!
Oof!
Gun!
Get back here and lay down your
life for your queen, you coward!
You wouldn't dare
attack a queen!
Maybe I forgot to mention
something to you.
I don't believe in queens.
You think freedom is something
that you can give
or take on a whim,
but to your people,
freedom is just
as essential as air.
And without it,
there is no life.
There is only...
Darkness.
Hey, you can't be in here.
No need for alarm.
I just need to make an
announcement to the entire city.
How do I do that?
Who do you think you are?
He's the man who just
took down the Earth queen.
You wanna be next?
Minghua, please.
We're here to help citizens
like him, not hurt them.
Now, can you help me?
Attention,
citizens of Ba Sing Se.
I have an important announcement
to make.
Moments ago, the Earth queen
was brought down
at the hands of revolutionaries,
including myself.
I'm not going
to tell you my name,
'cause my identity's
not important.
I'm not here to take over
the Earth kingdom.
I think you've had enough of
leaders telling you what to do.
It's time for you
to find your own path.
No longer will you
be oppressed by tyrants.
From now on, you are free.
I deliver Ba Sing Se
back into the hands
of the people.
We have to get out of here,
Bolin.
Zaheer came here to take out the
Earth queen, and now Korra is next.
You know that guy?
He's my hero!
Shut up!
You have to metalbend us
out of here.
Come on, I know you can do it!
This is your time!
You said before was my time.
I know I did,
but now it's really your time.
Do it!
Did you see that? I did it!
I mean, not for us, but I metalbent
all the other cells open!
I don't think that was you.
Listen to me.
I'm going to set you free,
but I want to talk to you first.
I have a message that
I need you to take to Korra.
She ain't pretty,
but I think she'll do the job.
No time for a test run.
Let's move!
I think he's gone. We did it!
You want to buy
a slightly used sandsailer?
Thanks, Asami. You've got
a good head on your shoulders.
I'm sorry for getting us
stranded out there.
I didn't mean
for that to happen.
You know, whatever the conflict
between you and the queen is,
I'm sure it's above my pay grade.
You got a tough job.
Good luck, Avatar.
Captain, have we been
in the desert too long,
or is that really
a dragon over there?
Ugh. Let's go get a drink.
Ah!
Easy, girl.
Did you think we weren't
coming back for you?
What are you all doing here?
Korra, you're safe.
Yeah, we made it out of the
desert, thanks to Asami.
Do you remember Lord Zuko?
I met you when you were
a very young girl.
It's good to see you again,
Avatar Korra.
It's good to see you,
Lord Zuko.
Thanks for ditching me
back at Zaofu.
Yeah, sorry about that.
But how did you all find us?
I am a detective, you know.
Did you find Mako and Bolin?
Some people at the inn saw them
get captured by Zaheer's crew.
We don't know where they are.
Did you hear
about the Earth queen?
What about her?
Once again,
the Earth queen's reign
has come to an abrupt
and violent end.
Ba Sing Se has descended
into chaos.
Rioters and looters
have overrun the palace.
- The Red Lotus.
- What's that?
The name of the group
that's been trying to capture me
and just took out
the Earth queen.
I'm afraid this is only
the beginning, dad.
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net