Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
The Red Lotus has captured the Avatar.
Korra gave herself up in exchange
for the airbenders.
But Zaheer double-crossed her
while Ghazan trapped Team Avatar
in the temple.
All seemed lost until Bolin saved
their lives by lavabending.
But he's not the only one
with new skills.
Zaheer unlocked the ancient
airbending ability of flight.
Will Team Avatar save the air nation
and Korra before it's too late?
__
When I get out of here,
none of you will survive!
You won't get out.
Unless the metal clan taught
you a way to bend platinum.
Once we administer this poison,
your body will naturally react,
forcing you into the Avatar state
in an effort to keep you alive.
Sadly for you,
you'll be entering it for the last time.
No.
The Avatar cycle...
Yes.
When we dispatch you in the Avatar state,
the cycle will end.
So we lucky few,
this band of brothers
and sisters in anarchy,
are witnessing the beginning
of an era of true freedom.
Together we will forge a
world without kings and queens,
without border or nations,
where a man's only allegiance is to himself
and those he loves.
We will return
to the true balance of natural order.
And though you will never again be reborn,
your name will echo throughout history.
Korra, the last Avatar.
Did you find any way to escape?
No, not yet.
But don't worry. We'll find a way out soon.
They might not make it that long.
Korra will come to save us, right?
I think we're going to
have to do this on our own.
Administer the poison.
Ah. Ahh!
Get ready.
As soon as she's in the Avatar state,
take her out.
Wait.
Why isn't she staying in the Avatar state?
Give it time.
She can't resist for long.
The place where I saw
them taking the airbenders
is around here.
That's gotta be where they took Korra.
That's it!
Down there, Lefty.
Find the airbenders
and my family.
Don't worry.
I'm not coming out without our children
and the rest of your people.
It's working.
I told you, Korra.
The world doesn't need you anymore.
The time of the Avatar is over, Korra.
Give up.
You're too weak to resist
and I'm stronger than ever.
There's no use fighting.
Let go.
I'm thirsty.
I gotta go pee.
Me too.
Hey. Keep it down over there
or you're all going to end up like them.
Sir, please. Could we just have some water?
There are children and a baby here.
Ah!
Oh, so you just called
me over to attack me.
Fine. Now nobody gets any water.
Ah.
I don't know how we
ended up here in day care
while everyone else gets to watch
the Avatar being destroyed.
I can hold a bowl of poison.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Ah!
Mom!
Oh, honey, I'm so glad you're safe.
Oh! Me too.
You're alive. I can't believe it.
Why?
Just because I was blown out of the sky
and fell hundreds of feet down a cliff?
Don't you know it takes more
than that to get rid of me?
We have to get these two out of here now.
They don't look so good.
What are you talking about?
I feel great.
You guys get everyone out of here.
I'll search for Korra.
We're going with you.
You don't have to search for her.
I know exactly where she's being held.
Now!
Destroy the Avatar.
Ugh.
Ah!
Korra.
We have to help her!
Look out!
You help Korra. We got this.
Daddy!
Oh, thank goodness you're all right.
Honey, are you okay?
I'll be fine.
We have to help Korra.
Ah!
What are you smiling about?
I was just remembering
the last time we fought.
Well, a lot has changed since then.
So that's how you got out of the temple.
Not bad.
Let's see what you've got.
You can't fight me and the poison.
I can fly up on my bison to help her.
You'd never be able to keep up with Zaheer.
He's too powerful.
We have to do something.
How can he fly like that?
He's unlocked powers of airbending
that haven't existed
for thousands of years.
There haven't been this many airbenders
in one place for a long time, either.
We have power together.
Hurry! Everyone form a circle.
Follow me.
Ah!
You have no water.
It's over.
Not yet.
Now it's over!
Ah!
Give up, Ghazan!
You can't win!
I'm never going back to prison.
If I'm going down today,
you're coming with me.
Mako, hang on.
Ah!
The poison has done its work.
The Avatar cycle will be over momentarily.
Ah!
Ah.
Korra, sweetheart,
it's me, dad.
Please hang on.
What are you laughing about?
You're too late!
The poison's been in her system too long.
The Red Lotus has won.
You can save her.
The poison is metallic.
Dad?
You're alive.
I'm here for you.
I'm never going to let you go.
No!
You don't understand.
The revolution has already begun.
Chaos is the natural order of
You see what I did there?
I put a sock in it.
Literally.
Classic Bolin.
I do what I do.
There you go.
All fixed up for a
formal Avatar appearance.
Take a look.
It's great.
Thanks.
You know, nobody expects you
to bounce back right away.
It's only been two weeks.
You need time to heal.
I want you to know that I'm here for you.
If you ever want to talk, or anything.
But let's just try to enjoy this today.
For Jinora.
You're right.
Okay.
Let's go.
You look beautiful, sweetie.
You're looking stronger every day, Korra.
I'd like to officially welcome
you back to Republic City.
I know that the last time we saw each other
it didn't end on the best terms,
but I want to thank you for taking down
those Red Lotus terrorists.
We should go inside.
I can help. I wanna ride with Korra.
Jinora's already inside.
It smells like shoe trees.
Sandalwood, Meelo.
I got this.
Hang in there, kid.
She's not looking good.
Neither would you if you'd
gone through what she had.
She'll be fine.
She just needs time to heal.
The poison took a great toll.
Of course.
I'm just saying, with the earth kingdom
in complete disarray
since the loss of the queen
and even with Zaheer locked up again,
we still don't know how
many Red Lotus members
might be out there, hiding.
Exactly.
With the world getting
more and more dangerous,
we need the Avatar now more than ever.
Who will protect us while
she's in a wheelchair?
Jinora, come forward.
Today we welcome the
first airbending master
in a generation,
and I couldn't be more
proud of my daughter.
When the existence of
our people was threatened,
when the Avatar's life hung in the balance,
Jinora never gave up hope.
Thanks to her leadership,
I see a very bright future
for the air nation.
Of course, there would be no
air nation without Avatar Korra.
She opened the portals
and somehow the world began anew for us.
And she was even willing
to lay down her own life
in order to protect ours.
There's no way we can ever
repay her for all she's done.
But we can follow her example
of service and sacrifice.
So while she recuperates,
the air nation will
reclaim its nomadic roots
and roam the earth.
But unlike our ancestors,
we will serve people of all nations,
working wherever there
is corruption and discord,
to restore balance and peace.
Avatar Korra,
I vow that we will do
everything in our power
to follow in your footsteps
and bring harmony to the world.
Now, let us anoint the master
who will help lead us in our new path.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net