Earth...
Fire...
Air...
Water...
Only the Avatar can master
all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -
Zaheer infiltrated Zaofu
and attempted to kidnap
the Avatar.
After a harrowing battle,
Korra was saved,
but she soon discovered
a shocking truth.
Aiwei, Su's trusted advisor,
has been working with Zaheer.
This truth seer turned traitor
managed to escape,
but Su tasks team Avatar
with tracking him down.
Now the hunted
to becomes the hunter
as Korra searches for answers.
Aiwei's definitely been
through here.
Nice tracking, girl.
Let's ask around.
Maybe someone's seen him.
Ooh, look,
they have a mover poster of me.
Must be big Nuktuk fans.
Yeah. I should go
over and say hello.
No, those are wanted posters,
and there's one for each of us.
"Wanted by her majesty,
the Earth queen,
for crimes against the kingdom."
I'm guessing this is because
we took her airbenders.
They weren't hers to keep.
I swear, if I ever see her pinchy
little queen face again, I am gonna...
Uh, guys.
We should get out of here.
Where is everyone?
I've been waiting to leave
for half an hour.
And good morning
to you too, lin.
Now, don't get mad.
Korra's fine.
I'm just waiting to hear
if she tracked down Aiwei yet.
What? You let Korra go?
I thought we were
on the same page about this,
and then you go stab me
in the back?
Oh, don't be so overdramatic.
You can't control
the Avatar's every move.
I can try.
Naga found something.
Oh, sorry. I forgot to bring treats.
But good girl.
This must be Aiwei's jeep.
He can't be far.
Bolin and I will investigate
the Misty Palms Oasis
and see if he's holed up there.
Yes, I love it
when you talk like a cop.
- I'm coming too.
- No.
You and Asami wait here
in case he comes back.
Besides, we don't want to call
too much attention to ourselves.
All right.
Ooh. Mako, Mako, Mako,
we should wear disguises
and pretend
we're going undercover.
That way, no one
will recognize us.
Police work is so exciting.
All right, now we need
our undercover identities.
I'm an exunited forces
operative named "Tingting".
War was the only woman
I ever loved,
until Ivy came along
and showed me what real love is.
Tragically,
she was taken from me
by my archenemy Dr. Razor,
and he...
Enough. Let's just find Aiwei.
But I haven't even told you
your backstory.
I'm a cop. I don't have a backstory.
Ooh, you're good at this.
Shoo. Human customers only.
Let's see if this guy
knows anything.
Excuse me, Sir.
We're looking for a man
about 60, balding,
wearing glasses
and a long green robe.
And he's got this weird piercing
that goes from his nose to his ear.
- Freaks me out.
- Yeah, sure.
Sounds like a guy
who came in last night.
I told him I had the best drinks in the
Earth kingdom, and he called me a liar.
That's him.
Any idea where he is now?
No, afraid not.
But he was right.
My drinks are terrible.
Are you okay?
I'm just frustrated.
What does Zaheer want with me?
What's his plan?
I don't know,
but I think I found a clue.
"Xai Bau's grove, sundown."
This must be where and when
Aiwei's going to meet Zaheer.
All right, Xai Bau's grove,
where are you?
Go away. I'm trying to find something.
Well, aren't you a cute little...
Ow! Hey!
No luck here.
I think there might be a couple bounty
hunters over there who recognize me.
We've been made. Let's lose 'em.
Okay, I think we're clear.
We should head back to Korra
before someone else recognizes us.
We could, or we could
follow Aiwei instead.
Look.
All right, play it cool.
Follow my lead.
Tingting always finds his man.
Keep an eye on him.
I'll go get Korra.
We found Aiwei hiding in an inn.
- That's great.
- We found something too.
It looks like he's going
to meet Zaheer at sundown
at place called Xai Bau's grove,
but I can't find it anywhere
on the map.
Let's go bust Aiwei's door down
and finally get some answers.
No, once Aiwei knows we're on
to him, we lose our advantage.
I say we stake out his room,
and when he leaves
for this meeting,
we follow him.
And he'll lead us
straight to Zaheer.
Good afternoon.
We'd like a room
on the ground floor
across from 102, please.
Forget it.
Last time a bunch of teenagers came
in here, they trashed the whole room.
We found you.
Hey, no bending in here.
Take it outside.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're not here to fight you.
We're here to meet Nuktuk.
We're your biggest fans.
Could you make it out
to Lily and Macao?
Uh, I'd be happy to.
Always love meeting my fans.
I made this Nuktuk doll for you.
Aw, it's...
Cute.
Why didn't you tell me
your friend was a mover star?
I'd be happy to rent you
any room in the inn.
We'll just take the one
across from 102.
But that room is too small
for the four of you.
Trust me. It'll be perfect.
I'd just like to state
for the record
that this room is not perfect.
Naga!
There he is.
I thought stakeouts
were supposed to be exciting.
This isn't at all.
Ooh, I wonder
if there's any snacks in here.
Hey, look!
A Pai Sho board.
Mako, you want to play?
Kind of busy here, bro.
- I'll play.
- Oh, well...
No offense, but I learned
street Pai Sho from Shady Shin,
and I am pretty good,
so wouldn't really be
a fair game.
So? I learned to play from my
dad, the diabolical genius.
I'll destroy you.
Well, looks like we have
ourselves a Pai shodown.
Ladies first.
Hmm.
I don't want to rush you,
but let's speed things up a bit.
Why?
This game is all about slow,
methodical strategy.
No, it's not;
This is a fastpaced,
edge of your seat game of chance.
Don't think. Just go.
I don't know
what Shady Shin taught you,
but it wasn't the real Pai Sho.
Oh, really?
I think our friend Mr. Rule book
might disagree with you.
"The origins of Pai Sho
date back over 10,000 years.
It is a game of both strategy
and chance."
- Wait, how could it be both?
- Let me see that.
"There have been countless variations
of Pai Sho through the centuries,
and each culture has its own rules
and variations on the game."
That's no help at all.
Korra, as the Avatar,
you need to standardize
these Pai Sho rules.
Okay.
I'll put that on my "to do" list right
after "bringing back the air nation"
and "taking down the group
that tried to kidnap me."
That's cool.
Whenever you get to it.
Assuming we do find Zaheer,
what then?
Then I make him talk.
He was locked away
for 13 years, Korra,
and never broke.
I don't think a little bending
is going to intimidate this guy.
- You have a better idea?
- Yeah, we spy on them.
If Aiwei and Zaheer don't know
they're being watched,
they'll talk freely.
Then we'll know who they are
and what they want.
That's just like Pai Sho.
"In order to defeat
your opponent,
you first have to know
your opponent."
Then I guess
I know you pretty well.
- I win.
- What?
All right, all right. You know what?
That was just a fluke.
Best two out of three.
Oh, come on!
Best four out of seven.
8 out of 15.
17 out of 33?
Looks like
you're on the ropes this time.
I can't believe it.
You might actually win this one.
No, Pabu!
Why?
It's almost sundown.
Why hasn't Aiwei left yet?
Maybe he slipped out
when you weren't looking.
No, I just saw him peeking out
the window 15 minutes ago.
It's in my logbook.
- I'm going over there.
- Korra, wait.
You're gonna blow
our element of surprise.
It's over, Aiwei. Where's..
What?
- That's a weird way to nap.
- He's not sleeping.
He's meditating. Wait.
Asami, those spirits were trying
to tell us something earlier.
Xai Bau's grove isn't on the map
because it's not
in the physical world.
It's in the spirit world.
I'm going in after him.
We'll watch him
in case he wakes up.
Be careful.
What happened back in Zaofu?
You told me
we wouldn't have any problems
getting the Avatar.
Because of you,
we've all been compromised.
No, any evidence was destroyed
when my library burned.
Where is your physical body now?
At the Misty Palms inn.
But there is no need to worry.
I was not followed.
You left a loose end.
I assure you
no one knows anything about us.
No, you are the loose end.
Zaheer!
It seems Aiwei was mistaken.
- He was followed.
- That's right.
We knew he'd lead us
straight to you.
So what did you do with him?
He'll be spending eternity
in the fog of lost souls,
which just leaves the two of us.
Don't move, Zaheer.
You're gonna give me
some answers.
There's no need for aggression.
Neither of us has our bending,
and I'm not going anywhere.
I'll answer whatever questions you have.
You deserve that much.
What would you like to know?
First off, who are you people, and
why do you keep trying to take me?
We are part of a secret society dedicated
to restoring freedom to the world.
- We are the Red Lotus.
- Red Lotus?
Are you related
to the White Lotus?
We are what the White Lotus
was meant to be,
but after the hundred year war,
the White Lotus
lost its true purpose.
Its members came out of hiding
and openly served the Avatar.
They became nothing but glorified
bodyguards who served corrupt nations,
so a great man named Xai Bau
broke from the White Lotus
and began his own society.
That's a great story, but it doesn't
explain why you tried to take me
when I was a kid.
That was Unalaq's idea.
What?
My Uncle was part
of the Red Lotus?
Avatar Korra.
Misty Palms inn.
- Find her.
- You two go.
I'll stay here and make sure
Zaheer's body is safe.
I met your Uncle
when I was a teenager
after we had both joined
the Red Lotus.
We learned about Raava and Vaatu
and how Avatar Wan
foolishly severed them,
disrupting the balance
of the world forever.
Avatar Wan wasn't foolish.
He was trying
to restore balance.
He closed the portals,
severing humans from spirits.
Even you realize
the error in his ways.
So all along, you and my Uncle
planned to use me
to open the portals
and release Vaatu?
That's why you tried to take me
when I was a kid?
Yes, and with members of the red
lotus as your elemental masters,
we could've taught you so much.
Sounds like you wanted to brainwash
me so I'd do whatever you wanted.
No, Korra.
All I wanted was to show the Avatar
a better path for the world.
Uh, I don't know how, but water
arm lady and lava guy found us.
- How?
- I just said I don't know how.
Korra, come on, wake up.
- What do we do?
- Get Korra out of here.
Bolin and I will hold them off.
The Avatar.
If my Uncle came up with a plan
to abduct me when was a kid,
why wasn't he caught?
He wasn't with us that night,
and he covered up
his involvement afterwards.
So he betrayed you
just like he betrayed me.
Yes, he allowed me and my
friends to remain imprisoned
while he pursued
his own selfish goals.
Unalaq becoming a dark Avatar
was never part of our mission.
And what is your mission
exactly?
I want what you want,
to restore balance
to this world.
I don't think our ideas
of balance are the same.
Are you sure about that?
You kept
the spirit portals open,
but why stop there?
Bringing the spirits back
should only be the beginning.
What do you mean?
The idea of having nations
and governments
is as foolish as keeping the human
and spirit realms separate.
You've had to deal
with a moronic president
and a tyrannical queen.
Don't you think the world
would be better off
if leaders like them
were eliminated?
No.
I mean, I don't really agree
with what they've done,
but taking out world leaders
isn't the answer.
It wasn't too long ago that the
airbenders were nearly all wiped out
thanks to the Fire Lord's desire
for world dominance.
True freedom
can only be achieved
when oppressive governments
are torn down.
But that won't bring balance.
It will throw the world
into chaos.
Exactly.
The natural order is disorder.
Do you know who once said,
"new growth cannot exist without
first the destruction of the old"?
No.
The wise guru Laghima,
an airbender.
I can't beat this guy. It's
like I'm giving him ammo.
Want to trade?
Go get the Avatar.
I have these two under control.
You know, being locked away
for so many years,
I was beginning to lose hope,
but when I awoke
with airbending,
I knew I would be the one
to destroy the old world
and plant seeds
for a new world to flourish.
Zaheer, please, as an airbender,
you could help make a positive
difference in the world
instead of destroying it.
You're a very smart
young woman, Korra,
but you must realize
that once change begins,
it cannot be stopped,
even by the Avatar.
Enough with your philosophical
mumbo jumbo.
I want to know one thing:
If you do capture me,
what are you gonna do with me?
You'll have that answer
soon enough.
The Red Lotus
should have you by now.
See you in the physical world.
Zaheer!
Zaheer, you tricked me.
Let me go!
Asami, are you okay?
Where's the rest
of the Red Lotus?
What's the Red Lotus?
And Zaheer didn't capture us.
The Earth queen's forces did.
- Where are we?
- I'm not sure.
Some camp by the desert.
They're taking us back
to Ba Sing Se.
The Earth queen's army snatched
up the Avatar before I could.
But we figured you could find
a use for these two.
Load them in the truck.
We're taking a trip
to Ba Sing Se.
Sync and corrections by masaca
- www.addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net