(gentle music)
- Well, I'm gonna see
the temple first, man.
(dramatic music)
- Let's get 'em!
- Oh, yeah!
(laughing)
(dramatic music)
- Hi, Neema.
- Good morning, eh?
- Hey, me and me.
- Oh, hello, eh?
(dramatic music)
- Oh, perfect timing.
- Hi, giving me a list.
- Yup, so this isn't the best time.
- Okay, and gold, you know?
- My body doesn't move like a used to.
- I'm kind of in the middle of something.
You are so heavy.
- Heavy, me?
- I eat nothing but vegetables.
- Hi, it's not a vegetable.
I'm gonna lose the race.
- Race?
What race?
(dramatic music)
- Hang, as an airbender, it's important
that you know when to show restraint.
- Even if you have the power
to win, you are the avatar.
- A lot of people are going to rely on you.
(dramatic music)
- He's gone.
- He ran away.
- What's up here?
- What's up, come on.
- Hey, where are you?
- Joseph, I'm here.
(dramatic music)
- Come here.
- Hey, mama.
- Hi, upper.
Was I asleep alone?
- Oh, okay, okay.
- Yeah, I'm awake already.
- No, I know.
We've got a job to finish.
- Ah, let's continue our journey.
Back to our old home.
(dramatic music)
- This may not have been our best trip,
but any airbender relic we
find makes it all worthwhile.
(dramatic music)
- This could be the oldest
piece in our collection.
(dramatic music)
- So numb.
- I miss you.
(dramatic music)
- Momma, go outside with Oppa.
- Now!
(dramatic music)
- Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
(dramatic music)
- Stop, I don't want to hurt you.
(dramatic music) Where is it?
Where is it?
- Nope, that's not it,
hey, those are antiques.
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music) And no!
- Wait, I found it!
(dramatic music)
- So numb, why in after you?
- Wait!
- No, that's 1,000 years old!
(dramatic music)
- Yes!
Give it to me!
- Why don't we just talk?
- Maybe I can help.
- We don't need your health to have a car.
We're done living in a world where vendors
have all the power and we have none.
- Who are you?
- Where are the denied?
- It's a night.
- Just kill them already!
- No, don't bring the whole place down!
(dramatic music)
- You saved me.
- Hey, leave, grab them out, let's go!
(dramatic music)
- Oh no!
- I'm fine, well more, I'm fine.
- Oh, you've got to get to Republic City.
- Alpha, you beat it!
(dramatic music)
- Water.
- Her tribes gather strength from
the mirror and flow with the tides.
- Earth.
- A kingdom of unshakeable
will, reliable and strong.
- Fire.
- The ancient capable of great
destruction, but also of great warmth.
- Air, peaceful nomads
with the power of a
hurricane, but the
spirit of a gentle breeze.
For generations, the Avatar, the one master
of all four elements, have
the nations in balance.
But when that
responsibility felt to me as a
child, I ran away, I was
caught in a deadly storm,
but my Avatar spirit
preserved me in a sphere
of energy where I stayed
for a hundred years.
I woke to discover that
the balance preserved
by the Avatar had
been destroyed by war.
The air nomads were gone, all but one, me.
I could no longer run from
my responsibility as the Avatar.
I found allies from every
nation, benders and non-benders.
Katara taught me how to water bend, tough,
train me in the ways of the earth benders.
Zuko, once my worst enemy
became my firebending teacher,
Saka showed me that bravery is the
most important part of being a leader.
We became a family, and together
we ended the hundred year war.
Then we began the hard
work of rebuilding the world.
(gentle music)
For so long, the nations did a part
alone, and we all suffered as a result.
But here on this ancient
site, we created a place for
all people are welcome,
bender and non-bender alike.
Work them together in
peace to build the future.
Though there are still those who
would seek to divide us, we remain united.
As a council representative, I
am honored to be here today,
celebrating the anniversary
of Republic City and
the opening of Unity Tower,
a symbol for all people.
(screaming)
- It's the Avatar!
(grunting)
(thunder rumbling)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
(giggling)
- Alpha!
- I missed you, too, old friend.
- Hey!
- Katara!
(gasping)
- Your heart.
(somber music)
- Take a deep breath.
And exhale.
I've heard the denied
are growing in numbers,
but they've never
done anything like this,
attacking the Avatar.
- Yeah, they were incredible
fighters, even without bending.
- Oops, ah, right through it.
- Hmm, be honest, you're enjoying this.
- Hey, this is serious.
Whatever this map they
took was, if they were willing to
kill the Avatar to get it, what
else are they willing to do?
- I don't know.
- I'm worried about you.
You're spending more and
more time at the air temple, alone.
- It's how I hold on to my past.
- I know how heartless is for you.
- When I was attacked, all I could
think about was that this could be it.
I'm the last airbender.
If I die, my culture dies with me.
- You may be the last
airbender, but you're not alone.
- Aye, none of this
would exist without you.
You made the city possible
with your heart and your mind.
Because of you, all of the
nations live here, together.
- I'll accept mine.
- I know, but the people
here still need your protection.
- You're an airbender,
but you're also the Avatar.
- You're right.
Whoever this sewn in person is,
I need to find out more.
(dramatic music)
- Aye, Avatar Roku.
- It is good to see you again.
How can I help you?
- In your lifetime, did you ever hear
of an ancient airbender named Sono?
- I have not, but you have
many past lives to call upon.
Perhaps one further back in the Avatar,
but it's likely to help you,
thank you, Avatar Roku.
(dramatic music)
- I'm sorry, I've never
heard of some of the money.
- Perhaps early I'm not
here, not here, I'm not here.
- I'm not here, I'm not here, I'm not here.
(dramatic music)
- Um, hello?
Is there anyone here?
Hello?
Who goes upon Avatar Sion's
best wealth of Norman's knowledge?
- Oh, hello?
You look like an avatar from
a time quite distant from mine.
Please, please, tell
me about your interact.
What are people wearing?
Are sandals still a thing?
- Uh, yes?
- Oh, why?
Why after so many years, open toes seem
that someone else's
crusty cuticles is disgusting.
- Right, anyway, I have come to
the guidance to see I was attacked.
- It was not me, okay?
Wasn't me.
- I know that.
I think it might have something to
do with an airbender named Sionum.
- Mm, Sionum.
- It sounds familiar.
- Sionum, where have
I put that name before?
- Ah, Sionum was the
youngest daughter of the owner
of the possum chicken shop
at the corner marketplace.
- Wait, that was my ex, Sionum.
It only, yes, you didn't have
those among us toenails.
- Yeah, I'm disgusting.
- This is going nowhere.
- So name?
- Well, thank you for your time.
- I must continue my search.
- Oh, Sionum, you were asking
about the legend of the last avatar.
- Sionum was an avatar, indeed, she was.
She was the avatar in the
golden age of eubendous.
Legend said she had a
staff that could channel
in the vast energy of the spirit world,
granting its keeper unlimited power.
Is that even possible?
- Ah, well, never know for sure.
Many avatars have tried to
communicate with her, but they couldn't.
She disappeared so completely,
that it was as if she never existed.
And perhaps it's better that way.
Maybe such a staff was too dangerous
for anyone to possess even the avatar.
- But that's exactly why I need to find it.
The people who attacked
me discovered a map.
It must lead to the staff.
Avatar Sion, please, you
have to tell me where it is.
- The legend says that Sionum disappeared
with her staff on the peak of Mount Bayhu.
- Katara, I'm sorry to leave so suddenly,
but I found out with a denyter after.
Sionum at a staff of immense power.
And in their hands, it could
be a devastating weapon.
They have a head start.
There's no time to waste.
You take off my momo and
gather up the rest of the teeth.
We're gonna need some help.
- Next on the agenda, a fire
nation naval vessel came into conflict
with an extremist group of
non-benders called the denied.
They've been robbing ancient sites.
- The Majesty.
- An urgent message has
arrived from Republic City.
- How impudent?
- Can you see Fire Lord Zuko Ambulin?
- There's only one person
who can send a message
urgent enough to interrupt
the Fire Lord's Council.
Is it from the Avatar?
- Yes, my Lord.
- Read it to me.
- Um, what are you doing?
- Read it quickly.
- Yes, yes, Grand Chamberlain.
- Flame your heart man.
How's ruling the Fire Nation?
- I hope the boring
Chamberlain you mentioned
in your letters isn't
still annoying you.
- Anywho, to cut to the
chase, I need your help.
Can you please come immediately?
Oh, and don't forget to
bring some firecracker buns.
- Allow me to present.
Sock a cycle.
Flames launch you into the sky where
you can drop water bombs on your enemies.
Then skis pop out to
help you stick the landing.
Pretty great, right?
- Mm, boring.
- Why would you need a sled
when you can just water bend?
- Uh-oh, like me, like me.
- Keep in mind, there are still
plenty of folks like me who can't bend.
- Why would Avatar aim
partner with a non-bender?
- Please.
- Why?
I'll tell you why.
I saved him from the iceberg.
My boomerang flew by his side while I
carried away enemies with my trusty blade.
I even took down the whole
Fire Nation airship Armada.
- Then on top of all that, I
was more popular than him.
- You're such a liar, Socka.
- It's from the Avatar.
- Wow.
- Really?
- Oh, so now you think I'm cool?
(laughing)
- All right, metal benders.
Let's see if any of you tender foots
can at least make me use my hands.
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(dramatic music)
- I'm still the greatest
Earthbender in the world!
- And I'm bored.
- Master Toph, there's a bird on your head.
- And?
- It looks like it has a message.
- Wait.
- Uh, it's from Avatar Ang.
He needs your help.
It's the denied?
- Where is he?
- Mount Bihu.
(dramatic music)
(grunting)
- No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, I love that ad.
(dramatic music)
- Sonam?
- Could that be you?
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
[MUSIC] Who are you?
Huh?
[MUSIC]
[BLANK_AUDIO]
Team Avatar to the rescue.
[MUSIC] >> You made it.
>> You couldn't wait a day before
running off to get yourself killed.
>> I thought you were
here looking for a staff.
>> Who's this guy?
[MUSIC]
>> How did he hold up an entire mountain?
>> How did this guy be a record
for longest frozen airbender?
>> Yeah.
>> How long do you
think he was in that ice?
I don't know.
His tattoos look ancient.
He's been in there a long time.
>> He smells good for an old guy.
>> What?
>> My sense is tell me
this guy is pretty attractive.
>> Someone else confirmed.
>> What is attractive even me?
>> Just give me a straight confirmation.
>> Is he attractive?
>> He's very attractive.
>> What? He is. It's on the bone structure.
[MUSIC]
>> Whoa, whoa, whoa.
>> Hey.
>> You said.
[MUSIC]
>> Earthbender, you don't know.
>> We're all friends here.
>> It's okay.
>> Someone woke up on
the wrong side of the mountain.
>> Where is she?
Where is Avatar Sonum?
>> You knew Sonum?
>> Who are you?
>> I don't know how to explain it.
But you've been asleep for a long time.
>> I'm the Avatar now.
I'm Ang.
>> If you're the Avatar, then Sonum.
>> Well, Sonum might
be long gone, but on the
bright side, you woke
up at the perfect time.
>> Everyone will be amazed
to see another airbender.
>> He's not the last one anymore.
>> What do you mean, last?
>> Oh.
>> The air nomads, they've been wiped out.
There's only me.
>> Oh.
>> Sonum staff, do you have it?
It's our only hope now.
>> What do you mean?
>> I thought it was a weapon.
>> The staff is no weapon.
It is a gift.
>> With it, Sonum was able to
channel the vast power of the spirit world.
It was this power that
allowed Jirana to flourish.
The greatest city in the
world, an air nomad utopia,
where Sonum presided
over a golden age of balance,
and where I devoted
my life to serving her.
In return, she raised me
up, and used her staff to
give me a lowly non-bender,
the power to bend the air.
I was the first, but I
would not be the last.
She filled the skies with airbenders,
and we flew by her side,
spreading peace across the world.
>> And are you okay?
>> Sonum used the staff
to give people airbending.
If we found it,
I could bring airbending back to the world.
>> This is kind of more than
an airbender scroll for 100 years.
>> This is everything you ever wanted, Ang.
>> We could heal the greatest
atrocity my nation committed in the war.
This could be the final
step to rebuilding the world.
>> Not if the denied get there first.
They have the map.
>> Who are the denied?
>> A group of violent non-benders.
They must be after the staff
to give themselves airbending.
>> Then there's no time to waste.
There's only one place it could be.
Ready your bison.
We'll need to travel
across the endless ocean.
>> On the other side of the world.
But there's nothing out there.
>> There's an island.
The journey will not be
easy, but we can make it.
>> Then let's get going.
>> The skies are no place for a waterchild.
>> Waterchild?
I know you just woke up after thousands
of years, but we do these things together.
>> Trust me.
We're stronger this way.
>> Welcome to Team Avatar.
>> What's your name?
>> Taga.
>> My name is Taga.
>> Just think of it as
a big metal air bison.
>> We will travel ancient
paths through the sky.
>> Ones that are people
learned by following the great air
bison herds that long
ago taught us airbending.
>> Air currents known only to us,
and circling the great sphere of existence,
allowing us to travel where we wish,
giving us our name,
the air no-mads.
[MUSIC]
>> What's he doing?
>> He's really feeling that air.
>> He's navigating by instinct.
What if his instincts are just wrong?
>> Who needs instincts when
you've got muscles like that?
>> Or what if his brain is
messed up from being frozen?
>> Like me?
>> No!
>> He was frozen for 5,000 years.
You were frozen for 100?
That's nothing.
Your brain is fresh.
>> Maybe he is a little
old-fashioned, but look at him.
He's so in tune with his element,
he can travel across the entire
ocean with no map, no instruments.
[MUSIC]
There's so much I can learn from him.
I get anything to be able
to see my air bison again.
[MUSIC]
>> And now, to see only one remaining.
>> Mm-hm.
>> Hang.
You said our people were
wiped out, yet you survived.
>> How?
>> I just found out I was the avatar.
But the responsibility, it was too much.
So I ran away.
While I was gone, the Fire Nation attacked.
They were looking for me.
If I just been there.
>> Sonum would say, air
nomads are formed from the best.
We walked the world for a moment in time.
Then we returned to the eternal wind.
>> Monkyatsu taught me that.
>> We carry the same weight.
A grief no one else
could possibly cover him.
But you and I can heal the past.
>> Let me show you how
powerful our element can be.
When air benders work together.
[MUSIC]
>> This is not Sonum taught me.
The only energy that tethers us.
[MUSIC]
>> Come on between us.
Can you feel it?
Use it.
>> This is amazing.
[MUSIC]
>> Whoa, whoa, yeah.
>> Human boomerang.
>> He's actually fine.
>> So are we.
>> That's my best friend.
>> No, you told me.
[MUSIC]
[SOUND]
>> I had no idea this was possible.
>> This is only the beginning.
[MUSIC]
>> I can't believe it.
Air benders will fill the sky again.
>> We have been given a great gift.
The chance to redeem ourselves.
You were destined to find
me on that mountain thing.
[MUSIC]
>> How did you end up there?
The earth benders had attacked Toronto.
Sonam and I fought fiercely side by side.
We drove them back to Mount Bayou.
And that's the last I remember.
[MUSIC]
>> She must have saved your life.
Only an avatar could
have put you in that sphere.
[MUSIC]
>> Hang, can I ask you something?
>> Of course.
>> If the Fire Nation
destroyed the Air Nomads,
how can you suffer the
presence of the Fire Lord?
[MUSIC]
>> Zuko is a friend in an ally.
He turned against his own
father to help me end the war.
>> Yet he wears the crown himself now.
Fire by its nature burns, hang.
Our kind have always suffered at
the hands of the other elements.
That's why we built Republic City.
To show the world that
if we listen to each other,
we can all live together in peace.
And once we bring back
air benders, it'll be complete.
[MUSIC]
>> When everyone stuck to their own,
the whole world was nearly torn apart.
And besides, Katara, Sokka,
Zuko, Toph, they're my family now.
I want to live in a world
where we can all be together.
>> You remind me so much of Sono.
[MUSIC]
>> It's the Avatar.
And this time he's got
his friends with him.
>> That's the Fire Lord's Airship.
>> But they get out of us.
They don't even have the map.
>> We can't risk him
getting to the staff first.
Kill him, but he spared our lives.
>> And how many countless were killed
in the 100 years waiting for his return?
>> Where was he when
your family was wiped out?
>> If we want anything to change,
we need what the benders have.
>> Power.
[MUSIC] >> Fire!
[MUSIC]
>> It's the denied.
>> We are definitely under attack.
[MUSIC]
>> Everybody loses red.
>> Is he crushing the ship?
[MUSIC] >> Taga.
>> Taga, stop.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC] >> We're here.
>> The Immortal Storm.
>> I don't know.
[MUSIC]
>> There has to be another way around.
>> No, together you and I declare a
path for the ship, but we have to go now.
>> Hey, trust me.
[MUSIC]
>> Maybe now's a good time to turn back.
>> I don't think that's an option anymore.
>> Where are they going?
[MUSIC]
>> The engines out,
we're losing air pressure.
[MUSIC]
>> Tara, come with me.
>> What about me?
>> Take the wheel.
>> What?
>> I believe a crash fire nation air ship.
>> Okay, let's see.
Here's our rudder.
This is the elevator.
And there's the giant tornado
that's going to kill us all.
[MUSIC] >> Oh, I leave.
[MUSIC]
>> Work with me, just like I showed you.
>> We can harder.
[MUSIC]
>> Yes, that's a thing.
Keep going.
[MUSIC] >> Got it.
[MUSIC] >> Let's go.
>> Let's go.
>> You can talk you're destroying
tornadoes, but there's too many everywhere.
>> Just steer the ship.
>> Don't lose a.
>> It's not that easy.
>> Especially when everything is sideways.
>> Okay, left.
[MUSIC]
>> [LAUGH] >> I did it.
>> No, we're falling behind.
I'm losing sight of them.
We have to go back.
>> Trust in your friends.
They won't make it if
we don't clear a path.
[MUSIC] >> Let's go.
We're going to crash into the sea.
>> Would I give you the signal?
Pull the leverness to the wheel.
[MUSIC]
>> We're going to crash.
>> Contaro.
[MUSIC]
Give me the signal.
>> Whoa, sucker.
>> No, here we go.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC] >> We did it.
>> What were you thinking?
>> I was clearing the
tornadoes to make a path.
>> The ship almost crashed in.
We could have died.
And what if you got yourself killed?
You're the Avatar.
This is too risky.
We need to turn back now.
>> No.
We're almost there.
We just need to get
to the eye of the storm.
>> Hey, no.
This is too dangerous.
>> The staff is out there.
The Denighter after it.
>> Do you really believe that they
could make it through the storm?
We're nearly there.
That staff can bring back by people.
>> I understand how much you want that.
>> You don't understand.
None of you too.
[MUSIC] >> Hang.
>> We push forward.
[MUSIC]
>> If we generate enough air,
we can push our way through.
[MUSIC] >> We're alive?
We made it through.
Thank you, Taga.
>> There was you.
>> Hang.
>> We're here because of you.
>> Yeah, we're having a good time too.
Could have told us we were
flying into the immortal storm.
>> I know it was dangerous,
but we had to risk it.
>> We?
I don't remember when
we took a vote on that.
>> There wasn't time.
I had to make a cry.
>> No, please, don't blame Ang.
This is all my fault.
I knew this would be difficult.
But Ang believed in
your strength as a team.
And I'm honored to be a part of it.
[MUSIC]
>> I forgive you, Taga.
>> Everyone.
>> Look.
>> These islands.
They were lion turtles.
>> Whoa, it's beautiful.
>> Long before my time, the lion turtles
granted the gift of bending to humans.
These are their final resting girls.
This is where Sonum
came to learn their ways.
I am certain that she left her staff here.
>> Where should we start looking?
>> Ang, you must connect with her.
>> Bye.
No one can connect with Sonum.
>> The spiritual power of the
lion turtles is still concentrated here.
Let it guide you.
We'll set out immediately.
>> Actually, Taga, we could
really use your help here.
If the denied are close
behind, we need to be ready.
>> Yeah, man.
We're going to need more than
tops metal bending to fix them.
>> My bending got us through that storm.
What did you do?
>> Seared with his feet.
>> Repairs can wait.
>> Ang needs me.
>> Taga, please.
>> Stay and help my friends.
I'll be okay on my own.
>> As you wish, we will begin
repairs for our voyage home.
>> Everyone, I know I've asked
a lot of you on this journey.
But we're about to accomplish
something that will change the world.
[MUSIC]
>> Let it guide you.
[MUSIC] >> Sonna.
[MUSIC]
>> This is turning out
to be a nice little vacation.
>> Aside from all the people
trying to kill us and the tornadoes.
We're supposed to be fixing the ship.
>> Has anyone seen Taga?
>> Yes, we've all seen Taga.
He's so gorgeous.
>> Geez, I get it.
>> I see what you mean.
>> He wanted off that way.
>> No, maybe that way.
[MUSIC]
>> Taga, where are you going?
>> Hang needs to be protected.
>> I agree.
>> I know my ways may seem unusual.
But I assure you,
everything I do, I do for hang.
Or for the staff.
>> You have no idea all that we've lost.
You've never known a world of airbenders.
>> I know hang.
He may be the last of his kind.
But he's the reason this world knows peace.
[MUSIC]
>> His values as an air nomad
have brought balance to chaos.
It's because of aim that the
water tribes, earth kingdom and
Fire Nation now work
together, striving for harmony.
A piece we once thought unattainable.
>> You speak of peace.
There will never be
peace among the elements.
There never was.
Your precious Republic
city is built on lies.
>> It's built on hope.
Do you have hope, Taga?
Saving my people requires
more than just hope.
It requires sacrifice.
>> I saw you try to
crush the denied's airships.
You were ready to kill them.
[MUSIC]
>> I know what kind of airbender ang is.
But what kind of airbender are you?
[MUSIC]
>> There's great strength in him.
But weakness as well.
>> Weakness?
>> Yes.
You.
[MUSIC]
>> What the hot monkey?
[MUSIC] [MUSIC] >> No.
[MUSIC] >> No.
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC] >> Brother.
>> Taga.
>> It's real.
>> We can finally bring back airpending.
>> Let's go tell the others.
>> We can do this.
Me and you.
>> I can't do this without my friends.
>> Earth killed my people.
Fire killed yours.
The staff is the only way we
can create a new air empire.
One capable of defending itself.
>> No.
>> We can build a new future, Taga.
But it has to be for everyone.
>> The staff doesn't belong to everyone.
It belongs to us.
>> What?
>> What have you done?
>> The longest they were around you.
You always put them ahead of our people.
>> Don't you see?
This is how we redeem ourselves.
It doesn't matter that you ran them.
As long as you stand with me now.
>> Wow.
>> Hey, listen to me.
God, this is the only way.
[MUSIC]
>> That's greater to
your own, just like so.
[MUSIC]
>> [NOISE]
>> I wanted to do this with you by my side.
But if I must build a new
air empire alone, so be it.
[MUSIC]
>> There's no way to end
and we have to turn back.
No, we keep trying to push through.
[MUSIC] >> Yes.
[MUSIC]
>> Some in staff.
[MUSIC] >> And I.
>> Avatar is dead.
If you wish to build a new world where
you have the power, I can give it to you.
[MUSIC]
>> Katara, Katara!
>> Katara, they're gone.
It's all my fault.
It's always been my fault.
Ever since I ran away.
>> No, Avatar has ever fallen into such
shame as to join me here in my sorrow.
>> Why do you grieve so, friend?
>> Avatar, sonar.
[MUSIC]
>> Taga murdered my friends.
And now he has his staff.
>> Taga?
>> No.
>> No, I.
I stopped him.
I hit the staff.
>> What have you done?
>> You're the one who gave him airbending.
How could you give power to a monster?
>> The Taga I gave bending
to was a different man.
It was a different time.
The airbenders were the
peacekeepers of the four elements.
We used our power to mediate
all conflict with nonviolence.
But we were the few western numbers.
For many years, we existed in a
beautiful balance of great prosperity.
But the world began to shift.
The airbenders formed their own kingdom,
separating from the other elemental tribes.
The balance of the world was at risk.
It was my duty to act.
So I learned how to channel the energy of
the spirit while justice align total state.
To give people the power of airbending.
My most devout pupil,
Taga, was the first to receive it.
I sent my new peacekeepers out
to help calm the growing unrest.
But they were not prepared for the
brutality of the new earth kingdom.
Taga watched as his brothers
and sisters were all slaughtered.
His heart darkened by the violence of war.
He now saw everyone who
wasn't an air nomad as the enemy.
Taga begged me to use the staff to create
an army and kill all who would do his harm.
I refused.
So he stole it.
When he connected
the staff to the temple,
his energy was so
corrupted by grief and rage
that the power of the
spirit world consumed him.
Taga became something more
than human, too powerful to kill.
He took all my energy
to finally trap him high
above the clouds, and
no one would find him.
I reclaimed the staff,
but I was fatally wounded.
Before the earth kingdom
could invade Jirana, I
sent the remaining air
nomads into the mountains.
And I hid my temple in the spirit world
when no one could access its power.
And then I locked the staff away,
where only the avatar could find it.
I died, hoping that one day
another avatar would create
more air vendors and
restore balance to this world.
And that avatar is you, Ang.
You have to get my staff before
Taga connects it to the temple.
They're still time.
Don't let my regret become yours.
My friends and I fought
hard for this piece.
I won't let him start another war.
Help me find a way back.
Soto?
What's happening?
No!
Please!
I have to fix this!
This can't be hit!
I can't die it!
Please!
Not yet!
No!
Katar!
I can't see you!
Come on, Ang!
Come on!
Ang!
Katar!
I was so worried.
Ang!
Soka!
I knew you'd pull through, buddy.
Hey, hey.
Suka.
Ramo!
Welcome back, Twinkle Toes.
Tough.
You're okay.
I...
I thought you were all dead.
We were.
But Katar has saved us.
This spiritual power of these
waters strengthen my healing abilities.
You're incredible, Tara.
Where's Apa?
Taga must have taken him.
I'm sorry.
No.
I can't believe I trusted him.
We'll get through this.
So, let me get this shrink.
He's pulling Sonim's temple out of
the spirit world to gain unlimited power.
Hey, let me guess.
You want us to stop him?
Sure.
Only problem is your air throw
crushed our ship and stole your bison.
Also, there's a massive
typhoon surrounding us.
I don't say this very
often, but... Soka's right.
Thank you.
Yep.
We're stuck.
We're flying turtles for all of us to have
our own island, so I'm calling this one.
I'm naming him Snappy.
Aww, Snappy is the best one.
I know.
We may not know where
Taga is, but we know
what he's looking for
is in the spirit world.
And lucky for us, we're stuck in the most
spiritually charged place on the planet.
So I may be able to open
a portal to get us there.
If I could summon an old friend.
Wow.
The ocean spirit.
This portal smells an
awful lot like the fish market.
I'm going to go check on Snappy.
Face your death with honor.
I'm sorry.
I know I got us into this,
but I promise you I'll fix it.
We'll fix it.
Together.
We're going to die.
Ah, God.
What?
Where's my power pony?
Uh, where are my hands always this small?
It's maybe tough, maybe tough.
Grand grand?
That's where it's just dark.
You mean head?
Get me tough.
They're there, Tom.
No, so go.
What happened to your beautiful face?
You look like a dried sea squid.
No, so go.
Let's go on here.
The spirit world is out of balance.
And so are we.
That's going to talk.
[MUSIC PLAYING] Oh, no.
He's pouring stone up's
temple into our world.
We're ready at a time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, pretty good landing.
Whoa, humans.
I love humans.
Two brothers.
They're a little sister.
There's an ugly couple.
There's a couple.
A couple.
Whoa.
Looks like I touched a nerve.
Oh, look at this one.
Hello.
I don't know.
Bad talk.
Woo.
Don't bite strangers.
[MUSIC PLAYING] Great spirit.
Excuse me.
Did you just come from
that temple in the sky?
I certainly did.
He looked my favorite highly home.
Until that dark, yucky energy
started corrupting this whole face.
Please.
We need your help getting up there.
It's my duty to stop this.
I'm the avatar.
[MUSIC PLAYING] Ooh.
The avatar.
Let me have a squeeze at you.
OK.
Now with this side and this eye.
Mm-hmm.
Can we bring it out?
Can we get a squeeze?
Sniff-chang!
[MUSIC PLAYING] Ooh.
Let's have a time as you reel right there.
Yes, it is.
Ooh.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It appears the universe has brought
us together for a very important mission.
[MUSIC PLAYING] To flee!
[MUSIC PLAYING] Come back!
Come back!
[MUSIC PLAYING] Stop!
Please, great spirit.
Both of our worlds are in danger.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I am not going back up there.
[MUSIC PLAYING] Mm-hmm.
Well, when you put it like
that, it does make more sense.
One reflection, I've decided I show
help you and your human-y friends.
Why did he say-- [MUSIC
PLAYING] I swear, mama.
All right.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
By the way, no, we can
anything you find in my teeth
as I'm saving that for later.
Ready?
Set and set it and rest.
One and two, and you know what to do.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
I know we haven't known each
other very long, but I love you.
You don't have to say it back.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
You got your hair back.
Why are my eyes cheery?
Was I crying?
No way.
Look?
What?
What is it?
It's Republic City.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
We can't let him destroy
everything we built.
We won't.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
It'd be the staff, Taga.
I see I underestimated you, Avatar.
Your friends are stronger than
I thought, but you're too late.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING] It's a night.
You see, I did what you wanted, Ang.
I returned airbending to the world.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
What's the plan?
We'll deal with the denied.
You have to get the staff.
I will rebuild Toronto on the ruins of
our enemies, just as they did on ours.
A new air empire will rise, kill them all.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
We have to get these people out of here.
[MUSIC PLAYING] Oh yeah.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC PLAYING] Talk off.
Give it to me.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
This is the way! We can use the
staff to bring back the balance!
Peace! You care so much about your ideal!
Then you let your people die!
I won't do anything to
make sure they survive!
I'm having a habit! I'm a cabinet!
My cabinet is my cabinet!
Go through this! You have the power now!
You can decide how to use it! I'm not
like you! The world hasn't been good to me!
The world is what we make it!
Get away from her!
You betrayed me! You betrayed our culture!
I gave you every chance to see the truth!
Can you be in the fire nation?
I'm fighting for a piece of all nations!
Big talk from someone who sits
at a throne built at a security war!
I'm still the greatest
earthmen in the world!
Oh no! I'm out of water!
We got ya!
And there's no avatar here to save you!
Suck us, I go!
Let's see if your fancy new bending
can beat some good old non-bending yo!
You just got deny!
Let's go!
Good luck saving your city!
We have to save as many people as we can!
I know you're paid!
I know what you've been through!
You don't know! I watched as all of
my brothers and sisters were slaughtered!
From the fire nation burned the
air nomads to ash! Where were you?
You ran!
You're a good man! You're a good man!
It's a full power of the spirit world!
This is what strength looks like!
I'm not going to be a good man!
You should have run away like you
did all those years ago! Little Avatar!
I wrote, run!
Then at least you'll die knowing
you're not the last air business!
You're a good man!
We call a big runners!
We don't have none of this together!
It's there to have the air like this!
He's got the staff!
Yeah!
Kick his butt, Mega Egg!
No! Something's wrong!
The power is corrupting him!
I dread to bring me the ammo that's
back to the world as peacekeepers!
They could have been a beacon of light
for the world to follow! But you ruined it!
You twisted my dream into a nightmare!
Finally, you have the
power the air nomads need.
Maybe there is
hope for you after all!
No!
Do it!
Use the staff! Show me you have
the strength to pay off your back!
Do it!
You will do so many great
things as you have a tower!
But you must be prepared to
do what frightens you the most.
Your people, your home,
we are always with you!
No!
No! My power!
No! No!
You fool! Why? Why did you break it?
We could have fixed everything!
We can't erase the pain of the past.
We couldn't save them.
But it's our duty to protect our people!
The cost of betraying
everything they stood for! No!
It's time to let go!
You have to forgive yourself!
I have to forgive myself too!
Air nomads are formed from the mist.
We walk the world for a moment in time.
Then we return to the eternal wind.
Take it!
Hey, guitar.
Seriously?
You do realize you're falling, right?
Hey, if you ever retire
for lying at all, but
I can hook you up with
one of these babies!
I don't know if
airbending will ever return.
But I know now that the true power of
the air nomads was never their bending.
It was their values, and that's
a power I can pass on to others.
Avatar and you are the true
embodiment of the air nomads.
Thank you for giving up
the power that I could not.
You give me hope for
the future of our culture.
It's amazing, isn't it?
The first new air temple in centuries,
Republic City is finally complete.
A city for all nations,
just like you promised.
I never could have done
this without you, Katara.
Hey, everybody!
Sorry I kept you all waiting.
Are you ready for our big trip?
As my new acolytes,
you'll be helping me
preserve our culture
for future generations.
So, who wants to search for artifacts
at an ancient abandoned temple?
Yay!
I'm only going to make sure you don't
try to release another beefy old airbender.
Yeah, I'm done with bad boys.
Avatar showed him told me
about this place, so it's very
possible that no one's been
here in hundreds of years.
Oh! Is this an abandoned relic?
I think that's just a rock,
but I love the enthusiasm.
Oh!
Keep your eyes up.
They never know what
we might discover here.
Oh!
I thought they were at stake!
I can't believe it!
The original airbenders!
Look at all of them!
Look at that!
Up!
You did it!
Ah!