Earth...
Fire...
Air...
Water.
Only the Avatar
can master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Unalaq has forced Korra
into opening
the northern portal
and trapped Jinora
in the spirit world.
Back in Republic City,
everybody loves Varrick's
Nuktuk movers.
Everybody, that is,
except Mako,
whose pursuit of Varrick
has landed him in the slammer.
And in the Southern
water tribe,
Unalaq's army is nearing victory
in the civil war.
But Tonraq isn't about
to give up without a fight.
Dad's back!
Where's Jinora?
No!
Her spirit is trapped
in the spirit world,
but she's going
to be all right.
- How could this happen?
- It was all my fault.
I should have never let Jinora
enter the spirit world
without me.
I couldn't protect her.
I'm so sorry, Pema.
I tried to save her,
but Unalaq tricked me.
Don't worry, honey,
I'm not going to stop
until our little girl
is back safe with us.
You've got a visitor.
- Hey, Mako.
- Hey.
What's with the fancy duds?
I'm on my way to the big finale
Hero of the South.
Yeah, everyone's
gonna be there,
except for, you know, you...
Because you're in jail
and stuff.
Thanks for the reminder.
Hey, I brought you something.
I thought this would
brighten up your new place.
Read the inscription.
"Dear Mako, Nuktuk says,
'keep smiling.'"
did you come by
just to give me a poster?
No, I came by
to give you my sincere,
heartfelt words
of encouragement.
I know our lives
have been moving
in two different directions,
but I want you to know
that I will always
be there for you.
We are brothers, after all,
even if one of us is a member
of high society
and the other one
is a criminal.
I am not a criminal!
Of course I know that,
but you do kinda look like one,
'cause you're in a jail,
and that's where criminals live.
I was set up!
Varrick knew I had figured out
he was hiring gangsters
to pose as northern soldiers
to get Republic City
to join the war.
That's why he had me arrested.
Ah, I see what you're doing.
You're going for
the insanity defense.
Smart.
No!
I'm trying to tell you that
Varrick isn't what he seems.
Where's Asami?
She'll listen to me.
I asked her to come,
but she said
it was too hard for her.
You being in jail like this
reminds her of her dad.
Okay, gotta run,
but I'll be back tomorrow.
And I am gonna get you
the best attorney
fame and fortune can buy.
Bolin, wait.
If my theory about Varrick
is right,
something might go down tonight
at your premiere.
Promise me you'll
keep your eyes peeled.
Yeah, okay, big brother.
I promise.
Whew! That insanity defense
is definitely gonna work.
Should we wait another day?
Korra still might come
with reinforcements.
We can't wait any longer.
It's time we take back
what is ours!
It's time to take back
our city!
Say "Nuktuk."
There they are, folks,
the sweethearts
of the big screen,
and Republic City's
most famous couple,
Bolin and ginger.
Let me get a picture.
Wow, that was fun.
And did you hear
what Shiro said?
We're Republic City's
most famous couple.
Bolin, you're a doll,
but you're as dumb
as the rocks you bend.
We are not a couple.
That's not what Shiro said.
Stop stuffing your moustaches
with varri-cakes
and get to your post!
You got it, boss.
You two are the pinnacle
of refinement.
This star-studded event
just keeps getting
star-studdier, folks.
President Raiko
and the first lady,
buttercup Raiko, just arrived.
And they're being greeted
by entrepreneur extraordinaire,
Varrick.
There they are,
my two most honored guests.
Mwah!
What do you think?
No expense has been spared.
I brought in the finest
entertainers from ba sing se
and the best food
from around the world.
Heck, I even
had this red carpet
imported from the fire nation.
They make the best red stuff
over there.
In fact...
all right, picture time!
Varrick, you didn't
have to do all this for us.
I wanted to.
Mr. President,
I took one look at your wife,
and I knew that you
were a man of exquisite taste.
And that's why I know
you're gonna love this mover!
Varrick,
I know what you're doing,
and I doubt your propaganda
is going to change my mind
about going to war
with the northern water tribe.
Oh, I think you'll be surprised
how persuasive I can be.
Thank you all
for coming to the finale
Hero of the South.
You know, when I first
started this project,
there were a lot
of naysayers out there.
"You can't make pictures move,"
they said.
"You can't take
some knucklehead earthbender
and make him a star,"
they said.
"You can't teach a polar bear
dog to speak," they said.
Well, they're wrong.
Thanks to the magic
of the movers,
our furry friends
have found their voices.
And you'll be shocked to hear
what they have to say.
They speak of the injustice
that's happening
in the Southern water tribe
right now.
My hope is that their words
and this epic mover
will inspire
a real-life hero
to rise up and help.
Thank you again.
Enjoy the show.
When last we left our hero,
be was captured
by the evil Unalaq's
dastardly pet bird.
Amazingly, with the power
of his whistling,
Nuktuk escaped...
And decided
to seek out counsel.
Thank you, wise sage.
I will travel to Republic City
and seek help.
Have a seat.
I'm just working on a cure
for the common cold.
No longer will my citizens
suffer from the sniffles.
Mr. President, there's
something more important
than the sniffles right now.
I need your help
to stop the evil Unalaq.
Did you say "help"?
If there is one thing
I love doing,
it's helping people.
The seal line
seemed a bit far-fetched,
but the portrayal
of this president
is right on the money.
I think this
is your best mover yet.
I just wish Mako
was here to see it.
Mmm. I like to eat the top
off the varri-cake first.
I just try
to shove the whole thing
in my mouth at once.
I love our job.
Huh?
Northern water tribe
automatons!
Nooo!
Bee Bo bop,
Nuktuk cannot stop Unalaq.
Must destroy Nuktuk.
Ha ha!
Aah!
Looks like you forgot
that water and automatons
don't mix.
Beep bop boo.
Oh, no, circuits not working.
We did it!
But wait.
Where's Juji?
Nukno!
You can't die, Juji.
Not on my watch.
It's okay, Nuktuk.
At least I got to be...
Your friend.
Juji!
Are you okay?
It seems like this mover
is really getting to you.
You do know Juji's
not really dead?
Of course I know.
Juji's fine.
He comes back to life
in the end
when the doomsday device shifts
the polarity of the earth.
Oops. Spoiler.
Sorry.
Then what's wrong?
I guess I just miss my friends.
Everything is going
so well for me,
but it feels empty
without everyone around.
Korra's gone, Mako's in jail,
you're doing...
Business lady stuff.
Team Avatar's fallen apart.
I know.
Things have changed so much
since we first met.
Why don't you come back in
and fish watching
the mover with me?
You go ahead.
I need another minute.
That's weird.
Whoa... ahh!
Ugh!
They're after the president!
You're too late, Nuktuk.
Soon, my doomsday device
will shoot this block of ice
into the earth's core,
freezing the entire planet.
And I will be the ruler
of ice earth!
I don't think so.
I don't think so!
Huh! Ha!
Mr. President, get back!
I'm here to help.
Looks like there's
nowhere to go.
Uhh!
Secure the president
and call for backup
immediately!
Nuktuk, look out!
Bolin, look out!
Hyah!
This is unbelievable!
Bolin is bending
two full stacks
of earth discs at once,
which would normally be illegal.
But then again, he's fighting
three waterbenders,
so all rules
are out the window.
Tell me who sent you!
It was Varrick.
Please don't hurt me, Nuktuk!
I think this
is our cue to exit.
Where do you think
you're going?
It's a knockout!
They're falling back.
Varrick's plan
was to kidnap you
and blame it on the north.
Then Republic City
would have no choice
but to join the war
on the side of the South.
I can't believe Varrick
would do something like this,
and no one saw it coming.
Actually, someone did.
Remember Mako?
You've got a great officer
on your hands.
He's one of the best.
Mwah!
I can't believe my boyfriend
is a real-life hero.
Boyfriend?
Wait, stop.
I thought you said
we weren't a couple.
You really are as dumb
as those rocks.
Of course we're a couple.
Bolin, you saved the president.
And you proved Mako
was right all along.
We have to go tell him
what happened.
Yeah.
Oh, you meant right now.
- President Raiko...
- Avatar Korra, what's wrong?
Sir, I know I've asked
for your help before,
but things have changed.
Unalaq doesn't just want
to take over the South anymore.
He wants to destroy
the whole world.
Unalaq is gonna
destroy the world?
He really does have
a doomsday device?
He's trying to release
a powerful dark spirit
during harmonic convergence,
which is only a few days away.
If he succeeds, the world
as we know it is over.
Sir, we desperately
need your help.
I'm sorry, Korra,
but my answer is still no.
There are lives on the line!
And my daughter is one of them.
Raiko, you must reconsider.
I'm aware that lives
are on the line,
and that's precisely why
my troops are staying here.
If the world is going
to be thrown into chaos,
like you claim,
I need to protect my citizens.
I'm sorry.
Sir...
Nuktuk needs your help.
I know you love helping people.
Son, I appreciate you
saving my life,
and I'm a big fan of your work,
but my decision is final.
I never should have saved
that guy.
If you guys need help,
I'm here for you.
Yeah, me too.
Thank you.
It's so good
to see you guys again.
Wait, where's Mako?
So how was the big premiere?
I saved the president!
In real life!
Wait, what?
You were right about Varrick.
He tried to kidnap Raiko!
I knew it.
But it didn't work,
because of you.
And because of me.
Let's just say
we both did good.
Beifong says you're free to go.
Sorry for ever
doubting you, Mako.
Don't worry about it, bro.
Nice job, Mako.
You're going to make
a great Detective.
But, chief, there aren't any
Detective openings right now.
Actually, we have two openings.
Mwah.
Mako, I missed you so much.
Oh, yeah, did I forget
to tell you?
Korra's back.
Korra, hey, I missed you too.
So you're not still mad at me?
Why would I be mad?
We had that fight
before you left, remember?
No, not really.
I got attacked
by a dark spirit,
and I lost my memory
for a little while.
Maybe it hasn't
all come back yet.
Was it a bad fight?
Uh...
Mm... No.
No, it...
it wasn't that bad.
Korra, we don't have much time.
We need to figure out
how to deal with Unalaq.
I think I know
just the man to talk to.
Guys, hey!
What do you think?
Varrick industries
built this prison,
and I had this cell
made special.
I had a feeling
I'd end up here one day.
Zhu Li, come on!
We got guests.
Whip up a pot
of that green tea I love.
Yes, sir.
Zhu Li's in prison with you?
Of course.
I don't go anywhere
without my assistant.
Do you?
We're not interested
in your tea,
and this isn't
a friendly visit.
Don't tell me you guys
are still mad
about everything that happened.
I did some good things too.
Korra, who warned you
about Unalaq?
I did.
Bolin, who got you
into the movers?
I did.
Asami, who saved your company?
Mako, who got you
thrown in jail?
I did!
Oh, yeah, I guess
that was a bad thing.
You stole everything from me,
and you tried to kidnap
the president.
Those are pretty bad too.
I wasn't going to hurt him.
I just needed to start a war.
Well, a bigger war.
Well, we're gonna end it.
Where's all the stuff
you stole from Asami?
The future industries stuff?
It's on my battleship.
You have a battleship?
Of course I do!
I bought the first one
they made,
named her the Zhu Li.
You named your battleship
after your assistant?
Yep. They're both cold,
heartless war machines.
Your tea, sir.
Look, I am truly sorry
for the mess I caused.
Let me make it up to you.
Take Zhu Li.
My battleship, it's yours,
and everything on it.
It's not the fleet
we were looking for,
but it's the next best thing.
All right!
Team Avatar is back
in business!
It's okay.
We're gonna stop Unalaq
and get Jinora back.
I hope my dad's all right.
I'm sure he's fine.
Get the men and fall back.
What about you?
I'm going to end this
right now.
Go!
Hello, Tonraq.
Looking for me?
Brother,
I'm too strong for you.
You're no brother of mine.
You betrayed me.
You had me banished.
Yes, I did.
Stop!
He's mine.
You are not the true chief.
I am.
And you will bow to me.
Now that I've defeated you,
your daughter is next.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
What's up with the coat?
And where did you get that pie?
It's a Varrick ship.
You never know
what you're gonna find.
There's a whole level
filled with funhouse mirrors.
Of course,
there's also the cat-gator deck.
I miss that guy.
He really knew how to make
a long trip interesting.
So have you told Korra yet
about how you guys broke up
and then you
kind of started dating Asami
while she was off
getting attacked
by dark spirits?
You wanna keep it down?
I'm waiting
for the right moment.
Oh, Mako.
You know, a wise man once
told me that delivering bad news
to a girlfriend was like ripping
off a blood-sucking leech.
You just have to do it fast
and get it over with.
I hate it when you listen to me.
Fine.
Unalaq will be waiting for you.
You'll need all of
your Avatar power to stop him.
I'm going to close
the spirit portals,
lock Vaatu in
for another 10,000 years,
and make Unalaq wish
he'd never been born!
Thanks, Mako.
Uh... Um...
Did you want something?
Uh, no, no, nothing.
As soon as we reach
the Southern water tribe,
we'll blast through the blockade
at the main port.
Then we can rendezvous
with Tonraq and his troops,
crash through the defenses
around the portal,
and enter the spirit world.
Whoa, since when
does my little brother
want to crash or blast
through anything?
I'll do whatever it takes
to save my daughter.
We all want to save Jinora,
but I think your plan
might be a tad overaggressive,
seeing as there are
only seven of us and one ship.
Really?
And what do you suggest?
An attack like this
calls for strategy.
I remember when I was surrounded
by pirates
in the hurricane straits.
We managed to capture them all
with just a feather, two eggs,
and a barrel of molasses.
I don't want to hear
any of your crazy stories now.
This is serious.
- Are we almost there?
- Almost.
But I just picked up
a distress signal
from the Southern troops.
There's a problem.
Mom!
I'm so happy you're here.
Where's dad?
Unalaq wiped out
the entire Southern resistance
and captured your father.
I'll get him back.
Where is my mother?
She's in the healing hut.
So many injured.
What happened?
Her soul is trapped
in the spirit world.
Oh, my goodness.
How long has she been away?
Almost a week.
I've tried to keep
her energy flowing,
but I can feel her
slipping away.
You're the only one
who can help her now, mom.
How much longer
can she survive like this?
I don't know.
But she's very strong
to have lasted this long.
I talked to the rebels.
They said Unalaq's got
the Southern portal surrounded.
Harmonic convergence
is only a few hours away.
Then we have to break through
the enemy lines ourselves
and get to the portal now.
There's no use
in talking anymore.
We know what our mission is.
A suicide mission.
You know, I was
in a similar situation once.
My platoon had crawled
through the desert
with no water for a week,
but when we finally located
the only oasis for 100 Miles,
it was surrounded
by angry sandbenders.
I realized our only chance
to get to the water
was to drop in from above.
So I fashioned together
a catapult,
and with the help of
a few well-trained hog-monkeys...
enough of your ridiculous lies.
Can't you see
that the fate of the world
and Jinora's life depends
on what we do here today?
Hold on.
Maybe Bumi's right.
We don't have a catapult
and hog-monkeys,
but we have a flying bison,
and there's a plane
on Varrick's ship.
Maybe we can attack from above.
What are you thinking?
Mako, Bolin, and I
can use the plane
to create a distraction
and scatter
some of the defenses.
You, Tenzin, Bumi,
and Kya can fly
into the spirit portal on Oogi
when you see an opening.
T's get moving.
What are we still doing here,
father?
The invasion
was completely successful,
and the Southern tribe
is under our control.
The spirit portals are open.
You've restored balance.
Now we would like to go home.
You don't understand.
Everything I've achieved so far
will pale in comparison
with what
I'm about to accomplish.
What else is there?
The water tribe is united.
After today, there will be
no more water tribe,
no more nations of any kind.
The world
is about to be transformed
into something magnificent
and new,
and I will lead
this glorious revolution.
Now go outside
and get the troops ready
to defend the spirit portal.
From whom?
We've already beaten everyone.
The Avatar will be here soon.
She has no choice.
Are you ready?
I'm an earthbender
strapped to the wing of a plane
hundreds of feet in the air,
so no.
Don't worry. There's no way
they'll be expecting this.
I think they were expecting it.
Asami!
Get ready.
Fire!
There are spirits everywhere.
I don't see an opening.
Let's circle around
and see if we can find a way in
from the other side.
Hold on!
The spirits are weighing
Oogi down.
We're losing altitude.
Get off of him, you sticky,
nasty, little blob of goo!
Whoa!
If I go, you're coming with me.
Aah!
Bumi!
I wish Varrick
was filming this.
We could call it
Sky warrior.
Brace yourselves.
Dad.
Korra, I'm so sorry.
I failed you.
Don't give up.
Harmonic convergence
isn't here yet.
We still have a chance.
We tried.
Congratulations, everyone.
You've all got
front-row seats
for the beginning
of the new world order.
You don't know
what you're doing, Unalaq.
Freeing Vaatu
won't make you powerful.
It will only make you a traitor
to everything good
that's happened
for the last 10,000 years.
You think what Avatar wan
did was good?
Driving almost all the spirits
from this world?
The Avatar hasn't brought
balance, only chaos.
You call yourself the bridge
between the two worlds,
but there shouldn't be
a bridge.
We should live together as one.
Even if Vaatu escapes,
I'll put him right back
in his prison,
just like Wan did.
It's true that,
when Wan fused with Raava,
he tipped the scales
in her favor.
But this time, I'll be here
to level the playing field.
When harmonic convergence comes,
I will fuse with Vaatu.
And together, we will become
the new Avatar.
A dark Avatar.
Your era is over.
Think about what you're doing.
I know that you've always had
a deep connection
with the spirits,
but you're still a man.
You're still my brother.
You're Eska and Desna's father.
Are you willing
to throw your humanity away
to become a monster?
I'll be no more of a monster
than your own daughter.
The only difference is that,
while she can barely recognize
her own spiritual power,
I will be in complete alignment
with mine.
Vaatu and I will be as one.
No one will be able
to stand against us.
Keep them locked up.
After the harmonic convergence,
I will come for Korra.
Yes, father.
I failed in every way.
We've lost Jinora forever.
There's still a chance.
They didn't get Bumi.
Oh, you want to play some more.
Well, bring it on.
Oh, we're playing dirty, huh?
Hmm, looks like we've got
a music lover here.
Reinforcements!
All right, soldiers.
Looks like it's on us
to save the day.
Luckily, I've got a plan.
Eska, Desna, listen to me.
You've got to help us
stop Unalaq.
I know he's your father,
but Vaatu has made him
completely crazy.
We will never turn
on our father.
Please, if you let me out now,
I can still stop him
from destroying everything.
Once he fuses with Vaatu,
no one will be safe.
Desna, he won't be
your father anymore.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Our father is the wisest man
in the world.
If he says what he is doing
is right,
I believe him.
Huh?
You know, if I wanted
some ball of evil
lurking over my shoulder
all the time,
I'd have stayed home
with my mother-in-law.
All right, spirit army,
your general is here.
Follow me!
It's working.
It's not working.
Get me out of here!
Whoo-hoo!
Aah!
All right, guys.
Rescue time.
Bumi, how did you manage to
take out this entire encampment
on your own?
I did it all
with my trusty flute and...
oh, never mind.
You wouldn't believe it anyway.
Let's get moving.
You run into the portal.
I'll try to hold off anyone
who comes after you.
No, you're too hurt.
You need a healer.
Asami, can you take Oogi
and my dad back to my mom?
- Mm-hmm.
- This is my fight now.
Korra.
I love you.
I love you too, dad.
Yipyip.
Once we're inside,
you go find Jinora.
Mako and Bolin
will take care of Unalaq
while I close the portal,
so Vaatu can't escape.
Wait a second.
Worst-case scenario.
So we're fighting Unalaq,
you close the portals,
and let's just say
something happens to you.
Are we gonna be trapped
in there for eternity?
If everything goes as planned,
we'll all walk out together
after harmonic convergence.
If not...
Let's go.
Tenzin, go find Jinora.
Come on!
You're running out of time,
Raava.
I know you feel it coming.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net