Earth...
Fire...
Air...
Water.
Only the Avatar
can master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
After 10,000 years,
harmonic convergence
is here again,
and the dark spirit Vaatu
is free.
Tenzin, Bumi, and Kya
have entered the portal
to rescue Jinora's spirit.
Asami split from the group
and took
the injured Tonraq to safety.
So it's up to Korra, Mako,
and Bolin to stop Unalaq
before he fuses with Vaatu
and becomes a dark Avatar!
Raava, nothing
could stop this moment.
Harmonic convergence
is upon us again.
I'm not going to let you
fuse with Unalaq.
You're going right back
in that prison.
Aah!
Don't let Unalaq
back in the spirit world!
We're on it!
Jinora.
Jinora's spirit,
do you hear me?
It's your Uncle Bumi.
Ah, this isn't working.
We can't just randomly
wander the spirit world,
call out for Jinora,
and expect to find her!
We just need to employ
the simple rules of tracking.
First we locate
her footprints...
Then we follow them.
Do you even know what
spirit footprints look like?
Do spirits even
leave footprints?
Face it, your tracking skills
won't work in the spirit world.
Let me try something.
Ommmm...
Jinora is over there.
I feel a lot of spiritual energy
coming from that direction.
We're in the spirit world.
There's spiritual energy
in every direction!
Enough!
We can't do this by ourselves.
We need a spirit guide.
There!
Spirit, hello.
I'm sorry to disturb you,
but I am in need
of your assistance.
You dare wake me, human?
Humans in the spirit world
belong in one place only!
- Aah!
Whoaoa-oa!
Oof!
Well, that didn't work.
Now where are we?
We're completely lost.
Oh! Uhh!
No!
Huh?
I don't know
if we can win this fight.
We don't need to win.
We just need to stop Unalaq
from getting back
in the spirit world.
Huh?
We're walking in circles!
I've seen that same
spirit mushroom five times!
That's not the same mushroom.
Yes, I am.
See?
Even it knows we're lost.
Oh, sure, listen to a fungus
over your own brother.
What's that?
Mushroom, is that you?
Nope.
Wasn't me.
Iroh?
How...
Where...
It's been so long.
Almost 40 years.
It's nice to see you again.
How did you know we were here?
My friendly spirit fox
told me you were lost.
I came to show you the way out.
Iroh, we are grateful,
but we're not
looking for the way out...
we're looking for my daughter.
I'm sorry to hear that,
but you shouldn't be here.
Vaatu has escaped,
and darkness
threatens to take over.
I'm not leaving
until I find Jinora.
I understand.
But I beg you to be careful.
If you travel too deep
into the spirit world,
you could end up in a place
where only the lost
will ever find you.
A place where only the lost
can find you...
That's it!
I know where to find Jinora!
I'm locking you away
for another 10,000 years,
Vaatu!
Unalaq?
Are you out there?
He must have gone home?
Hello,
my feeble turtle-duck.
Aah!
Huh?
Don't let them escape
this time.
Are you sure this
is the best way to find Jinora?
Trust me.
Hey, you, spirit...
wake up!
You again?
I thought we were going to be
taken to a prison.
This is a prison.
Welcome to the fog
of lost souls.
You will never escape.
Aah!
Stop!
No!
We are now one.
Now a new era for spirits
and humans will begin,
and I will lead them all
as the new Avatar.
Well, I'm the old Avatar,
and my era's not over yet.
What kind of prison
doesn't have any bars or walls?
We could walk
right out of here.
The fog of lost souls
is a spirit prison for humans.
I read about it
in an ancient text.
The fog is actually a spirit...
That infects your mind
and slowly drives you mad,
imprisoning you
in your own darkest memories.
How long can you
be trapped in here?
I am Zhao the Conqueror!
I am the Moonslayer!
I will capture the Avatar!
I am Zhao the Conqueror!
I am the Moonslayer!
I will capture the Avatar!
Hopefully we're not trapped
in here as long as that guy.
You!
You're him!
The last airbender!
Ah!
No!
Get off me!
You've grown...
But I will still defeat you!
Ah!
Ohh!
Come back, Avatar!
Face me!
I am Zhao the Conqueror!
I will capture you!
Victory will be mine!
If we stay together,
we'll find Jinora
and make it out of this fog.
Aah!
Give in.
Your time is over.
Korra, this fight is not over.
Raava...
Vaatu cannot win.
Do not give in
to 10,000 years of darkness.
You are the Avatar.
Aah!
You cannot win!
Jinora!
- Wait a second.
- What?
Do you hear something?
Yes.
They're all around us.
The cannibals,
they're everywhere.
Bumi, you must
focus your mind right now.
There are no cannibals.
Yes, there are!
They're gonna eat
every last one of us!
Who are you two?!
Kya, we're your brothers.
You must remember
before the fog infects you.
No, you are just a vision.
I have no family.
You can't tie me down!
They're closing in!
I gotta get outta here!
Aah!
- Aah!
- No!
Bumi! Kya!
Come back!
Please, let us out.
His groveling is pathetic.
But I do enjoy
the sweet scent of desperation.
Come on!
Your dad has become
an evil monster.
He's trying to bring on
eternal darkness!
Why would you protect someone
who doesn't care
about you at all?
Father was going
to let me expire
when we tried to open
the northern portal...
Perhaps we should
rethink our position.
- Yes!
- No.
Don't listen to him.
His words
are poisoning your mind.
What's with this
outburst of emotion?
I'm sorry, I can't help it.
It's just so sad...
That I'll never get to be
with you again.
What?
Explain yourself further.
Eska, I've always loved you,
and I've always
wanted to be with you...
But now that
the world is ending,
I'm never gonna
get that chance.
We could have been together,
but you left me at the altar.
I was scared!
I was scared
of my true feelings for you.
I should have never left you!
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry that we'll never
have a chance to rekindle
the dying ember
that was our love into a...
Big fire of love flames.
You'll never defeat my father.
But should you survive,
perhaps we can spend
eternal darkness together.
Wow, that was
the best acting I've ever seen.
You completely fooled her!
Yeah, right, that...
that was acting.
They will certainly perish.
I must stay focused.
Remember who you are, Tenzin.
You are the son of Avatar Aang.
You are the hope
for future generations
of airbenders.
The fate of the world
rests on your shoulders.
But what if I fail?
Then your father's hope
for the future dies with you.
I can't fail!
You will.
Aah!
Stop it!
I am the son of Avatar Aang.
I am the hope for future
generations of airbenders.
I am the son of Avatar Aang!
Hello, my son.
Dad, I've failed you.
I am no spiritual leader,
and I've let the world down.
I'll never be the man you were.
You are right.
You are trying to hold on
to a false perception
of yourself.
You are not me,
and you should not be me.
You are Tenzin.
I am not a reflection
of my father.
I am Tenzin.
Jinora!
Ah...
What happened?
I think our brother saved us.
Dad.
You're going to be okay,
sweetie.
I'm here.
What happened?
The last thing I remember
is dark spirits taking me away.
You were trapped
in the fog of lost souls,
but I wasn't going
to let you stay there.
I'm so happy to see you, dad.
Korra!
He's got the light spirit!
Aah!
The world's in trouble.
What are you talking about?
How do you know?
I can feel it.
- What happened?
- It's Korra.
This light spirit
will guide you
out of the spirit world.
I have to go help.
Jinora, wait!
Now...
10,000 years of darkness
begins!
Aah!
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net