Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar
can master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
After fusing with Vaatu,
Unalaq became a dark Avatar
and ripped Korra
and Raava apart.
By destroying Raava,
Unalaq and Vaatu transformed
into the most powerful
dark spirit that's ever lived.
Tenzin managed to free Jinora
from the fog of lost souls,
but her spiritual quest
isn't over yet.
Can anyone save the world from
eternal darkness?
Ooh.
Pretty.
General Iroh,
are your ships in position?
Yes, Mr. president,
but I need to know
what kind of enemy
we're dealing with.
It's time to take back
the physical world.
Fire!
Monster attack!
They're over here!
Please, wake up.
They're going to be all right,
but I need to get them into
some spirit water right away.
Thank goodness you're all okay.
Did you find Jinora?
I was able to rescue her soul,
but she wasn't ready
to return to her body yet.
She sense the world
was in grave danger.
She was right.
Were you able
to stop Unalaq and Vaatu?
No, they fused, then Vaatu
ripped Raava right out of me
and destroyed her.
Vaatu won.
No!
I'm too young
to live through 10,000
years of darkness.
Korra, can't you talk to one of
your past lives or something?
When Vaatu destroyed Raava,
he destroyed my connection
to the past Avatars too.
If that's true, then...
the cycle is over.
I'm the last Avatar.
I'm so sorry, Tenzin.
She needs you now,
more than ever.
It's going to destroy
the entire city.
We're going down.
It's pandemonium
in the streets.
Giant vines
are destroying everything.
This is Shiro Shinobi
signing off...
Zhu Li, commence operation
"winged freedom!"
Do the thing!
The other Avatars may not
be able to help you anymore,
but perhaps I can.
No one can help me now.
I know I haven't been
the best mentor to you,
but I realized it was because
I had a lot of spiritual growth
to do myself.
There may still be a way
for you to stop Vaatu.
How?
Let go of your attachment
to who you think you are,
and connect
with your inner spirit.
Haven't you heard
anything I said?
Raava is gone.
I'm not connected
to a spirit anymore.
I'm not talking about Raava.
Raava is not who you are.
Come with me.
I need to show you something.
Why are you showing me
Vaatu's prison?
Because this tree had a history
long before it held Vaatu.
This is the tree of time.
And the legends
say that its roots
bind the spirit and physical
worlds together.
And you think this tree
can help me somehow?
Yes, I have read that long ago,
the ancients would meditate
beneath this tree
and connect with the great
cosmic energy of the universe.
These are my memories.
The tree of time remembers all.
Korra, the most powerful thing
about you
is not the spirit of Raava,
but your own inner spirit.
You have always been strong,
unyielding, and fearless.
Avatar Wan.
Before he fused with Raava,
wan was just a regular person.
But he was brave and smart
and always wanted
to defend the helpless.
That's right.
He became a legend
because of who he was,
not what he was.
He wasn't defined by Raava
any more than you are.
Everyone in Republic City
is in danger.
- You have to help them, Korra.
- How?
They're halfway
around the world.
Do as the ancients once did.
Connect to the cosmic energy
of the universe.
Don't bend the elements,
but the energy within yourself.
You really think I can do this?
I have no doubt.
Thank you
for not giving up on me.
I'm proud of you.
If you and Vaatu have the same
fight every 10,000 years,
why hasn't one of you
destroyed the other?
He cannot destroy light
any more
than I can destroy darkness.
One cannot exist
without the other.
Find the light in the dark.
Uh... What did you say to her,
exactly?
Korra's back.
And she's a blue giant.
You are looking
for something that is gone.
Raava has been destroyed.
And soon you will be too!
They're coming for Korra.
Leave my Bolin alone!
I am so done with spirits.
Eska!
I love you!
Mwah!
Let's face the end
of the world together!
You're so romantic.
With you out of the way,
I will be the one true Avatar.
Mommy, it's Jinora.
She's... Beautiful.
What?
Let me see.
Be careful, sweetie!
No!
Raava.
Go in peace.
Harmonic convergence
is nearly over.
We must return to the spirit
world so we can fuse once again.
I'll see you soon, dad.
Gran-gran, I missed you.
What about Korra
and the others?
Don't worry.
They're all right.
Korra saved the world.
Her Avatar spirit has returned.
It's over.
Mwah.
I don't even know what to say.
You were amazing.
And the way you turned all
gigantic like that, wow!
I just wish Varrick
had been here to film it.
It would have been
the greatest mover ever.
After the Nuktuk chronicles,
of course.
I'm sorry about your father,
but he was already
fused with Vaatu.
I couldn't save him.
It seems cousin Korra
is under the impression
we are saddened
by our father's demise.
But I will not miss him at all.
In the end,
he became a deplorable man.
Agreed.
But how will we
explain this to mother?
So I was thinking,
I'm not really a fan
of the long-distance
relationship thing.
So how about you move
to Republic City with me?
I do not think
that will be possible.
Okay, Desna can come too.
I will not be joining you,
Bolin.
Desna and I must return home.
- But you said...
- Eternal darkness was upon us.
I became caught up
in the moment.
Yeah.
I guess I did too.
But... You will always
hold a special place
in the organ
that pumps my blood.
I will remember you fondly,
my turtle-duck.
Bum-Ju, you're okay.
I missed you, little buddy.
Now that you're bonded
with Raava once again,
are you also reconnected
to your past lives?
No.
I think that link
is gone forever.
I see.
Why don't you close the portals
and we'll go home.
Maybe I shouldn't.
What do you mean?
What if Unalaq was right
when he said the Avatar
shouldn't be a bridge
between the two worlds?
What if Avatar wan
made a mistake
when he closed the portals?
What if humans and spirits
weren't meant to live apart?
Well, what do you think
I should do?
I think you should
trust your instincts.
There is nothing else
I can teach you.
You are the Avatar.
Whatever your decision,
I support you.
- Hey, can we talk?
- Of course.
There's something
I've been wanting to tell you
about that fight we had.
I know I said
it wasn't that bad,
but that's not exactly true.
I, um... I broke up with you.
I remember.
But I thought you said you
lost part of your memory?
I did, but being inside
the tree of time
brought it back.
I'm sorry
for blowing up at you.
That's okay.
I think we both said
some things that we regret.
Why didn't you just tell me
the truth in the first place?
I know I should have,
but I didn't wanna hurt you
all over again.
I guess part of me wanted to
forget about the breakup too.
I think we both know that
this...
Us... Doesn't work.
You're right.
It's over.
For real this time.
I'll always love you, Korra.
And I'll always love you.
You want a hug?
Hmmm.
The war of the water tribes
is over.
Unalaq has been defeated
and the northern fleet
is returning home.
The water tribes
will always be allies,
but the Southern tribe
is now independent.
And the Southern council
of elders has appointed
my father, Tonraq,
to be your new chief.
I've realized that even though
we should learn
from those who came before us,
we must also forge
our own path.
So that is why I've decided
to keep the portals open.
Humans can now physically
enter the spirit world
and spirits will
be free to roam our world.
I will no longer be the bridge.
Humans and spirits
must learn to live together.
My mission will always
be to use Raava's light spirit
to guide the world
toward peace and balance.
Harmonic convergence has caused
a shift in the planet's energy.
I can feel it.
Things will never
be the same again.
We are entering a new age.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net