Earth,
fire,
air,
water...
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Six months ago, Avatar Korra defeated
Amon and the Equalists.
Since then, the council was disbanded
and the United Republic
elected its first president.
Tenzin's brother, Commander Bumi,
retired and moved to Air Temple Island.
And Korra and her boyfriend, Mako,
have been the talk of the town.
Peace has come to Republic City,
but unbeknownst to the Avatar,
danger now threatens
the Southern Water Tribe.
This your first watch?
Well then, you'd better keep
your eyes peeled, laddie.
You never know what creatures
lurk in the murky depths.
Uh, sir.
What?
Man overboard! Man overboard!
It's pro-bending night in Republic City,
and have we got a doozy for you.
Fan favorites, the fire ferrets,
are about to take on hot newcomers,
the rhino-lions.
Now we all know that our
last match was garbage.
Terrible.
Even Pabu could have done a better job.
But that's in the past,
because when you back a
fire ferret in the corner,
well, mister, he comes out fighting!
So let's get out there
and bend like there's no tomorrow.
Are you with me?
Ooh, the fire ferrets go down in the water
and right into the record books
for the fastest knockout
in pro-bending history.
Where's Mako when I need him?
Looks like you had some car trouble.
Good thing the police are here.
I think these planes are
finally ready to ship.
I hate to mention the
elephant-rhino in the room,
but since your father was thrown in prison,
no company will work with us.
We're nearly bankrupt.
Don't worry.
I'm going to the South Pole
to meet with someone who can help us
put future industries back on top.
Wah!
The Avatar is the winner!
No fair.
You can't go into the Avatar state to win.
You did what?
The Avatar state is not to
be used as a booster rocket.
You are toying with a dangerous power
that you obviously do not appreciate.
It's the "Avatar state,"
and I'm the Avatar.
Who appreciates it more than me?
Clearly, you need more training to grasp
the depths of your spiritual connections,
not to mention that you're still a long way
from mastering air-bending.
I have mastered air-bending.
Punch, punch, punch!
See? Mastered.
Looks pretty good to me.
Is it too late for you to un-retire
from the united forces?
The paperwork's gone
through, little brother.
From now on, it's 24/7 Bumi time!
You've mastered Korra-style air-bending.
Now you need to master real air-bending.
Hopefully, our visit to
all of the air temples
will give you the inspiration you need
to delve more deeply into your studies.
Can we see where Grandpa Aang was born?
How many lemurs can I have?
I want to get tattoos,
but instead of arrows,
I want lightning bolts.
You can't get lightning bolts.
That doesn't make any sense.
You don't make any sense!
Fight, fight, fight!
No one's fighting.
We're going to have a wonderful time.
Now that the president is in office
and I'm not needed on the council,
I can finally relax with my family
and give Korra the attention she needs.
Great. More attention.
Relax?
I'd pay money to see that.
Maybe I'll tag along just
to see "Vacation Tenzin."
You're not invited.
Before we go on your dad's study trip,
we're going to have some
real fun in my hometown
at the glacier spirits festival.
They've got rides, games,
and all kinds of fried food on sticks.
Yay!
Yep, there's Vacation Tenzin.
And you can't stop me
from going to the festival.
Mom already invited me.
So I walk up and say,
"looks like you had some car trouble.
Good thing the police are here."
Did you write that beforehand?
Yeah, I had a few others. Let's see, uh...
"Looks like you guys should
put more 'try' in triad," huh?
Or, "when you get to jail,
tell 'em Mako sent ya."
Ooh, I like that one.
Okay, I'll use that next time.
Beifong says if I keep it up,
I could make detective soon.
Oh, that sounds so fun.
All I do is train all day.
It's like Tenzin's totally
forgotten how I beat Amon.
Tenzin's just trying to help you become
the best Avatar you can be.
Of course you'd take his side.
I'm not taking his side. I'm just...
I'm gonna take a walk.
Why is it so much easier to bust triads
than it is to get through one
conversation with my girlfriend?
Grangran!
Oh, you've all gotten so big.
We missed you, Aunt Kya.
Oh, I missed you too.
Your father doesn't bring
you to visit nearly enough.
He's probably scared I'll beat him up
like when we were kids.
I'm not scared of you...
anymore.
- You remember Mako.
- Sir.
I hope you're not getting my daughter
into any more trouble up in the city.
Uh, no. I, uh... no.
Knock it off, dad.
Wow, look at all these people
that came out to greet us.
Uh, no. They came to greet them.
The great chief of the Northern Water Tribe
comes to grace us with his presence.
Hooray.
Just relax, Tonraq.
He'll be gone soon enough.
Whoa, who are the lovely ladies?
That's Eska and Desna,
the chief's children.
Desna is a guy.
Oh, no, sure. I knew that.
And which one is Desna?
Good to see you again, Avatar Korra.
Good to see you too.
Tonraq.
Brother.
It's a shame the southerners have abandoned
all connections to the spirits,
even during the most hallowed times.
I've always loved the
glacier spirits festival.
It's fun.
This festival used to be a solemn time
of fasting and meditation.
Now it's just a chance to watch some rube
try to stick an entire
arctic hen in his mouth.
Wha... what? It's so good.
Traditions change.
It's not the end of the world.
Tell that to the sailors
who are being attacked
by angry spirits in Southern waters.
Some traditions have purpose.
Wait, spirits are attacking ships?
I'm surprised the Avatar
doesn't know about that.
Apparently you haven't been given
all the information you need.
It would be my honor to instruct you
in the spiritual ways of the water tribe.
I wouldn't mind learning
about fighting spirits.
Air-bending is getting pretty boring.
Tenzin is Korra's instructor.
He can give her all the training she needs.
So you've said.
I'm glad you came with me to this meeting.
Varrick is one of the
richest men in the world,
and he controls the entire
global shipping business.
So you're my assistant.
Just stand there and don't say anything.
No problem.
Pabu and I are natural assistants.
Man, this is nice.
I gotta get into this
whole "business" thing.
Did you see that? Levitation!
I was a foot off the ground.
Is that incredible or what?
How does he do that?
- That's unbelievable.
- That's amazing.
What?
It looked like you were
just sitting on a pillow.
Are you saying I wasn't levitating?
Uh, no?
Well, why didn't anyone tell me?
Now I look like an idiot!
Swami, you're fired!
I like you, kid.
You're a real straight
shooter, just like me.
Ms. Sato? He's with you?
Brought your tiger-shark
with you to do business, huh?
Now that's moxie.
Get over here and pop a squat.
Zhu Li, get some tea for my guests.
Thank you for meeting with me.
As you know, future industries
is looking for a partner
- to handle our shipping...
- Sure.
But first, you gotta check out
moving pictures.
Zhu Li, do the thing.
You're gonna love this.
Mind-blowing, right?
- Yeah.
- Now, forget that!
That's the past! Shut it off, Zhu Li!
Imagine watching this.
Ginger, come over here and do your poses.
Spectacular.
And we tell a story.
There's romance, action,
some funny animal stuff for the kids.
You know, whatever.
Thanks, Ginger. Go rest your gams.
How about that, tiger-shark?
We're gonna do big business
with these "movers," as I call 'em.
Okay.
But I'm just concentrating
on getting future industries back on track.
If we could hammer out a deal...
Stop.
Look me in the eye.
We got a deal!
We'll hammer out the details
at the royal feast tonight.
Now who wants a rocket-boat ride?
Is that how business usually goes?
You are a natural assistant.
This is a wonderful feast
in your honor, Uncle.
This is nothing.
When this festival was founded,
the tribal elders would
commune with the spirits.
People would watch the
brilliant displays of light
as spirits danced in the sky.
Wow. I've never seen that.
And that is a shame,
since the Avatar is the bridge
between the material world and the spirits.
That is why I want so badly to teach you,
to help you fulfill your destiny.
I thought I had made it clear
that Tenzin is teaching her.
Every Avatar before you
traveled the world to learn.
It was Tenzin and your
father who kept you secluded
at the South Pole.
I thought Aang ordered the white lotus
to keep me down here?
We all did what we
thought was best for you.
Who I train with should
be my decision, dad,
not yours or Tenzin's.
Looks like someone's
trying to take your place
as the Avatar's stick-in-the-mud mentor.
Bumi, don't pick on Tenzin.
You know he's always been sensitive.
I'm not sensitive!
As your chief, it is my honor to speak
at this festival, which was founded
to bring our tribes together
and restore the ancient balance
between our world and that of the spirits.
But I am saddened to
see what it has become...
a cheap carnival that celebrates
greedy and trivial humans.
I fear the time is fast approaching
when the North can no longer stand idly by
while our Southern brothers
slip into total spiritual decay.
Angry spirits are already
attacking ships in your waters.
I only hope we are not
too late to change course.
Chief Unalaq, everybody.
Always great to have him in town.
Now let's have some fun
with wacky wushu's dancin' otter-penguins.
Wish me luck. I'm making my move.
Good luck.
Those two have always creeped me out.
They smell like a grandma's attic.
Hey, I'm Bolin. I'm a friend of Korra's.
You're Eska, right?
Wow, I'm just... I'm loving these robes.
So you are from the North, right? Cool.
That's like... you know, that's, like,
my favorite direction.
I think he is trying to establish
some kind of bond with you
based on your geographic point of origin.
Perhaps it would be interesting
to spend time with a person
whose ways are so rough and uncultured.
You amuse me. I will make you mine.
You mean like a boyfriend
or... or like a slave?
Yes.
Win me prizes.
Unalaq offered to train me.
He says he can teach me about the spirits
and my connection to them.
Sounds good. What does Tenzin think?
Tenzin thinks I'm his prisoner
or one of his kids.
I'll never finish training
with him in charge.
We have a winner.
I mean, you heard what Unalaq said.
The South is spiritually unbalanced,
and it's the Avatar's job to fix it.
But my dad won't even let me
think about Unalaq teaching me.
- Well?
- Well, what?
What do you think I should do?
I guess you should do
what you think is right.
I support whatever decision you make.
Oh, thanks. That's a big help.
I thought you wanted me to be supportive.
Now you want me to tell you what I think?
Make up your mind.
Just forget it.
Naga, what are you doing?
Naga, hush.
Quiet, Naga. You'll wake everyone up.
What's going on?
What is that?
Got it!
Don't got it!
Korra!
Spirit, why are you angry with us?
What have we done to offend you?
Go in peace.
Korra, are you all right?
How were you able to control that spirit
when no one else could?
As your father could tell you,
I have spent my life studying the spirits
and learning their ways.
All of this knowledge is lost in the South,
but I could teach you everything I know.
Chief Unalaq, clearly,
you are very knowledgeable,
but Korra still has much
to learn about air-bending,
and I hope that going to the air temples
will help her connect
with the past avatars.
The air temples will teach her nothing.
Only I can give her the training she needs
to be a complete Avatar.
I've told you that will not happen.
Hey, I'm right here!
Anyone want to ask me what I think?
Korra, please, listen.
I'm tired of listening
to you... both of you.
You keep me locked up,
telling me you know what's best,
but both of you were powerless
against the spirit attack.
I think it's time I had a new teacher.
Now, Korra...
Unalaq has proven he's the only one
who knows what I need to learn.
I have to go with him.
Please, I know you're angry,
but we've come so far together.
I'm sorry, Tenzin.
This is as far as we go.
It has been a pleasure serving you,
Avatar Korra.
I think you forgot a couple of things.
Mother, I think I need some time alone
with my family right now.
This is your family, Tenzin.
When you get to be my age,
you'll be thankful for the time you had
with your siblings.
Besides, I think it's important
that you all visit your
father's home together.
Come on, it'll be fun.
I'm dying to see that
laid-back "Vacation Tenzin"
I've heard so much about.
All right. Hop on.
I love you, mom.
We'll see you soon.
Do you think I did the right thing?
I don't know.
I'm sorry, but I'm not very good
at this Avatar counseling thing.
But I know your heart
is in the right place.
You'll just have to trust it.
I know this was a hard decision, Korra.
But it was the right one.
Now it is time to put it behind you
and begin your new training.
I have great plans for you.
You're early.
What can I say?
I'm pumped up to learn
that unalaq spirit fighting.
I'm not here to teach you to fight spirits.
I'm here to help you begin
your spiritual training.
We're going to one of the most
remote places in the world...
the long-neglected spiritual
center of your tribe:
the South Pole.
You're gonna train me at the South Pole?
We will do more than just train.
By neglecting the spirits,
the people of the South
have brought darkness upon themselves,
and now it threatens to destroy our tribe.
We must set things right.
The Southern Water Tribe depends on you.
A dangerous trip to the South Pole?
Count me in.
There it is, the Southern air temple.
Isn't it magnificent?
Master Tenzin, welcome.
Good to see you again, Abbot Shung.
Is there anything you need?
Water? Dandelion Greens?
Ah, perhaps you'd like
to re-center yourself
by meditating in the gardens.
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
And you must be the honorable Pema.
Please, accept these gifts.
This is an ancient air-bender head shaver
we've refurbished just for you.
Oh... okay.
And, Pema, these flowers
once filled the mountainside.
Now they can brighten up your room.
That's... sweet?
You didn't have to.
Nonsense.
Whatever you need is yours.
Anything for the mother
of the next generation of air-benders.
No! That gift is mine.
You don't even like to read.
Yep, those are the world's
next generation of air-benders.
Mommy, daddy, look.
I finally got a lemur.
I'm gonna name him Poki.
Poki, come back!
Excuse me, a little help here.
Sorry, I thought you were the servants.
We're Tenzin's brother and sister.
Avatar Aang had other children?
The world is filled with more air-benders?
We're not air-benders.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
I thought you said Bolin was coming.
He said he'd be here, but
I can't worry about it.
I have to make sure you
have everything you need
for a safe trip.
Thanks, captain expedition,
but I'll be fine.
Tonraq, what do you want?
I heard you're taking
Korra to the South Pole.
I'm coming.
Absolutely not.
You're a distraction to Korra
and a hindrance to what needs to be done.
My daughter is not going without me.
She needs someone to watch after her.
Dad, why do you always think
you know what's best for me?
Because he's misguided.
The sad truth is it's men like your father
who have put the spirit
world out of balance.
He's ignored my warnings in the past
and hasn't learned since.
What happened in the past?
It doesn't matter.
What matters is the everstorm.
The everstorm?
It's a massive blizzard that's
battered the South Pole for decades.
I'm coming, unless you
think you can stop me.
Guys! Hey, wait for me!
Check it out.
I'm traveling in style.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Still getting used to that throttle.
Uh, where'd you get the ride?
Varrick. He's awesome.
He also gave me this fancy snowsuit.
It's inflatable with an internal heater,
emergency beacon, and food ration pouch.
I mean, if I get lost, I
can survive in this thing
for, like, like, a month.
Who wants some freeze-dried cucumber-quats?
Nobody?
Did I interrupt a conversation?
No, the conversation is over.
Dad, come if you want.
Just don't interfere with my training.
Does this sidecar have the
capacity for two passengers?
Sure does.
But, uh, who's gonna drive?
Well, what do you know? Looks like...
Go away, Mako.
So once we get to the South Pole,
then what happens?
You will open an ancient spirit portal.
I'm sorry. What now?
At the South Pole, there is a portal
that connects our world
to the spirit world.
But it has long been closed.
And that's why the evil
spirits are attacking?
There are no evil spirits.
There is light and dark in them all.
But when they're unbalanced,
the darkness takes over.
If you can open the portal in time,
balance will be restored.
What do you mean "in time"?
There's a reason the
glacier spirits festival
ends on the winter solstice.
That's when the spirit world
and the physical world are close together.
Only then can the Avatar open the portal.
The winter solstice is tomorrow.
Exactly.
And we can't afford to wait another year.
Easy, Naga.
What are those?
Dark spirits.
Let's keep moving.
We have to find a safe
place to set up camp.
Uncle, why do you think the dark spirits
are following us?
Can we not talk about dark spirits, please?
My brother doesn't like ghost stories.
Don't worry.
I will protect you, my feeble turtle-duck.
Thank you.
Sadly, this isn't a ghost story.
This is real.
The spirits are angry because he's here.
Haven't you ever wondered how your father
ended up in the South Pole?
Why he's never taken you to
visit his homeland in the North?
Unalaq, this is not the time.
You're right.
You should have told her a long time ago.
Told me what?
I left the North Pole because...
I was banished.
You were banished from the North? Why?
Because I almost
destroyed the entire tribe.
20 years ago, I was a general
in the Northern Water Tribe,
sworn to protect my people.
Brother, we're being attacked.
I drove them out of the city
and deep into the frozen tundra.
We tracked them deep
into an ancient forest.
Many believed this forest
was the home to spirits,
and the Barbarians retreated there
because they thought wouldn't attack
on such hallowed grounds.
They thought wrong.
We captured the barbarians,
but in the process, we
destroyed the forest.
I didn't realize the consequences
of what I had done.
By destroying the forest,
I unknowingly let loose angry spirits.
They threatened to destroy everything.
The entire city.
Unalaq was able to guide the
spirits back to the forest,
but by then, the damage had been done.
For being the cause of so much devastation,
my father banished me from the
Northern Water Tribe in shame.
That's when I came to the
South and started a new life.
So you were supposed to be chief.
Then he became chief.
No wonder you guys don't like each other.
What?
Isn't that what happened?
I can't believe you kept this from me.
I was protecting you from the shame
I brought on the family.
Why do you keep hiding things from me
and then telling me it's
for my own protection?
I'm tired of you protecting me!
Korra.
The statue room.
That's right, Jinora.
The most sacred place
in the entire Southern air temple.
Here you will find statues of
every Avatar who ever lived.
Where are your brother and sister?
You can't catch me.
I'm the greatest
air-scooter-er of all time.
Meelo!
Korra, you have every
right to be mad at me,
but I don't want you to
make the same mistake I made.
I should have never gone into that forest,
and we shouldn't be going
to the South Pole now.
Spirits and the physical
world should remain separate.
Dad, it's my job to be the bridge
between the spirits and the physical world,
and I finally have a chance
to live up to my potential.
You don't even know if
what unalaq says is true.
You want proof? Look to the sky.
Where I'm from, the spirits are at peace,
and they light up the dark.
The Northern Lights.
Yes.
There used to be lights
in the South as well.
But during the hundred year war,
the South was thrown out of balance,
and the lights disappeared.
When the war ended, the North helped
to rebuild you physically as a nation.
But we have not rebuilt you spiritually.
Now the spirits no longer
dance in your skies.
Instead, they rampage in the everstorm.
I think we're here.
Is that what I think it is?
We must keep moving.
Oh, man. I really don't like this.
Bolin, just stay calm.
There's no reason to... panic!
Korra, look out!
Oh, it's in the engine!
Is everyone okay?
I can't stop it!
I'll save you.
I'm a raft!
Uh, can someone please deflate me?
Thank you.
Oh, great. There goes our equipment.
Now what are we supposed to do?
There's only one thing to do.
- We have to turn back.
- No.
The solstice is tonight. We're so close.
This mission is too dangerous.
- We're leaving.
- No, dad.
You're leaving.
Don't worry, sir.
I'll keep an eye on Korra for you.
Thank you, Mako.
Let's open this portal and lead your father
and the entire Southern Water Tribe
in the right direction.
We don't have much time.
Then what are we waiting for?
So what exactly were you
and my dad talking about?
Nothing.
He was just worried about you, that's all.
You know, sometimes I
wonder whose side you're on.
There aren't any sides.
We all just want to help however we can.
You have to trust that we're here for you.
We've arrived.
Trees frozen in ice.
It's just like the Sacred Fforest
Tonraq destroyed in the North.
So what do I do?
You must find your way
to the heart of the forest
where the dormant spirit portal lies.
From here, you're on your own.
Wait a second.
There's no way she's going alone.
Yeah, if she goes, we go too.
The Avatar must go alone.
But I don't have any
connection with the spirits.
In fact, it seems like they hate me.
You have to believe in yourself
like I believe in you.
What is it?
I guess I'm just so used to people
telling me how to do things
that I forgot what it was like
to have someone trust in me.
Korra, all the past avatars
live on inside of you.
Let them guide you.
Let them help you find
the light in the dark.
Wait here.
I'll be okay.
Good luck.
The spirit portal.
Amazing.
What Avatar is this?
The light in the dark.
Why isn't it opening?
Come on, portal. Open!
The spirits dancing in the sky.
I can't believe it.
It's beautiful.
She did it.
Hey, Korra, you're back!
Hey, Korra's back!
Wha...
Why are you initiating physical contact
with another woman?
Everything you said was true.
Avatar Korra, you have taken the first step
in bringing balance back to the South,
and soon, the whole world.
- You never cease to amaze me.
- Thanks.
By the way, I'm really
sorry for being a total pain.
Things were really stressful and confusing.
It's hard being the Avatar.
It's harder being the Avatar's boyfriend.
What are all your
northern troops doing here?
Opening the spirit portal
was only the first step
in getting the Southern Water Tribe
back on its righteous path.
There's more difficult work to be done
before our two tribes are truly united.
== sync by cwluc / corrected by chamallow ==
= www.addic7ed.com =
== s02e01-02 Rebel Spirit / The Southern Lights ==
= original air date 2013-09-13 =
www.tvsubtitles.net