Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar
can master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
The Avatar has gone missing.
After president Raiko
refused Korra's request
to aid the South
in the war of the water tribes,
she headed to the fire nation,
seeking a new ally
against Unalaq.
But unbeknownst to her friends,
a dark spirit attacked Korra
and dragged her into the ocean.
She has washed up
on a desolate island
with no memory of who she is.
We found the Avatar
washed up onshore,
but she doesn't
remember anything.
Raava.
A dark energy has infected her.
We must purge it
before it destroys
her Avatar spirit.
Let the waters
cleanse the darkness
that plagues your spirit.
- Who are you?
- I am you.
Who am I?
You are the Avatar.
I don't know what that is.
In order to remember,
you must regain your connection
with your Avatar spirit.
If you don't,
darkness will engulf the world.
You will die,
and our era will end.
How do I regain my connection?
Go back.
Return to the beginning.
Find Raava.
Are you Raava?
No, but I can help you
find her.
My name is Wan,
and I will show you
how I became the first Avatar.
Nobody steals
from the chou brothers!
Really?
Because I just did.
You're dead, Wan.
Actually, I feel quite alive.
Hey, stop!
Hey, fellas.
You're just in time for lunch!
Oh!
I told you
no one steals from us.
Did you steal
from the Chous again?
Yeah, and I got nothing
to show for it
except a few dirty rolls
and a whole lot of bruises.
Hey, Yao,
I got some food for you.
Mmm.
Delicious.
Thank you, Wan.
You guys are hungry too, huh?
Wan, you should eat.
They need it more than I do.
Besides, I'm tired
of eating scraps.
If only there was some way
to get
into the Chous' food cellar.
We'd be eating like...
well, like Chous.
If chou the elder catches you
sneaking into his palace,
you'll end up dead.
Or worse, he'll banish you
to the spirit wilds.
No, don't get banished.
You don't want nothing to do
with those spirits.
They'll get inside ya,
scramble up your mind,
turn ya into this...
a monster!
Don't do anything crazy, Wan.
You just gotta accept
the world is the way it is.
Some people have power.
Some people don't.
And you don't.
Not yet, anyway.
Are you strong?
Are you fearless?
Do you have what it takes
to battle the spirits?
Then join the hunt.
Count me in.
We're going to be out
in the wilds for a week.
You wouldn't last two seconds.
I can handle myself.
We all get fire, right?
Yeah, but do you know
how to use it?
Well, not exactly, but I...
ah, let him come.
Not like we got
any other volunteers lining up.
All right.
Welcome to the hunt.
The lion turtle.
Great guardian of our city,
we are venturing
into the spirit wilds
to bring back food
for our people.
Please, grant us
the power of fire.
The power is yours to keep
until your return.
You're first, kid.
May the element of fire
protect you
against the spirits.
Whoa!
Just make sure you aim
at the spirits, not us, okay?
Sure thing.
Everyone stay close.
Spirits love
to pick off stragglers.
Uh, guys?
I don't think I can do this.
Now, quit your whining.
We haven't even seen
a spirit yet.
I think I wanna go home.
I knew you were nothing
but a sniveling coward.
Go give your fire back
to the lion turtle,
and don't ever show
your face around me again.
Wan, you're back.
What goodies did you snatch
for us this time?
What did you do?
You can't steal
from the lion turtle.
Really?
Because I just did.
You know it's forbidden
to bring the power
of the element into the city.
Please, go back
to the lion turtle
and return the fire.
Jaya, it's time to stop
being so afraid of the Chous
and show them we have the power
to change things.
Hey, Chous!
Open the gate, and let us in.
What are those filthy peasants
doing here?
Don't worry, father.
We'll take care of them.
Hand over all the food
you're hoarding,
and we won't give you
any trouble.
You're not getting past us.
We have the weapons.
You're powerless.
Powerless, huh?
Follow me!
Grab as much food as you can.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe we do have the power
to change things.
Stop right there!
Looks like the Chous
found backup.
Get everyone out of here.
I'll hold them off.
No, please.
Have mercy.
Wan?
Even when you have the power,
you're afraid to use it.
Tell me who else
was involved in the rebellion,
and I might take mercy on you.
I'm not telling you anything.
Then, you've left me no choice.
Wan, you are hereby banished.
Yeah! And give back
the fire you stole.
No!
Wait.
Great lion turtle, I am sorry
for stealing the fire from you,
and I accept my punishment.
But please, I need to be able
to protect myself in the wilds.
Never again may you return
to this city.
But I will allow you
to keep
the power of the element.
Bet he doesn't last
till morning.
Hey, watch where
you're stepping, human!
- Who said that?
- Down here!
How'd you like it if I started
walking all over you?
You're just a little frog.
Who's little now?
Get off me!
You are not welcome
in my oasis, human.
Please, help me.
I'm starving,
and I haven't slept all night.
Not my problem.
Let me pass.
You dare use fire against me?
Now, be gone with you!
And who might you be?
I am bushy, the bush spirit.
And I would like to enter
your oasis.
Very well.
You may pass.
Wait a second!
Something stinks.
I knew I smelled a human!
Come on, let me in,
just for a little while.
No!
Go back to your lion turtle.
Believe me,
I'd love to go back home.
But I can't.
I was kicked out.
- That's too bad.
- Poor human.
Don't pity him.
He's just like
every other human:
Ugly, destructive,
and lacking any respect
for nature.
Who are you calling ugly, ugly?
Hmm.
If you can't go back
to your city,
then you should go live
in another one.
What?
There are other lion turtles?
"There are
other lion turtles?"
Of course there are,
dozens of them!
Boy, you humans are stupid too.
So which way
to the nearest lion turtle city?
Hmm.
I think it's on the other side
of none-of-your-business valley.
Real funny.
You know what?
I don't need your help.
I'll find it myself.
Good luck!
It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of there.
Finally, we caught something.
Get it down.
Back off.
Wan?
What are you doing here?
I'm saving this animal.
That animal's our dinner.
Now, get out of the way.
No.
Ahh!
He... help!
Help!
Get 'em off!
Ahh!
Well, looks like
you're all out of tricks, Wan.
I really hate humans!
No, no.
I don't know
what he's screaming about.
He's better-looking now.
I feel great.
What's in this water?
It has
special healing properties.
Thanks.
So what did you do
to that hunter?
Spirits are able to take over
a human body for a short time.
If I stayed in there
any longer,
I would've killed him,
which I did consider.
Thanks for saving my neck.
But why'd you do it?
I saw you save the cat-deer
from those hunters.
I've never seen such an act
of selflessness
from a human before.
Told you
I wasn't like the others.
Guess I underestimated you,
human.
Are you off to find
another lion turtle city?
I was.
But I think I've had enough
of humans for a while.
I've decided to stay here
and learn the ways
of the spirits.
- What a great idea.
- That'll be fun.
Oh, now, now, hold on.
A human living with spirits?
It's never been done.
First time
for everything, right?
Hmm.
I guess we can try it.
I've never had a human
as a pet before.
I think
I'll call you "stinky."
The name is Wan.
Stinky is more accurate.
What happened in the wilds?
Where are the others?
Gone.
Spirits took them.
They were protecting
that kid Wan
like he was one of their own.
Did you hear that?
Wan's still alive.
And the way Wan moves fire,
it's like nothing
I've ever seen.
He uses it like
it's an extension of his body.
Wan has proven
that with the power of fire,
anyone can survive
in the wilds.
We don't have to live
under chou the elder's rules
anymore,
so I say we leave this city
and start over.
Who's with me?
You ready to go, Mula?
You sure you want to leave?
Yes, it's time I see
the rest of the world
and find
the other lion turtle cities.
I'm proud to call you
my friend, stinky.
Thank you for everything.
Good-bye, everyone.
We'll miss you.
The all-powerful spirits
are battling.
They're gonna wipe out
the entire valley!
Stop,
or you'll destroy everything!
This doesn't
concern you, human!
It does when the lives
of spirits and animals
are in danger.
If you're a friend to spirits,
then use your fire to help me
break free.
Don't involve the human.
This is between us.
Please, save me.
She has tormented me
for 10,000 years.
10,000 years?
Let him go!
Thank you, human.
You have performed
a great service for the spirits.
Do you realize
what you've done?
Yeah, I helped a spirit
who was being bullied by you.
You are gravely mistaken.
I was keeping him
under control.
And what gives you the right?
You don't even know who I am,
do you?
- Should I?
- Yes.
My name is Raava.
That spirit you freed is Vaatu.
He is the force
of darkness and chaos.
I am the force
of light and peace.
Since the beginning of time,
we have battled
over the fate of this world.
And for the past 10,000 years,
I have kept darkness
under control
and the world in balance,
until you came along.
So by freeing Vaatu,
I let chaos into the world?
Precisely.
The human and spirit realms
are headed toward annihilation,
and it's all your fault.
Raava, I found you.
Should we pull her up?
No.
She is connecting with
her deepest Avatar memories.
She must confront her own past
if she is to move forward.
We can only hope
that she survives her ordeal.
The human and spirit realms
are headed
toward annihilation,
and it's all your fault.
This is why
humans have no place
interfering in the business
of spirits.
This world is home
to all of us,
and what happens here
is everyone's business.
Thanks to you,
this world may cease to exist!
I only hope
I can track down Vaatu
before it's too late.
Let me help you.
I don't want your help.
Don't interfere with me
again, human!
Let's get moving.
Do you see that, mula?
People.
And they have some kind
of wind power.
More humans!
I found you.
Aah!
Wait! I'm friendly!
Huh?
The legends are true.
Another lion turtle city.
And it's flying.
I have got to get over there.
There.
Okay, mula.
Wish me luck.
Oh, no...
Wow.
Hi, how are you?
I'm Wan.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but it's been a while
since I've seen other humans.
Where did you come from,
stranger?
Another lion turtle city
far away.
For the past two years, I've
been living among the spirits
and exploring the wilds.
Remarkable.
Come. Sit with us.
We would love to hear
of your travels.
Vaatu.
So we meet again, human.
Why is the great spirit
of darkness here
but not his other half?
Uh, I'll explain later.
Leave these people in peace.
They've done nothing
to harm you.
Be gone.
How are you feeling
since our split, Raava?
I've never been better.
When harmonic convergence comes,
I will destroy you forever.
I told you not to interfere.
I had to do something.
These people were in danger.
Great spirit of light,
we thank you for your help.
But how did you become split
from Vaatu?
Ask him.
It wasn't my fault.
Vaatu tricked me
into freeing him.
I'd take it all back
if I could.
It's too late for that.
Now that Vaatu is free,
he is turning
other spirits dark.
The more spirits he turns,
the stronger he becomes.
He's getting bigger,
and you're getting smaller.
As darkness grows, light fades.
I'm sorry for endangering
your village,
but I promise
to set things right.
How?
Great lion turtle,
I ask that you grant me
the power of air
so that I can defeat Vaatu
before it's too late.
You already carry
the power of fire.
No human has ever held
two elements at the same time.
I'm not like other humans.
I can learn to do it.
Hmm, perhaps.
But to do so, Raava
must hold the power for you
until you master it.
Ancient one, why would I
do that for a human?
Especially one who's caused
so much trouble?
Raava, please, I can't let
the world fall into chaos
because of my mistake.
Neither of us
can defeat Vaatu alone,
but together we have a chance.
You may be right.
Very well.
I will help you to master
the power of air.
Thank you.
And in return, I will help you
restore balance to the world.
What's this harmonic thing
Vaatu was talking about?
Harmonic convergence.
That is when Vaatu and I
must battle
for the fate of the world.
How long do we have until then?
About a year in your time.
Then we better start training.
All right,
I'm ready to try air.
How's this gonna work?
The only way for me to give you
the other element is to pass
through your body
and combine our energies.
Great.
So you've done this before.
No. This has never
even been attempted.
It is very dangerous.
That's what they said about
living in the spirit wilds,
and I survived that.
I'm ready.
Give me the air.
It feels completely different.
If you and Vaatu have the same
fight every 10,000 years,
why hasn't one of you
destroyed the other?
He cannot destroy light
any more
than I can destroy darkness.
One cannot exist
without the other.
Even if I defeat Vaatu
in this encounter,
darkness will grow inside me
until he emerges again.
The same will hold true
if Vaatu defeats me.
That doesn't sound so bad.
Even if Vaatu wins,
you'll come back.
Yes, but you will
probably not survive to see it.
Vaatu will destroy the world
as you know it.
Darkness will cover the earth
for 10,000 years.
If I'm gonna help you
battle Vaatu,
then I should visit
more lion turtles.
Why is there so much conflict
between humans and spirits
in the first place?
This physical world
is where humans come from.
Spirits come from
another realm.
At the north and South poles,
the two realms intersect.
Over time,
more and more spirits
have drifted into this world.
Humans have been forced apart,
settling on the lion turtles
who protect them
and losing touch
with each other.
Most people think they live
in the only human city
in the world.
Most humans
think only of themselves,
no matter
how many others are around.
When you pass through me,
I feel an incredible rush
of power.
I feel like I'm changing.
The more we practice,
the stronger I become.
Smells like smoke.
Humans are nearby.
Let's check it out.
A spirit!
Easy there, fellas.
We're friendly.
I can't believe it.
Wan?
Jaya!
What are you doing out here?
Ha ha!
You inspired us.
Once we heard that you survived
out in the wilds,
we decided to try it too.
Where's Yao?
Did he come with you?
Yes, but sadly,
he didn't make it.
We... we lost a lot
of good men along the way.
So why were you protecting
this spirit?
This is Raava.
Don't worry.
She's not like the dark spirits
you've probably run into.
Dark spirits?
What's the difference?
We throw fire at any spirit
we see around here.
Just like they attack any man.
You have no idea
what you're doing!
You're only
making things worse.
The spirits are coming back!
Let's wipe 'em out this time.
We'll burn down
this whole forest if we have to.
What happened to you?
When did you become so violent?
You showed me we could change
the world if we just stopped
being so afraid.
Now we're doing it.
This isn't what I had in mind.
Get out of the forest, humans.
Wait.
We can resolve this peacefully.
Stinky?
You came back.
It's good to see you again.
You and Raava are just in time
to help us
clear these tree-killing
fire-lovers out of here
just like the old days.
You are the one
who's getting cleared out.
There's no need for violence.
I know there must be a way
to work out a compromise.
You have a good heart, stinky.
These fire tossers
aren't like you.
Spirits like him
killed our friends.
I can't let them
get away with that.
We are protectors
of the forest.
We won't let you burn it down.
It's Vaatu.
He's growing stronger,
using their anger
to turn them to his side.
Wipe them out!
Stop, please!
Raava, we need to combine
our energies.
Maybe then we'll have
enough power to stop this.
Enough!
You need to stop fighting now
before you destroy each other.
Stinky, w-what happened?
He's controlling
all four elements.
Wan, I have to leave
your body, or I'll destroy you.
No.
It's working.
If you leave,
the fighting will start again.
Wan!
We have to go back.
Don't bother.
Your human friends
have already been annihilated.
- No!
- Enjoy your final days.
See you at the end
of the world.
- Raava.
- I'm sorry, Wan.
We're almost there.
I was wrong about you, Wan.
I had no idea
that humans were capable
of such nobility and courage.
I'm sorry that we do not have
much more time together.
Let's not give up
before the battle's even begun.
Who knows what will happen?
After all, this is
my first harmonic convergence.
This is the Southern portal
to the spirit world.
Here, Vaatu and I
will do battle once again
at the place
where the two worlds meet.
Are you ready
for our final battle, Raava?
Thanks to our friend
separating us,
I think this time,
I may be rid of you
once and for all.
Before you get to her,
you'll have to go through me.
No human can stand against me.
Haven't you heard the legends?
I'm not a regular human
anymore.
Uhh!
I lived 10,000 lifetimes
before the first of your kind
crawled out of the mud.
Aah!
Oof... oh!
It was I who broke
through the divide
that separated
the plane of spirits
from the material world!
To hate me
is to give me breath.
To fight me
is to give me strength.
Now prepare to face oblivion!
Raava!
The only way to win
is together.
Ah!
Aah!
I have to leave you.
If I stay any longer,
you will die.
It doesn't matter.
If you leave me now,
Vaatu will destroy everything.
We have to finish this
together!
The harmonic convergence
is about to begin.
The era of Raava is over.
Aah!
We are bonded forever.
This is your prison now.
And I will close the portal
so no human will ever be able
to physically enter
the spirit world
and release you.
The spirits must stop
fighting with humans
and return to their home
in the spirit world.
I will teach men
to respect the spirits
so that balance
will be maintained.
I will be the bridge
between our two worlds.
The world is entering
a new age.
Our time protecting mankind
is over.
We will no longer give humans
the power of the elements.
Different groups of people
must learn to live together.
This is my mission...
to use Raava's light spirit
to guide the world
toward peace.
I'm sorry, Raava.
I failed to bring peace.
Even with Vaatu locked away,
darkness still surrounds
humanity.
There wasn't enough time.
Don't worry.
We will be together
for all of your lifetimes.
And we will never give up.
I remember.
Do you know who you are?
My name is Korra.
I'm the Avatar.
We've been raising
this herd of air bison
since the hundred year war.
I never thought I'd be able
to present one to the Avatar.
Thank you
for all your kindness.
I wonder how long
I've been away.
That I cannot say,
but you do not have
much time left.
The harmonic convergence
is only weeks away.
I have to close
the spirit portal
before that happens.
www.tvsubtitles.net