Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
The new air nation is in jeopardy.
In an effort to force
Korra to surrender herself,
Zaheer ambushed the northern air temple.
Tenzin, Bumi and Kya attempted
to hold off the Red Lotus
but were injured in battle.
The airbenders were unable to escape
and everyone was taken captive,
except Kai.
Now Korra and team
Avatar race to the temple,
hoping to mount a rescue.
__
I say we make our approach from the west.
Drop down from the airship on cables.
Ambush these Red Lotus lowlifes
before they know what hit them.
It'll never work.
That combustion lady will
pick us off one by one.
You have a better idea
how to save the airbenders?
Yeah.
We come up from the valley,
scale the side of the mountain,
and take them off guard.
That could work.
And give them the high ground? No.
If their lavabender spots us,
he'll melt the mountainside and us with it.
Wait! I got it.
I'll disguise myself as a lost hiker.
And once I'm in the temple,
I'll distract the Red Lotus
with my bird calls.
Caw! Caw!
That's when you all strike!
Bird calls?
Really?
Well, I haven't noticed you
offering any suggestions.
It doesn't matter.
None of these ideas will work.
The second Zaheer realizes
we're up to something,
he'll wipe out the airbenders.
And Opal is one of those airbenders.
Believe me, I understand what's at stake.
Then I think you'll agree.
The only plan that will work
is for me to give myself up.
What? Korra, no.
We'll figure out another way.
I talked it over with Lord Zuko,
and I've given it a lot of thought.
I have to do this.
You can't expect us to sit by
and just let Zaheer take you.
The world has been out of
balance for far too long.
It needs the air nation back again.
I can't let Zaheer destroy
it and everyone we love.
Help me save the airbenders.
Then you can can worry about saving me.
We're with you, Korra.
Yes, whatever you need.
We're here.
I'll go radio Zaheer.
Zaheer, are you there?
It's me.
I've been waiting for your call.
So do we have a deal? Yes.
You release the airbenders,
and then I'll turn myself over.
And take away the only leverage I have?
No.
I can't do that.
Listen carefully.
Here's what I want you to do.
Will you sit down?
I'm already tense enough as it is!
I'm just worried about Opal.
And Pabu's not here to comfort me.
I hope he and Naga are
doing okay back in Zaofu.
No.
Not Mako's scarf!
Bad dog and ratthingy!
I'm very disappointed in you two.
- Did you speak to Zaheer?
- Yes.
He told me to come to the top
of Laghima's peak at noon. Alone.
Once he has me, he'll release
the airbenders over to you
at the temple.
I think I figured out a way to play this
so the airbenders and Korra
all come out in one piece.
How?
Zaheer doesn't know how
many of us there are.
So we have the numbers advantage.
I say we split into two teams.
Mako, Bolin and Asami will take
the airship up to the temple.
Meanwhile, my metalbenders,
Tonraq, Lin, and I will get
into position below Laghima's peak.
Let go your earthly tether.
Enter the void.
Empty and become wind.
The airbenders are secure.
Thank you, P'Li.
For everything.
Of course.
I want you to know,
not one day went by in that prison
when I didn't think of you.
The years apart only made
my love for you stronger.
And, deep down, I knew you'd
find a way to get me out.
Just like you saved me from becoming
that warlord's killing
machine when I was a girl.
You've shown me what true freedom means.
And, after today,
we'll show the entire world what it means.
No more prisons.
No more running.
I love you, Zaheer.
I love you too.
Radio the second you see those airbenders.
I will, chief.
Good luck.
Be careful, Korra.
You too.
- Korra.
- Don't worry, dad.
I'll be all right.
I just want you to know
how proud I am of you.
The risk you're taking
to save the air nation
will be remembered for generations.
I love you, dad.
I love you too, sweetheart.
And, dad.
Watch out for Zaheer.
He's not very fond of world leaders.
I can handle him.
Just stay focused on your mission.
Oh, man.
Must have been some
fight.
Mako, do you see the airbenders?
Not yet.
We're just arriving.
Don't turn yourself over
until I get a visual on them.
This way.
You want the airbenders or not?
Drop your staff and surrender yourself.
Don't make me come get you.
Mako.
What's going on?
They're here.
But so is the lavabender.
Tell ghazan to let the airbenders go.
Not until you turn yourself over.
This isn't a negotiation.
Wipe them out.
No! Wait!
I'm coming.
Stand down.
And don't bother trying
to metalbend out of these.
They're platinum.
We have her.
It's okay, Tenzin.
We're about to get you out of here.
Korra, it was a trick!
They're not here!
Don't turn yourself over!
We had a deal!
Chief, get Korra out of there now!
Go! Go!
Get the Avatar on the airship.
I'll deal with them.
Nowhere to go, Zaheer!
Where are the airbenders?
I don't know.
Zaheer moved them out of the temple.
Will you just bury them already?
Come on.
We have to get back to the airship!
Not gonna happen! The exit's blocked!
- Where's Oogi?
- Gone.
All the bison got scared
off during the attack.
But I think I know another way out.
Bolin, can you get us through that wall?
On it!
Through there.
Is it just me?
Or is it, uh, getting really warm in here?
Oh, this is not good.
Let's move it, people!
Say hello to the earth queen for me.
Dad!
We're pinned down!
I'm gonna draw her fire.
You take her out.
Lin, no.
I love you.
Come and get me, you thirdeyed freak!
Ooh!
P'Li!
It's over, Zaheer.
Let go your earthly tether.
Release the Avatar!
Enter the void.
This is your last warning!
Empty and become wind.
No! Stop!
Did he just fly?
Guess he doesn't need a ride.
Korra.
We can't outrun it!
This way!
Now what?
Bolin!
Yah!
Incredible.
You're a lavabender.
I know.
I just found out.
Hey, you guys need a lift?
Kai.
You're all right.
More or less.
Everyone hop on.
I owe you my life.
Thank you, Captain.
You can call me Kuvira.
Caw! Caw!
Hey, everybody.
There's something I gotta tell you.
How did you guys make it
out of that temple alive?
It was all Bolin.
I thought we were done for.
Then out of nowhere, he lavabends.
I knew you had the
potential for something big.
You just had to believe in yourself.
You're right.
Being moments from death was
a pretty good motivator too.
Of course, we never would
have made it back without Kai.
Glad I could help. So anyway
did Zaheer get away with Korra?
I'm afraid so.
- Apparently, he can fly now.
- What?
- How?
- Are you sure?
I wouldn't believe it either
if I hadn't seen it for myself.
I've heard the legends about
Guru Laghima's ability to fly.
But I never imagined they were true.
So what's our next move?
I have an idea.
Not right now, kid!
We need to figure out
where Zaheer took Korra.
And find the airbenders.
That's what I've been trying to tell you!
I know where the airbenders are,
and I bet it's where Korra is too!
Well, why didn't you say something?
Where are they? How did you find them?
After I got blasted out of the sky,
I woke up on the side of the Mountain,
where this little fellow found me.
I tried to sneak back into the temple
to see if I could rescue everyone,
and that's when I saw the airship leaving.
I followed it to some
caves a few miles from here.
That giant lady met up with some people
who took the airbenders into the caves.
Was it Ghazan and Minghua?
No, there were four more of them.
Didn't look familiar.
Must be more Red Lotus
members than we thought.
I couldn't fight them all on my own.
So I came back here, hoping
you guys would show up.
We need to get to those caves.
How? I don't think we
can all fit on my bison.
Oogi!
I'm glad to see you too, old friend.
I wanna come with you.
No, Kuvira.
Stay with the injured.
We'll be back for you
once we have the Avatar.
Hey, um, I appreciate
you coming back for us.
Sorry for ever giving you a hard time.
That's okay.
I probably deserved it.
Yeah, you kinda did.
Why didn't you ever tell us you can fly?
I wasn't sure I could.
Only one other airbender
in history had the ability.
How'd you figure out how to do it?
I found true freedom.
I am no longer bound to this
earth by worldly desires.
I have entered the void.
Where's P'Li?
She sacrificed her life for our cause.
Now let's make sure it wasn't in vain.
You...
You killed my father.
I understand your grief.
I also lost someone I loved today.
But your pain will soon be over.
Bring the poison.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net