Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can master
all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Is there any place safe
for the Avatar?
First, President Raiko
banished her from Republic City.
Then the earth queen declared
her an enemy of the kingdom
after Korra rescued a group
of airbenders from Ba Sing Se.
And now Korra
has learned that Zaheer
and his fellow criminals
are after her.
With Tenzin busy bringing
the new recruits
to the northern air temple,
Korra's protection now rests
in Beifong's hands.
_
While you're playing fetch,
four of the most dangerous
criminals in the world
are hunting you down.
We should get moving.
Relax.
We just got here.
Besides, no one knows
where I am right now except us.
I think she wants you
to throw it for her.
I'll pass.
Thanks.
We just got a call on the
radio about another airbender.
Finally.
Where are they?
A city called Zaofu,
the home of the metal clan.
You know the place?
Uh, never been, but
I don't want you going there.
I'd rest a lot easier if you
were back safe in Republic City.
Wow, wow, wow!
An entire city made of metal, whoo!
You should be right at home, Beifong.
Hmm.
Yeah!
- Aren't you coming?
- What's there to see?
It's metal. Big whoop.
Just find the airbender,
and let's get moving.
And don't tell anyone I'm here.
Why not?
I don't need to explain myself to you.
Just do what I say.
Fine. You got it, chief cranky pants.
Avatar Korra, it is an honor to meet you.
My name is Aiwei.
- Thanks for having us.
- Is this everyone?
Yep, just us.
So can I meet the new airbender?
Of course. Right this way.
And this is the air acolyte dining hall,
where everyone eats, and this is Daw.
He's a new airbender too, like you guys.
It's so nice to meet you.
How exciting. New friends.
Excuse me, hello?
My name is Yorru.
I heard this was the place to
come if you're a new airbender.
You got that right, stranger.
Well, a couple of weeks ago,
I woke up, and suddenly, I could do this.
Mom, Aunt Kya, we got another one!
That statue honors the first metalbender,
Toph Beifong, who expanded
the possibilities of what
benders were capable of.
Here, everyone is encouraged
to reach his or her highest potential.
Does Toph live here?
Are we gonna get to meet her?
I'm afraid not.
She used to visit from time to time,
but years ago, she left to wander the world
in search of enlightenment.
No one has seen her since.
Wow, is this where the airbender lives?
Yes, but first,
her mother wants to meet you.
Is this some kind of combat training?
Not exactly.
They are rehearsing for a
dance premiere next month.
That's it for today, everyone.
Allow me to introduce
the matriarch of the metal clan, Suyin.
Please, call me Su.
Great to finally meet you, Avatar Korra.
And this must be Mako, Bolin, and Asami.
You've done your research.
I make it my business to
know who's visiting my city.
So you're a dancer?
Dancer, leader, wife, mother,
collector of rare meteorites.
You'll find people here have
many skills and interests.
Korra, why did you lie
when Aiwei asked if there
was anyone else with you?
What? I-I didn't.
I mean...
How did you know I was lying?
I am a truth seer.
When people lie,
their heart rate and breathing increase.
I can sense the most subtle of changes.
Thanks to Aiwei,
there are no secrets in our city.
We came with Republic
City's chief of police.
She didn't want anyone to know she was here.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Lin's here? Well, I would love to say hello.
Wait, you two know each other?
You're joking, right?
Oh, lin never told you about me.
No. Why would she?
I'm Lin's sister.
I found out why you were
so against coming here.
Why didn't you ever tell
me you had a sister?
Half-sister.
Same mom, different dads.
So what? We're blood, lin.
And after 30 years,
the least you could do is say hello.
I have nothing to say to you.
You two haven't spoken in 30 years...
how come?
Ask her. I've tried.
Oh, don't put that on me.
You're the one who tore our family apart.
And you've done a bang-up
job keeping it that way.
You haven't changed one bit, have you?
Look, we can stand here
arguing about the past all day,
but that's not the reason
the Avatar came here.
My daughter is thrilled to meet you.
Lin, your niece is the new airbender.
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah. Terrific.
Those are my two youngest, Wei and Wing.
They're playing a game called power disc.
They invented it all on their own.
Yah!
Oh, nice power, Wei.
Ha! Wing goes down.
I'm so proud of those two.
Huan,
I want you to meet the Avatar and her friends
and your aunt lin.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey.
Wow, that's a really nice... Banana?
Yes, very, very lifelike.
It's not a banana!
I was inspired by harmonic convergence.
It represents the dawning of a new age,
obviously.
Oh, yeah, no, I c... I can totally see that.
I... wait, let me stand here.
Yes, I can see that now.
Yes. Thank you.
Banana.
I mean, that's a banana, right?
And this is my daughter Opal.
Wow, Avatar Korra.
I can't believe you're really here.
You are so amazing.
It's great to meet you, Opal.
Opal? That's a beautiful name.
- Thanks.
- I'm Bolin.
Opal, but, uh, you already knew that.
Great. We found the airbender.
Let's take her back to the
airship and get out of here.
And the woman apparently
trying to abduct you
is your aunt Lin.
Really? I've always wanted to meet you.
My mom has told me so
many stories about you.
I'm sure she has.
So I've set all of you up in the guesthouses
while Korra trains opal.
Oh, I'm sorry, but I was hoping
she could train with the
rest of the airbenders
at the northern temple.
- That sounds amazing.
- Nonsense.
This is where opal's home and family are.
You can train her here.
I guess I could help her get started.
Absolutely not. We're leaving.
She's just a little worried
because there are a bunch
of crazy criminals after me.
If you're concerned about security,
don't be.
This is the safest city in the world.
Now, I'll see you all at dinner,
and come hungry.
My chef will blow the taste
buds right out of your mouth.
Why do you have such a
problem with your sister?
She seems nice.
Come on, we can stay a little while.
Okay, let's see what you got.
- I'm not very good.
- That's okay.
I've never been a teacher before,
so we're in the same boat.
You wanna keep your elbows in,
torso straight,
feet just skimming the ground.
Why don't you try it with me?
Wow, you're a natural.
You really think so?
Thanks.
You call yourself an airbender?
Disgraceful!
Be the leaf!
But I don't know what that means!
Now that man's a leaf.
The student is only as good as his master.
Great news.
I just got a message from Tenzin.
He's with a whole group of other airbenders
at the northern temple,
and he wants all of you to join them.
We leave first thing in the morning.
And the Avatar is with them?
No,
apparently she had to split off from Tenzin.
That's unfortunate.
I was really looking forward to meeting her.
Tonight, for your dining pleasure,
I present a seared wild Kyoshi elephant koi,
paired with a ginger-infused pea tendril
and hibiscus root salad.
Stunning.
Sorry, dear, I'm going to have
to take dinner in my office.
I just had a major breakthrough
on the tram station remodel.
Well,
don't let me stand in the way of inspiration.
You're the best.
That was my brilliant architect of a husband,
Baatar,
and our oldest son.
He engineers all my husband's projects.
Five kids. What a nightmare.
No, no, my children are a blessing.
Yeah, mom used to say that too,
but she never meant it.
Mmm.
I have to admit, I was pretty skeptical
when he said "pea tendril..."
But this is delicious!
I know, right?
I don't think I've ever
had a bad meal in my life.
Oh, I had plenty
when Mako and I were living on the streets.
I mean, you'd be surprised how
bad food from a dumpster can be.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
No, it's okay, it's okay.
That's all in the past.
Things are great now.
I got to be a pro bender,
fought against a dangerous revolution,
became a mover star,
and now I'm helping the
Avatar rebuild a whole nation.
Wow, your life sounds so exciting.
How's your search for
the new airbenders going?
Honestly, not great.
We had to rescue a whole group
of them from the earth queen.
Oh, she's horrible.
She thinks she can just
do whatever she wants.
- Sounds familiar.
- What?
Nothing.
I mean, the idea of even having a queen
is so outdated... don't you agree, Korra?
I haven't really thought about it too much.
Well, you should start.
The world is evolving, and the earth queen
can evolve with it or step aside.
Hey, everyone,
my little sister is an
expert on world affairs now.
You wanna talk about
what's really bugging you?
Because I'm right here.
Sorry we're late, everyone.
Varrick!
- What are you doing here?
- Great question, Asami.
I mean, what are any of us doing here?
Wow. Food for thought.
Anyhoo, how's our company doing?
You mean my company?
Future industries reverted back to me
after you plotted to abduct the president.
Allegedly plotted to abduct the president.
Never convicted.
Uh, that's because you escaped prison.
No, the universe decided to set me free.
So I looked up my old friend Suyin here,
pitched her a few ideas, and bam!
We're in business together.
Varrick's heading up my
new technology division.
I've seen the future,
and the future is magnets!
I'm working on a high-speed rail
that'll revolutionize transportation
and shipping as we know it.
But that's not all! I'm...
all right, enough!
I'm trying to keep the Avatar safe,
and you're harboring a criminal?
Ease up, lin.
Sure,
Varrick's made a few mistakes in his past,
but that doesn't mean he should
pay for it the rest of his life.
My chef was a pirate,
but now he's a culinary master.
People change.
You haven't.
Lin!
So you and opal seemed
to hit it off at dinner.
I think she's really into you.
Yeah, you know,
she's sweet and pretty and super nice.
Too bad she's not my type.
Right, I forgot.
Your type is dumb mover
star or psycho ice princess.
You know, that hurts a little bit.
Right... Here.
But maybe you're right, bro.
Maybe opal is Bolin material.
Thanks. Yeah!
You know, before I built this city,
there was nothing here.
I wanted to make my mark on the world.
It's amazing.
Thank you for being so welcoming,
and I'm sorry for how Lin's been acting.
Can I ask, what happened with you two?
It's complicated.
We didn't have a normal childhood.
Neither of us knew our fathers,
and Toph was always busy
being chief of police.
Because mom grew up in such a strict house,
she gave us all the freedom in the world,
hoping we'd figure out our own paths.
That sounds like a good thing.
And in a way, it was.
But we both ended up
fighting for mom's attention.
Lin followed in her
footsteps and became a cop.
I was more of a rebel.
Mom wasn't too happy with
how either of us turned out.
When I was 16,
I left home to explore the world.
I sailed the seas on a pirate ship,
joined a traveling circus for while,
and lived in a sandbender
commune in the desert.
It took me a while, but I finally realized
what I was looking for was a family.
So I bought this plot of land,
found a brilliant architect
who later became my husband,
and created a place I could truly call home.
It sounds like you've created
the perfect life here.
Almost.
I've always wanted lin to be a part of it,
but I gave up hope long ago
of her ever coming around.
Hey, little lady.
Wow, you're really blowing
me away with your airbending.
Why are you acting weird?
I don't like how you're talking to me.
Look, I'm sorry.
I just get really self-conscious
when I know a girl likes me,
and I end up acting stupid.
Who said I liked you?
Oh, no! But I thought... Mako said...
just kidding.
But do me a favor and stop trying.
Well, don't stop trying.
Just stop trying so much. Just be yourself.
Huh, be myself.
Yeah, I guess I could give that a shot.
Oh, hey, Korra.
Can I steal you away
from Bolin for a minute?
I need your help with something.
"Let go your earthly tether.
"Enter the void.
Empty and become wind."
What are you doing?
No one's allowed in
daddy's study except daddy.
I'm sorry. I couldn't sleep.
What were you reading?
A poem by Guru Laghima,
the wisest airbender who ever lived.
Ikki, you should be in bed.
Come on.
- Night.
- Good night.
You seem to know a lot
about airbender history
for someone who just got airbending.
I've always admired the culture.
And you moved through
those gates like a natural.
Where did you say you were from?
A small village up north.
You've probably never heard of it.
Wait.
Zaheer!
I need some help!
Hold it right there!
Sorry I won't be joining you
at the northern air temple.
I'm afraid I have other plans.
Who is it?
Hey, it's me.
I brought someone who wants to talk to you.
You wanna talk, then talk.
I'm sorry being here has
been so hard for you.
When you showed up,
I was so excited to get to know you.
I'd heard so many great things about you
from mom and grandma Toph.
So I guess I was kind of sad
that you didn't wanna get to know me.
Believe me,
I know my family can be a little crazy
and overwhelming sometimes,
but I would love it so much
if you would be a part of it.
Get out.
Sorry. Did I say something wrong?
Get out!
What's your problem?
Don't get mad at Opal.
I asked her to talk to you
because I thought it would help you
snap out of whatever funk you're in,
but I guess I was wrong.
Why don't you focus on fixing the world
and stop trying to fix my family?
Su's right. You're never gonna change.
You're always gonna be a bitter,
lonely woman.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net