Water
Earth
Fire
Air
Long ago,the four nations lived together in harmony
then everything changed when the firenation attacked
Only the avatar mastered all four elements could stop them
but when the world needed him most he vanished
100 years passed, my brother and I discovered the new avatar
airbinder named Aang
And although his airbinding skill is great,
he has a lot to learn before he is ready to save anyone.
but I believe...
...Aang can save the world
-=AVATAR=-
The last airbender
Translation from www.avatarspirit.net
Sub: Tucity
Previously on
Avatar...
If I want to catch my prey, I must be agile....nimble.
I need a small, elite team.
Even though I was born blind, I've never had a problem seeing.
I see with earthbending.
You're gonna be a great teacher, Toph.
I thought a lot about what you said
you did?
good, good
we no longer have anything to gain by traveling
I need to find my own way.
Book two: Earth
Chapter eight: The Chase
Hey, you guys picked a great campsite.
The grass is so soft.
That's not grass. Appa's shedding.
Oh, gross!
That's not gross; it's just a part of spring. You know,
rebirth, flowers blooming, and Appa gets a new coat!
Ah, the beauty of spring.
Stop, Appa, stop!
It's not that bad, Katara. It makes a great wig!
And a great beard!
I'm just glad we finally have another girl in the group because you two are disgusting.
Excuse me, does anyone have a razor? ...because I've got some hairy pits!
So, Toph, usually when setting up camp we try to divide up the work.
Hey, don't worry about me, I'm good to go.
Well, actually, what I'm trying to say is, uh,
some of us might fetch water while someone else might set up the fire pit...
... or put up the tent.
Even Momo does his fair share.
Katara, I'm fine. I can carry my own weight.
I don't need a fire, I've already collected my own food, and look.
My tent's all set up.
Well, that's great for you, but we still need to finish...
I don't understand. What's the problem here?
Never mind.
Sorry
Hey Toph, I wanted to apologize for earlier.
I think we're all just a little tired and getting on each others' nerves.
Yeah, you do seem pretty tired.
I meant all of us.
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight.
There's something coming toward us!
What is it?
It feels like an avalanche...
But also not like an avalanche.
Your powers of perception are frightening.
Should we leave?
Better safe than sorry.
What is that thing?
Ahh, land, sweet land!
See you guys in the morning!
Actually, can you help us unload?
Really? You need me to help unload Sokka's funky-smelling sleeping bag?
Well, yeah.
That and everything else.
You're a part of our team now and...
Look. I didn't ask you to help unload my stuff.
I'm carrying my own weight.
That's not the point.
Ever since joining us you've been nothing but selfish and unhelpful.
What?
Look here,
sugar queen,  I gave up everything I had so that I could teach Aang earthbending,
so don't you talk to me about being selfish!
Sugar Queen!?
D-Did you just slam the door in my face!?
How can you be so infuriating!?
Should we...do something?
Hey, I'm just enjoying the show.
Okay, okay, you both need to calm down.
Both?  I'm completely calm!
I... can see that.
The stars sure are beautiful tonight. Too bad you can't see them, Toph!
Hey, how is a guy supposed to sleep with all this yelling and earthquaking!?
That thing is back!
Well, how far away is it? Maybe we can close our eyes just for a few minutes.
I don't think so, Sokka.
Seriously, what is that thing?
And how does it keep finding us?
I don't know, but this time I'm going to make sure we lose 'em.
Okay, forget about setting up camp.
I'm finding the softest pile of dirt and going to sleep.
That's good, because Toph wasn't going to help anyway.
Oh, I didn't realize baby still need someone to tuck her in bed.
Come on guys, there's something after us and we don't even know what or who it is.
It could be Zuko. We haven't seen him since the North Pole.
Who's Zuko?
Oh, just some angry freak with a ponytail who's tracked us all over the world.
What's wrong with ponytails, ponytail?
This is a warrior's wolf tail.
Well, it certainly tells the other warriors that you're fun and perky!
Anyway, whoever's chasing us, they couldn't have followed us here. So... now would everyone...
just...sshhh!
No, Momo, ssh! Sleepy time.
Aww, don't tell me?
That's impossible.
There's no way they could have tracked us.
I can feel it with my own two feet!
Let's get out of here!
Maybe we should face them.
Find out who they are. Who knows, maybe they're friendly.
Always the optimist.
It's those three girls from Omashu!
We can take 'em. Three on three.
Actually, Toph, there's four of us.
Oh. I'm sorry, I didn't count you. You know, no bending and all.
I can still fight!
Okay. Three on three plus Sokka.
Well, we wanted to find out who they were. We found out. Now let's get out of here.
Appa, yip yip!
I can't believe those girls followed us all the way from Omashu.
I still think we could've taken them.
Are you kidding me?
The crazy blue firebending and the flying daggers are bad enough,
but last time we saw them one of those girls did something that took my bending away.
That's scary.
Oh no, the sun is rising! We've been up all night with no sleep.
Sokka, we'll be okay.
Are you sure!? I've never not slept before!
What if I fall asleep now and something happens? And something always happens!
Every time we land, those girls are there,
so we'll just have to keep flying.
We can't keep flying forever.
So, what's the plan?
Don't know...too tired to think.
I'm sure we'll come up with something after a short nap.
Yes!
Sleep!
What's going on!?
Appa fell asleep!
Wake up buddy!
Appa's exhausted.
Okay, we've put a lot of distance between us and them.
The plan now is to follow Appa's lead and get some sleep.
Of course, we could have gotten some sleep earlier  if Toph didn't have such issues.
What?
Alright, alright! Everyone's exhausted. Let's just get some rest.
No! I want to hear what Katara has to say.
You think I have issues?
I'm just saying, maybe if you helped out earlier we could've set up our camp faster...
and gotten some sleep and then maybe we wouldn't be in this situation!
You're blaming me for this!?
No, no! She's not blaming you!
No, I'm blaming her!
hey, I never asked you for diddly doo da. I carry my own weight!
Besides, if there's anyone to blame, it's sheddy over here!
What? You're blaming Appa?
Yeah! You wanna know how they keep finding us? He's leaving a trail everywhere we go!
How dare you blame Appa!?
He saved your life three times today!
If there's anyone to blame, it's you!
You're always talking about how you carry your own weight, but you're not! He is!
Appa's carrying your weight! He never had a problem flying when it was just the three of us!
I'm outta here.
Wait
What did I just do!? I can't believe I yelled at my earthbending teacher.
Now she's gone.
I know.
We're all just trying to get used to each other,
and I was so mean to her.
Yeah, you two were pretty much jerks.
Thanks, Sokka.
No problem.
We need to find Toph and apologize.
Okay, but what are we going to do about the tank full of dangerous ladies chasing us?
I have a plan.
Toph was right. Appa's fur was leaving a trail right to us.
But now that he's clean, no more trail!
Are you sure that he's okay to fly?
He'll be fine as long as we leave his saddle and all our stuff here.
I'm going to use Appa's fur to make a fake trail and lead the tank off course.
Ohhh? That really hurt my tailbone.
Wads of wet fur.
How delightful.
Hmm? They're not wads, more like... bundles.
Or bunches? It's got an "uh" sound.
Clumps?
Clumps! They're clumps!
The trail goes this way.
The Avatar is trying to give us the slip. You two head in that direction and keep your eye out for the bison.
I'll follow this trail.
Toph couldn't have made it too far.
What is it Momo?
oh no, katara
How did they find us?
Appa, come on! We need to go faster!
He's too tired!
Not good, not good!
We just need to make it across that river!
oh, no, Appa, just a little further!
We made it!
We're safe!
You did it, Appa!
Good try, but no.
How ya doing?
Well, you know!
I thought when Ty Lee and I finally caught you guys ...it would be more exciting.
Oh well, victory is boring.
Thanks Appa. I don't know what we'd do without you.
Was it just me, or was that guy kinda cute?
Alright, you've caught up with me. Now who are you and what do you want?
You mean you haven't guessed? You don't see the family resemblance?
Here's a hint.
I must find the Avatar to restore my honor.
It's okay. You can laugh. It's funny.
So what now?
now?
Now it's over. You're tired and you have no place to go.
You can run, but I'll catch you.
I'm not running.
Here is your tea.
You seem a little too young to be traveling alone.
You seem a little too old.
Perhaps I am.
I know what you're thinking. I look like I can't handle being by myself.
I wasn't thinking that.
You wouldn't even let me pour my own cup of tea.
I poured your tea because I wanted to and ...
... for no other reason.
People see me and think I'm weak.
They want to take care of me. But I can take care of myself by myself.
You sound like my nephew.
Always thinking you need to do things on your own without anyone's support.
There is nothing wrong with letting people who love you help you.
Not that I love you; I just met you.
So, where is your nephew?
I've been tracking him, actually.
Is he lost?
Yes, a little bit.
His life has recently changed and he's going through very difficult times.
He is trying to figure out who he is ...
...and he went away.
So... now you're following him.
I know he doesn't want me around right now,
but, if he needs me, I'll be there.
Your nephew is very lucky,
even if he doesn't know it.
Thank you.
My pleasure. Sharing tea with a fascinating stranger is one of life's true delights.
No, thank you for what you said.
It helped me.
I'm glad.
Oh, and about your nephew? Maybe you should tell him that you need him too.
Do you really want to fight me?
Yes, I really do.
Zuko
I was wondering when you'd show up, Zuzu.
Zuzu?
Back off, Azula! He's mine!
I'm not going anywhere.
Katara
Uncle?
Get up!
I thought you guys could use a little help.
Thanks.
Well, look at this. Enemies and traitors all working together.
I'm done.I know when I'm beaten.
You got me.
A princess surrenders with honor.
Get away from us!
Zuko, I can help!
Leave!
-=To be Continued=-
Translation from www.avatarspirit.net
Sub: Tucity