Water
Earth
Fire
Air
Long ago,the four nations lived together in harmony
then everything changed when the fire nation attacked
Only the avatar mastered all four elements could stop them
but when the world needed him most he vanished
100 years passed, my brother and I discovered the new avatar
an airbender named Aang
And although his airbending skill is great,
he has a lot to learn before he is ready to save anyone.
but I believe...
...Aang can save the world
Previously on
Avatar...
The Avatar has kidnapped my daughter.
I want you to do whatever it takes to bring her home.
Sandbenders! Shoo! Away from the bison!
Library's sinking!
No!
I'm sorry Appa.
Where's Appa?
Book Two: Earth
Chapter Eleven: The Desert
How could you let them take Appa? Why didn't you stop them?
I couldn't! The library was sinking! You guys were still inside and...
You could have come to get us! I could have saved him!
I can hardly feel any vibrations out here.
The sandbenders snuck up on me and there wasn't time for...
You just didn't care! You never liked Appa! You wanted him gone!
Aang, stop it. You know Toph did all she could. She saved our lives.
Who's going to save our lives now? We'll never make it out of here.
That's all any of you guys care about yourselves!
You don't care whether Appa is okay or not!
We're all concerned, but we can't afford to be fighting now.
I'm going after Appa.
Aang, wait!
We'd better start walking. We're the only people who know about the solar eclipse.
We have to get that information to Ba Sing Se.
You think if we dig out the giant owl, he'll give us a ride?
Maybe we should make camp.
No, please, don't stop just for me!
What now?
Colonel Mongke! What a pleasant surprise!
If you're surprised we're here then the Dragon of the West has lost a few steps.
You know these guys?
Sure. Colonel Mongke and the Rough Riders are legendary.
Each one is a different kind of weapons specialist.
They are also a very capable singing group.
We're not here to give a concert. We're here to apprehend fugitives!
Would you like some tea first? I'd love some. How about you, Kachi?
I make you as a jasmine man. Am I right?
Enough stalling! Round 'em up!
It's nice to see old friends.
Too bad you don't have any old friends that don't want to attack you.
Hmm... Old friends that don't want to attack me...
Can't you watch where you're...
No.
Right. Sorry.
Come on guys, we've got to stick together.
If I sweat any more, I don't think sticking together will be a problem.
Katara, can I have some water?
Okay, but we've got to try to conserve it.
We're drinking your bending water?
You used this on the swamp guy!
It does taste swampy.
I'm sorry, it's all we have.
Not anymore! Look!
Sokka, wait! You shouldn't be eating strange plants!
There's water trapped inside these!
I don't know...
Suit yourself. It's very thirst-quenching, though.
Drink cactus juice.
It'll quench ya! Nothing's quenchier.
It's the quenchiest!
Okay, I think you've had enough.
Who lit Toph on fire?
Can I get some of that cactus?
I don't think that's a good idea. Come on, we need to find Aang.
How did we get out here in the middle of the ocean?
Uhhh...
Appa!
No...
No!
What is that?
What? What is what?
It's a giant mushroom!
Maybe it's friendly!
Let's just keep moving. I hope Aang's okay...
Friendly mushroom! Mushy giant friend!
Yeah, a little barefoot blind girl and her friends passed through here a few days ago.
Did they give you any indication where they were headed?
Maybe you could give me a little incentive?
You suggesting I break your fingers?
They went in the desert! Too bad there's almost no chance they survived.
That's okay, since she's wanted dead or alive.
No she's not! I'm certain her father wants her alive.
Hey, look... Fire Nation wanted posters!
So?
So, look who's here.
I'm sorry, Aang. I know it's hard for you right now,...
...but we need to focus on getting out of here.
What's the difference?
We won't survive without Appa.
We all know it.
Come on, Aang! We can do this if we work together.
Right Toph?
As far as I can feel, we're trapped in a giant bowl of sand pudding.
I got nothin'.
Sokka? Any ideas how to find Ba Sing Se?
Why don't we ask the circle birds?
Ugh... We're getting out of this desert, and we're going to do it together!
Aang, get up. Everybody hold hands. We can do this.
We have to.
I think we should stop for the night.
Is there any more water?
This is the last of it. Everyone can have a little drink.
Momo, no! You've killed us all!
No, he hasn't.
Oh, right. Bending.
Sokka, let me see the things you got from the library.
What!? I didn't steal anything! Who told you that?
It was you! You ratted me out!
Sokka, I was there.
It doesn't matter. None of those will tell us where Appa is.
No, but we can find out which way Ba Sing Se is.
We can use the stars to guide us.
That way we can travel at night when it's cool and rest during the day.
Just try to get some sleep. We'll start again in a few hours.
No one here is going to help us. These people just look like filthy wanderers.
So do we.
Ah, this is interesting.
I think I've found our friend.
You brought us here to gamble on Pai Sho?
I don't think this is a gamble.
Let's take them now!
This place is full of desperate characters.
If they find out we're collecting a bounty,...
...we might have to fight them all just to keep our prize. Patience.
May I have this game?
The guest has the first move.
I see you favor the white lotus gambit.
Not many still cling to the ancient ways.
Those who do can always find a friend.
Then let us play.
Welcome, brother. The White Lotus opens wide to those who know her secrets.
What are you old gasbags talking about?
I always tried to tell you that Pai Sho is more than just a game.
I'm not waiting all night for these geezers to finish yapping!
It's over! You two fugitives are coming with me!
I knew it! You two are wanted criminals with a giant bounty on your heads!
I thought you said he would help!
He is. Just watch.
You think you're going to capture them and collect all that gold?
Gold?
Uh... Maybe we shouldn't.
Come on, get up. We need to go.
Yesterday my mouth tasted like mud. Now it just tastes like sand.
I never thought I'd miss the taste of mud so much.
I'm awake. I couldn't sleep.
Well, we need to get moving if we want to get out of this sand pit.
Appa!
Appa? But why would Princess Yue need him?
She's the moon! She flies by herself!
It's just a cloud.
Wait! A cloud!
Here, fly up and bend the water from that cloud into my pouch.
Wow... there's hardly any in here.
I'm sorry, okay! It's a desert cloud. I did all I could!
What's anyone else doing! What are you doing?
Trying to keep everyone together. Let's just get moving.
We need to head in this direction.
Ow! Crud! I am so sick of not feeling where I'm going!
And what idiot buried a boat in the middle of the desert?
A boat?
Believe me, I kicked it hard enough to feel plenty of vibrations.
It's one of the gliders the sandbenders use!
And look! It's got some kind of compass on it!
I bet it can point us out of here!
Aang, you can bend a breeze so we can sail it. We're going to make it!
It is an honor to welcome such a high-ranking member...
...of the Order of the White Lotus.
Being a Grand Master, you must know so many secrets.
Now that you played Pai Sho, are you going to do some flower arranging,...
...or is this club going to offer some real help?
You must forgive my nephew.
He is not an initiate and has little appreciation for the cryptic arts.
Who knocks at the guarded gate?
One who has eaten the fruit and tasted its mysteries.
I'm afraid it's members only. Wait out here.
The needle on this compass doesn't seem to be pointing north according to my charts.
Take it easy little lady.
I'm sure the sand folks who built this baby know how to get around here.
That's what the compass is pointing to! That giant rock!
It must be the magnetic center of the desert.
A rock? Yes! Let's go!
Maybe we can find some water there!
Maybe we can find some sandbenders.
Ahhh... Finally! Solid ground!
I think my head is starting to clear out the cactus juice. And look!
This tastes like rotten penguin meat!
Awww I feel woozy.
You've been hallucinating on cactus juice all day and then...
...you just lick something you find stuck to the wall of a cave?
I have a natural curiosity.
I don't think this is a normal cave. This was carved by something.
Yeah... look at the shape.
There's something buzzing in here. Something that's coming for us!
What are you doing? That rock almost crushed me!
Sorry, I can't tell where they are in the air!
I got this one.
Sokka, there's nothing there.
I guess my head's not as clear as I thought.
We have to get out of here! I'm completely out of water to bend!
Momo!
I'm not losing anyone else out here.
Come on, we're going down.
Toph, shoot a rock right there.
Fire!
Yeah! You got it! She got it, right?
Yes. Now let's move.
On your left!
What's going on? Is the club meeting over?
Everything is taken care of. We're heading to Ba Sing Se.
Ba Sing Se? Why would we go to the Earth Kingdom capital?
The city is filled with refugees. No one will notice two more.
We can hide in plain sight there.
And it's the safest place in the world from the Fire Nation.
Even I couldn't break through to the city.
I have the passports for our guests,...
...but there are two men out on the streets looking for them.
You seen these guys?
What are you doing in our land with a sandbender sailer?
From the looks of it, you stole it from the Hami tribe.
We found the sailer abandoned in the desert.
We're traveling with the Avatar.
Our bison was stolen and we have to get to Ba Sing Se.
You dare accuse our people of theft while you ride in on a stolen sand sailer?
Quiet, Gashuin. No one accused our people of anything.
If what they say is true, we must give them hospitality.
Sorry, father.
I recognize the son's voice. He's the one that stole Appa.
Are you sure?
I never forget a voice.
You stole Appa! Where is he? What did you do to him?
They're lying! They're the thieves!
Where is my bison?
Hey you, where are these men?
I got a tip that they're in your shop.
As you can see, no one is here but us.
We know all about your secret back room.
Kick it down.
Hey! That room is for flowers only!
Some unlucky soul has an incomplete Pai Sho set.
Let's go back to finding the girl.
You tell me where he is now!
What did you do?
I... It wasn't me!
You said to put a muzzle on him!
You muzzled Appa?
I'm sorry! I didn't know that it belonged to the Avatar!
Tell me where Appa is!
I traded him! To some merchants! He's probably in Ba Sing Se by now!
They were going to sell him there!
Please! We'll escort you out of the desert! We'll help however we can!
Just get out of here! Run!
Subtitle by rendy1287 [at gmail dot com]
Sync by Osimon [at gmail dot com]
Thanks to Psycho Silver for The Transcript.
http://www.avatarspiritmedia.net/
www.tvsubtitles.net