Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all four elements
...
And bring balance to the world.
Republic City became
a war zone.
While Prince
saved the remaining citizens
The Avatar team fighting
the mecca giant.
But no dominant
the tips.
In the latest attempt,
Asami and her father
They used their costumes mecca-
to cut platinum.
Hiroshi helped Avatar
team to infiltrate the mecca giant,
But he paid a very high price.
This victory will strengthen
our heroes?
BALANCE BOOK 4 CHAPTER 11
"The FINAL CONFRONTATION"
Initiate the lock.
Find the Avatar
and who else is with her.
We need to act quickly.
Su Lin, rise to the arm
try and disable the gun.
Mako, Bolin,
go to the engine
And try to turn off the power.
- I behind Kuvira.
- Are you sure?
- When you fought with her before...
- I know.
It almost destroyed me.
Not this time.
I will deal with this lever.
With each other.
I treat this type.
Disable the gun.
- Good job.
- The outside is of platinum
But we can cause a lot of damage here.
The loading system is not operating.
- We are unable to shoot.
- It is not malfunction.
I'm someone to bend the metal
within arm.
I lost the connection.
The gun became useless.
- I'm ready!
- I'll be with you in a second.
I'm a busy little.
Okay, I'm ready!
1.
2.
!
- There is nothing happening.
- Something must have overloaded
And taken control!
There has to be another way
turn off the power here.
What's the matter.
You spent a lot of time
Working with Varrick
and the Baatar Jr.
Not learned anything
about robots?
The only thing I know these vines
,
Is that a lot
mexeres with them explode.
Take the engineers here.
I have an idea.
- Would you tell me?
- I'll mess with these vines
- With electricity.
- Let's recap, okay?
Said that this can make the vines
explode.
Exactly.
It is the only way to bring down this thing.
- I stand.
- No, I do not Aguentas.
This is not the time to prove it
how amazing you are.
I know how amazing you are.
- You're awesome.
- I do not have time to argue.
I'll do it,
so out of here.
Okay.
But for the record,
not approve.
Sai
as soon as you can.
Promise?
I promise.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
Now go!
Over.
You'll call your army
and surrender yourself to the President Raiko.
So you...
Stop!
Kuvira! Give it up!
Never.
Please
stop this madness.
This has to end now!
If you really want to end up with this
,
Then walks catch me!
- It's over now.
- No!
Turn it off!
I can not!
Look.
A new Spiritual Portal.
Spread out and find the Kuvira.
Korra!
Tenzin,
no sign of her.
Keep looking.
Korra!
What happened?
We are...
Dead?
No. We're fine.
But we are in the spirit world.
All the energy of the gun
created a new portal
And brought us here.
Why do you saved
life?
After all
what I did with you.
I think I see a lot of me
in you.
- We're nothing alike.
- Yes we are.
We both are fierce
and determined to succeed,
Sometimes without thinking correctly.
That was not what he had planned.
If you had thee surrendered,
none of this would have happened.
Have caused it to yourself.
Stir with vines,
act as a dictator of your people...
You had to know that what
were doing was wrong.
I was trying to help
my people.
Su turned away
to the Earth Kingdom.
You disappeared.
I had to do something.
I think I get it.
I do not understand anything about me
.
I see.
Su told me how you hosted
when you were young.
It must be so difficult
be orphaned.
Do not pretend you know
how I felt.
The Avatar is worshiped by millions
!
I set aside
by my own parents
Meant nothing to them!
How could stay without doing anything
And see the same happen
with my nation
When needed someone to command it?
You wanted to create a place
where you and your people
Never feel vulnerable
again.
I may not be an orphan,
but believe me,
I understand what is fear.
After being poisoned,
Would have done anything to feel in control.
The spirits returned.
And also  Korra.
You all right!
Unleash Kuvira,
or attack.
Step back.
This battle is over.
I owe my life to Avatar.
Her power is beyond anything
I can hope to get
.
I will accept any punishment
that the world deems just.
And Su, I am very sorry for all the trouble
I'm
caused to you and your family.
You'll answer for everything you've done.
And although the battle has caused a lot of damage
In our beloved city...
Through destruction,
love flourished.
So that's why,
dear friends and family
We gather today to celebrate the wonderful
And sometimes
the inexplicable bond
Between Mr. Varrick
and Mrs. Zhu Li!
Hey, mate.
Foca me.
This is my big day!
True love is a fickle creature.
Hard to find,
Almost impossible to tame,
But Varrick
and Zhu Li proven
That even with such huge differences,
There may be circumstances
to be happy together.
Now for the votes!
Thank you, Pabu master.
You, Lord
Iknik Blackstone Varrick,
Of the Southern Water Tribe,
master of the high seas,
Accepts Ms. Zhu Li Moon
as his lawful wife?
Promises to treat it not as his assistant,
But as its
honored and beloved partner?
Yes, of course I accepted!
And you, Zhu Li,
accepts Varrick
As your lawfully wedded husband?
Promises to take care of him in sickness and in health,
And...
And you rub the calluses
With exfoliating weekly
which is not very...
I will not read it all.
I accept Varrick.
With the calluses and everything else.
And now...
Do the thing.
You all right?
You make me so happy,
curse.
My cousin told me
as you kept your cool
Throughout the evacuation.
I have to admit, I'm impressed
.
I think you'll be
a great leader,
But that does not mean
I'll help you with Korra,
- So not the parts.
- Okay, Mako.
Sometimes good extraction
is the only reward.
It's good to see you, Prince Wu.
Or should I say King Wu?
Are you ready to go back
to Ba Sing Se and take the throne?
Yeah, about that...
I've been thinking lately
to leave the post of King
And get rid of the monarchy
completely.
Are you kidding?
For the first time,
I'm not.
Now, I know you will say I'm lazy
,
I'm afraid
have responsibilities
I put my career ahead of
people...
But that's not it.
I really think that the Earth Kingdom
Will be better if the states are independent
And its leaders are elected,
as in the United Republic.
That's really very wise and mature
coming from you.
I think it's a great idea.
The Earth Kingdom
must evolve
And I will do everything to help you
to make it happen.
I look forward to working with you
,
But for now,
the dance floor call me.
- How's your arm?
- Much better.
The word "thank you" is not enough
For what you did.
But honestly,
I do not know what else to say.
I do not have to say anything.
I want you to know that I will follow you in any battle
,
No matter how crazy things get
.
I went to your building,
and always will be.
I spoke with President Raiko.
Tomorrow, he will announce
the expansion plan of the city
Rather than rebuild it.
I bet Aang
never imagined that there could be a Portal
Right in the heart of
Republic City.
Korra, have transformed
over the world in a few years,
Than most of the Avatars
during their lives.
But I feel that just started.
There's so much I want to learn
and do.
You do not know how glad
Heard you
so full of hope again.
It has been a journey full of
hurts, does not it?
I realized that life is full of sorrow.
I know I sank deeply
after being poisoned,
But finally I understood why, because
had to go through all this.
Needed
understand what it meant to suffer,
So I could have
more compassionate with others.
Even with people
as Kuvira.
Excuse Tenzin.
The Varrick is looking for you.
Something about borrowing a glider fact
- To fly around the tower.
- This does not seem a good idea.
Want to sit with me
for a moment?
I'm not ready
to return to the party.
I do not think apologized real
.
- Of what?
- Having gone for so long.
Why not have come back
earlier.
You do not have to forgive you anything.
I'm so glad that
're here now.
I do not know if I could deal
if I lost you and my father
The same day.
I'm sorry for what happened.
Thank you.
I'm glad to have been able
to forgive him.
So, now what?
Returned to the dance floor?
I have no great desire
dancing.
Honestly, after all
what happened in recent months
I felt like having a vacation.
Let's do it.
Let's enjoy a vacation, just the two
.
Where do you want.
Really?
It's ok.
I always wanted to see how
the spiritual world.
Sounds perfect.
END
Translation En United4ever and MundoAvatar
pTpT Adaptation - Arodri
Sync: NeoStar
www.tvsubtitles.net