Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the avatar can
master all four elements,
and bring balance to the world.
Sync and corrections by:kDragon
www.Addic7ed.com
Book four, chapter one Original
air date 03/10
Welcome to Republic City,
the place of hopes, dreams,
and spirit wilds.
This Metropolis truly has
something for everyone.
Visit Air Temple Island,
the hub for all air benders
as they travel the world helping others.
Or take a stroll through
beautiful Avatar Korra Park,
named in honor of you-know-who.
We've missed her these past
three years and we can't wait
to welcome her home.
Get well soon, Korra.
And of course you'll want to
see our most unique attractions,
the spirit wilds.
Here spirits and people
live harmoniously together,
like this old codger and his new pals.
Yes sirree, this town is
truly on the up and up.
Come be a part of the
action in Republic City.
And of course, my biggest
thanks goes to Asami Sato
and future industries.
She brought our old central
terminal into the modern era.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
world is entering a new age
of peace and prosperity.
Soon, Prince Wu will
take his rightful place
on the Earth Kingdom throne,
and thanks to our updated rail system,
Republic City and the Earth Kingdom
will be united like never before.
Hey there, Asami right?
Great train house.
Maybe you can give me a
personal tour sometime,
what do you say?
I do like the idea of
putting you on a train
and sending you far, far away.
That's... that's funny.
I like funny dames.
Maybe I should introduce myself,
I'm Prince Wu, future king.
Yeah... I'm aware of who you are.
Don't let my reputation intimidate you.
I'm still human just like everyone else,
only more human, like extra-human,
or, hmm, super-human.
Super-human?
So, what do you say?
Can I show you a low-key night out
with a super-human soon to be king?
Prince Wu, President Reiko
has some really important
king stuff to talk to you about.
Now? Fine.
Think over the offer, I'll be back.
He's a real charmer, huh?
He's... something.
How can you stand being his bodyguard?
Well, I just remind myself
that once he's on the throne,
I go back to being a detective.
- And that works?
- I also go home
and smash my head into
the wall for an hour.
You know, just to get the stress out.
It's good to see you,
Mako. It's been too long.
You hear from Bolin lately?
I haven't talked to him for a while,
but he's coming in a few
days for the coronation.
And Bei Fong told me that
Korra is getting in tonight.
I can't wait to see her.
It's gonna be weird
having the old team avatar
back in the city after all these years.
After your coronation the united forces
will escort you to Ba Sing Se.
Right, about that.
Are we all positive that the Earth Kingdom
is safe enough for me to return?
I don't have to remind
everyone what happened
to my great aunt three years ago?
May she rest in peace.
Prince Wu, I assure you
Kuvira has the Earth Kingdom
pretty much stabilized at this point.
Define: "pretty much. "
Well, the roving bandits
have mostly been dispersed.
Mostly?
Don't worry kid.
The chances of you being
assassinated are almost zero.
Almost?
Get out of here.
We don't have anything left.
Now, you don't have anything left.
It's safe to come out everyone,
the airbenders are here.
You finally made it.
So, where are the rest of you?
Actually, it's just the two of us,
but we're going to do
everything we can to help.
I'm Opal, and this is Kai
- it's nice to meet you.
- What?
I called Master Tenzin
because my state has been
under siege by bandits for months.
They blocked all the roads,
cut off our supply lines,
and all he sent is you two kids?
Hey, us two kids
just took care of those three guys for you.
There are hundreds more
where they came from.
My citizens are going hungry.
Our entire state is on
the brink of collapse.
Unfortunately, the air nation is
spread thin right now.
We're all you have.
We just got some good news.
Two more Earth Kingdom
states have agreed to join us.
Excellent. Thank you, Bolin.
We're 90% there, Kuvira.
That's great!
Julie, dish out some of
that special celebration tea.
None for me.
I won't celebrate until the Earth Kingdom
is 100% reunited.
Why have we stopped?
Apologies, there are rocks on the tracks.
It's most likely bandits.
We're sending troops
to handle the situation.
Call them off.
I will take care of the bandits myself.
- Gah!
- O-wah!
- Aah!
- Oww!
- Ahh!
- Argh!
Ugh, ooh!
- Ehh!
- Ack, ohh!
You're... Kuvira.
And you're the bandits
who have been causing chaos
where I am trying to
establish order, aren't you?
We're sorry.
We didn't know this was your train...
Don't talk over me
Please, take mercy on us.
Stop groveling as if this is
the worst day of your life.
This is a good day.
I'm gonna give you all the opportunity
to rehabilitate yourselves
and become productive
members of your nation.
Right now, you're lost,
but pledge your loyalty to me,
and I'll give you a new
purpose in your lives.
Of course, if you don't want to join,
you could always stay right here.
Hopefully someone saves you
before the next train speeds through,
but I wouldn't count on it.
No, we'll join.
Don't leave us here.
We pledge our loyalty to you, great uniter.
♪
I don't know why we're leaving so early
if you're just getting a haircut.
The dinner at air temple island
isn't until later tonight.
Because I'm not just getting a haircut.
It's a spa day.
We're talking minimum four hours.
Are you kidding me?
What are you having done
that takes four hours?
A rejuvenating tea leaf skin wrap.
Have you ever gotten one of those, Mako?
Yeah, I'm not interested.
Oh, you will be.
So while your hands soak
in a bubbling milk bath,
your feet are in a tub full
of these little suckerfish
that literally eat your calluses away.
Gobble them right up. Crazy, huh?
That's disgusting.
Then they scrape your skin
with blocks of sea salt,
lube you up with seaweed infused aloe,
wrap you in tea leaves,
put you in a hot box
for four hours and bam, you're done!
Mako, look at all my fans.
They must be in town for my coronation.
Uh, I don't know if all
those people are your fans.
Boo!
Yeah!
All right, Wu!
Wu, we have to get you out of here.
What?
Go, go.
What just happened out there?
I think those were Kuvira
supporters in the crowd.
Oh, no! Mako, I've been hit.
It's a gusher.
That's not blood, it's strawberry pie.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah, you're right. But that was close.
I don't know what would've
happened if you weren't there.
You would've been hit by a pie.
It's really not that big of a deal.
Or I could've been killed.
I don't know what I'd ever do without you.
Wait a second, did you say strawberry pie?
I'm allergic to strawberries.
I don't think I can breathe.
Get me to the hospital, Wu down.
You're allergic to bee stings.
Oh, right.
I always get those two mixed up.
Look! A train made it through.
Maybe they brought food and supplies.
Hey, what's your boyfriend doing here?
If he's here, he must be
with Kuvira and my brother.
This isn't going to be good.
- Bolin!
- Kai!
Wow, you are a lot heavier
than you used to be,
you're really growing up.
What's up with your new hair?
You look like a stiff.
Hey, Kuvira says it
makes me look intelligent
and professional.
Don't believe everything she says.
Opal, I can't believe you're here too.
I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
Look who it is.
It's good to see you again, little sister.
What a wonderful surprise.
A happy reunion for my favorite couple.
How's mom doing?
Like you care. She still
hasn't forgiven you.
You know, for someone who
claims to be so enlightened,
mom can really hold a grudge.
I guess when her son betrays her.
Please.
Opal. We're not here to bicker with you
about something that
happened three years ago.
We're here to help this
town, just like you.
I've heard how you help
towns by conquering them.
I know the rumors about
me can be pretty nasty,
but I am giving everyone in
this nation a better future,
and with Bolin's help
and my fiancé's ideas,
we're laying the groundwork
for the people to achieve
their own greatness.
- Your fiancé?
- You haven't heard?
Your brother and I are getting married.
Isn't that great, sweetie?
I know things got heated with your family
when Baatar and I left Zaofu,
but don't you think it's
time to forgive and forget?
What are you doing here?
Hello, Governor. I was wondering if you
and I could talk privately.
So, have you had time to
rethink my generous offer?
Generous? You want to take everything.
How is that generous?
Governor, your state has
been overrun by bandits.
They have you outnumbered
and out-supplied.
The question's not if
they'll take over, it's when.
Unless you sign our deal.
Agree to our terms and
you'll have the full force
of my army backing you.
You will remain in charge,
just under my supervision.
I will save your life, and
the lives of your citizens.
I think that's pretty generous.
I know how you manipulate states
and force them to join up under you.
I know the only reason you want this region
is because it's rich in ore.
They might call you "The Great Uniter,"
but you're destroying everything.
I'll never turn the great state of Yi
over to you.
You have a lot of pride,
but it cannot protect your people.
Your pride will not stop the hordes
as your city crumbles to the ground,
and your pride certainly
will not feed your hungry
when all that is left is rubble.
Leave! Get out of my state.
You will perish,
unless you take my generous offer.
It's time to go, we're not wanted here.
What happened?
It appears we can't make a deal right now.
Wait, aren't you guys
gonna stick around and help?
Here's the contract, we'll
wait at the border for one day.
You get the governor to sign it,
and you'll have all the help you need.
I guess I gotta go.
Don't, please!
You can't turn your back on these people.
I'm not.
I want to help, but if
the governor wants us gone,
there's-there's nothing I can do.
I'm sorry... hey!
Opal, please.
Leave if that's what you're going to do.
You know, we might not
need their help after all.
The roads may be impassable,
but not the skies.
We can use lefty to fly
to all the nearby villages,
pick up supplies and fly back.
You're right.
We can save this town ourselves.
Sorry we couldn't give you
more, that's all we could spare.
Every little bit helps.
Because of you and the
other farmers around here,
we have more than enough
food to feed the town
until we can get some reinforcements.
Thanks.
So... you and Bolin doing okay?
I don't know.
It's really tough having a
long-distance relationship,
and I can't stand that
he's working with Kuvira.
I can tell.
But it does seem like he
found his calling, doesn't it?
He loves helping people.
Maybe, it's just he's changed a lot
since he's been around her.
He's growing up.
I just hope we're not growing apart.
Speaking of long-distance relationships,
how are you and Jinora doing?
Actually, we're doing fine.
You hear that?
It's more bandits.
We're hooked.
No!
Ah!
Whoa!
What happened? Where's all the food?
We were attacked in mid
air. We lost everything.
It might be time to make a tough call.
Here, tell Kuvira to save my people.
For what it's worth, I think
you made the right decision.
Did I ever really have a choice?
When Korra gets here, I bet she's not even
gonna know who I am. Why is that?
Because Meelo the boy
has turned into Meelo the man.
Right, you're completely unrecognizable.
You've never
had the tea leaf wrap?
You have no idea what you're missing.
The face massage alone is to die for.
Ugh. This coronation
cannot some soon enough.
I can't wait to go back
to being a detective.
Right. Um, yeah, about that.
What?
I don't know how to tell you this.
You're going to Ba Sing Se with the prince.
No!
I tried to get you out of
it, but it's over my head.
Wu personally asked Raiko.
He said he doesn't know
what he'd do without you.
This can't be happening.
I'm not even an Earth Kingdom citizen.
I work for the Republic
city police department.
Not anymore.
You're just a pawn in
Raiko's diplomatic game.
You can try talking to
him, but I don't think
he's going to let you quit.
There's a Southern water tribe
ship pulling up to the dock.
Korra!
- Cool!
- Yeah!
The state of Yi is now under
the full protection of my army.
Proclaim your loyalty, if
you wish to keep your post.
I pledge my loyalty to you, great uniter.
Tonraq, it's good to
have you back in the city,
and everyone is excited
to see the avatar again.
What do you mean? Isn't Korra already here?
No, we thought she was coming with you.
Korra left the south pole six months ago.
She's written me letters.
She said she was here in Republic City.
I assure you, your daughter's not here.
Then where is she?
Is that all you got?
Unh!
Unh.
We have a winner.
Here, for your lackluster participation.
Thanks.
You know, you look very familiar.
Yeah, you kind of look
like that avatar girl.
I get that a lot.
Whatever happened to her anyway?
I wouldn't know.
Sync and corrections by:kDragon
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net