Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all four elements
...
And bring balance to the world.
Korra returned to Republic City
But Bolin and Varrick
are still at large.
For weeks ago
Korra removed the poison that remained in his body,
But the memory of the attack of Zaheer
still haunts her.
And after being defeated by Kuvira
,
Does not believe in his full recovery.
Meanwhile, Kuvira was spoon
spiritual vines in the swamp.
But how close is finished
their spiritual energy weapon?
BOOK 4 BALANCE CHAPTER 9
"WILD BEYOND"
All, mother,
we can stay close, please?
The tour is about to begin
.
This is my boy, Ryu.
He lived in the basement
But then
received command of the air,
And has done important things
by the Air Nation.
His father and I
are here to visit you,
And we are really enjoying
the big city.
We are so proud,
is not, dear?
At least now I have a job.
Mom, Dad,
I'm trying to work.
A curiosity, personal:
All these vines
were created by Unavaatu
When he fought the giant spirit of Korra
The fate of the world.
Excuse me, we are
in the spirit world?
No.
The Spirit World
is on the ground beneath us?
No, can I just read
my guides?
- Honey, do not be nervous.
- I'm not nervous!
Why
vine that is coming in our direction?
I do not see anything about it
in my guides.
I will mess you
with a stick.
Do not!
Why did you do that?
Return all back!
This tour is exciting!
Is not he the best air domineering
all?
Is everything okay?
No, Kuvira has
my family
And no one but me
seem to care.
All we care.
Do not worry.
Let's get them back.
There I am.
I felt a strange surge of spiritual energy
To come from spiritual jungles.
Something's wrong.
Are you sure you felt
a disturbance?
Perhaps you sense you've barely
with something you ate.
I'm telling you.
I felt.
Maybe something happened
with Ryu group.
We should have found them.
Yes, but it's Ryu.
Can be at the mall,
for all we know.
Korra, you can not feel
how strange is energy?
No, but...
Maybe you can make a reading
.
Korra, what was it?
You are fine?
It is the Kuvira.
I saw her spoon vines
swamp.
Must be affecting our spiritual
jungles.
I bet that's
you were feeling.
Why she's the scoop
vines?
Whatever the reason,
I am sure that is not good.
We have to tell the Raiko.
This can help convince other leaders
Finally do away with it.
I will continue to look for
Ryu and others.
I think we should deal with
Kuvira immediately.
Yes! I agree!
I know how get rid of it,
Tell you who won
vacation with all expenses paid
A tropical island.
So when you get there,
reveal it was a trick.
The island is a prison!
Ready! We caught her!
Or, okay...
I'm only advise.
Marched with an army of moles
-badger.
Does anyone know if the Kuvira
have any allergies?
I think we all know
what should be done.
We take the fight
to her.
I do not think that attacking
is the right move,
Since she has not done anything aggressive
- For the United Republic.
- Not yet.
But we can not rely on
Kuvira.
She told us that gave
power and did not.
I agree with the Raiko.
We must take the offensive and begin
to resume Zaofu.
President Raiko,
sorry to interrupt, but...
- What is happening here?
- Hello, Avatar Korra.
We're just having a meeting of world leaders
,
To find out what to do with the Kuvira.
For the record, I told Raiko
I should have invited you.
Invited him to it,
but not me?
Please Korra,
is not personal.
Just think, perhaps, have we called
Too early to return to active.
Again...
Him, I do not?
We are half
a meeting
Can not have people
to appear when they want!
Personal!
Perfect!
They're all here!
Bolin?
What are you doing here?
Guards,
remove these intruders.
Do not!
We fled the Kuvira Army.
We're back at your side.
We have intelligence
for you!
I believe we should have started
by the way.
Listen to me. The Kuvira
is doing this thing going...
I do not know how it works,
but has this...
It is a super weapon.
As a normal weapon,
except it's super!
And let me guess.
It has something to do with the spiritual
vines.
Yes! How did you know?
I saw her spoon vines
swamp.
If she finds out how to use that power,
We are all doomed.
It can use the weapon to attack
Republic City.
The only way to protect ourselves is
with a preemptive strike.
The rulers of mine air will not make
part of an unprovoked attack.
Not the Fire Nation.
But
Lady Fire Izumi
The Kuvira is a threat
to the world.
It needs to be stopped!
The Fire Nation
spent too much in its history
Fighting wars
meaningless.
And I refuse to drag
my nation to another,
Unless there is no other choice
.
If they attack Kuvira,
will be without my army.
Okay.
I will postpone any attack plans.
Let's get defensive
And increase security at the borders.
This,
will my help.
Opal, wait!
Please...
I just want to say
I regret so much for everything.
I'm glad you are doing well,
But it's a little late
to repent.
I know. I know.
I did not hear you.
I was on the side of Kuvira,
Helped her to win
the Earth Kingdom,
Taking your house,
and capturing your mother,
Of your brothers and your father...
Wow! That sounds really bad
when I say aloud.
But I will try to change everything
for you.
Forgive me, lovebirds,
but I need to talk to Opal.
In particular.
I'm sorry, kid. But Raiko
failed to convince
The other leaders to attack the Kuvira.
So our family...
It seems ourselves
have to save them.
Do you think other people
- Agree to go with us?
- This was not allowed.
It is a dangerous mission into enemy territory
.
We can not ask others to
risk their lives for our family.
If we want to rescue them,
we will have to act alone.
Bolin,
am glad that you have come back.
- I was worried about you.
- We all were.
Thank you, friends.
Mako, I'm sorry for the way
as we left things.
I'm such a fool.
You tried to warn me about the Kuvira
,
And I was on her side,
like a fool.
You were right,
'm just an idiot.
I hope to be able
to earn your trust again.
If anyone has lost confidence
in people, I went.
Since Kuvira defeated me,
no one wants me around.
We want you around.
And Bolin,
I am not a fool.
I was just doing what
You thought right.
I love you.
I embrace them again.
Korra! The vines!
They are taking me!
Help!
Get all here!
Take a barrier.
Cancels all tours.
Someone call Tenzin.
We have to go in there and find
Jinora.
I think nobody
should go there now.
I know I'm not the Avatar
it used to be
But I can do this.
Be careful.
- Jinora!
- Hello! Anyone here?
Expected.
Did you hear that?
Let's go.
Korra, look.
What are those things?
It is the Jinora and the rest of them.
Their spirits are trapped
in the Spirit World.
- Let's get out of here.
- No!
It will cause the vines.
Let me try.
They will not open.
Perhaps meditate
in the spirit world,
Can free them.
Wait...
This is not
the spiritual world.
Zaheer! No!
You can not fight me
and against the poison.
- No, I removed it.
- You shall never remove it.
Korra, what's the problem?
- It Zaheer.
- What are you talking about?
It has haunted me since
fought him.
I can not be at peace.
It's like you're preventing me
Meditating
in the Spirit World.
I'm here to help you.
What do you need?
- I face Zaheer.
- Korra, it is very dangerous.
Even arrested,
it is not reliable.
Need if you want to save
Jinora and others.
- There is another way.
I'll call your father,
it can make an expedition
To the Spirit World
the South Portal.
Also lost faith in me,
not lost?
Everyone thinks that I am unable to do anything
.
- This is not it.
- I know I can do this.
I'm so worried
with Jinora.
I can not imagine anything happening to you.
Tenzin, please.
I'll be fine.
The Zaheer is stuck in the depths
the mountains outside the city.
I'll call Raiko
and get his approval.
Thank you.
Pa-baps, where are you?
Pabu!
I felt you so much.
So, I do not know if you heard, but the
Opal is angry with me.
He was waiting for me
ajudasses to win her back.
Amazing!
Yes, I had an idea.
Hello, Pabu.
Yes, it's also good to see you.
What do you have there?
- Opal, got it.
- What is this?
A picnic,
just for the two of us.
I mean three.
Sorry, Pabs.
So this ticket that brought me Pabu
Saying
broke his legs, was a trick?
Perhaps. But now you're here,
do not want to sit down, relax...
Try my cookies.
It is a recipe Pema.
And see the Pabu
to make their performances
Most famous for entertainment.
Homemade cookies.
Preferred mine.
This will make me forget
which worked for Kuvira,
The person arrested
my family.
And that probably is
the torture this time.
So, yes. Let's sit down
and make a great picnic
Because we are so in love!
I'm sorry that you saw this,
Pabu.
Thank you for coming.
It's nice to be welcomed back with open arms
.
In fact, I called him here
necessity.
It is no secret
I do not like you.
Especially after trying
kidnap me.
Supposedly.
For. Everything you do
is "supposedly".
Like when you took possession
my company
Bombardeaste and the cultural center
of the Southern Water Tribe.
I built it!
A man is entitled
to blow up your property!
Right now, I need you put
your differences aside.
If Kuvira is really
to create a super weapon
We need the brightest minds
Working together to prevent it.
What do you say, Asami?
Partner again?
Okay.
I will help.
But you dare not even think
in fool me again.
You sure you're ready
for this?
I have. I think if you see the chained Zaheer
,
Will recognize that it is no longer a threat.
Get closer to the wall.
No.
I need to do this alone.
I thought you were appearing,
sooner or later.
So...
You should really be in trouble
if you came here to see me.
I came here to look in your eyes
And tell you that you no longer have
no more power over me.
I will not be afraid
you.
I think it's not true.
Yet seem scared.
- This was a mistake.
- I know why you're here.
You know nothing about me!
Can not you come
in the Spirit World.
I spend most of my time there,
And everyone knows that the spirit of Avatar
Is not seen there a few years.
You can meditate there
from here?
Do you feel spiritually
distressed?
Is this your problem.
Republic City is taking
of spiritual energy
And I do not even
can you feel it.
No, my problem is you!
You poisoned me!
You ruined me!
People thought me
unstoppable
But now I find that I am not capable of anything.
Blaming me is a crutch
you feel better to you,
But it is not helping
anything.
I thought personally see you
would put an end to all this.
Maybe it's time to give me account
Would never be the same.
None of us will return to
the same as before.
I learned to fly,
but now I am in chains.
You have all the power in the world
and freedom to use it,
But preferiste suppress you.
I'm not repress me,
but my powers have limits.
You're wrong.
That poison should have killed you.
But could you
to combat it.
Do you think that your powers have limits
,
I would say are unlimited.
Any.
Before, you spoke about always
chaos and freedom.
Then
killed the Queen of Earth
And have created the worst dictator
that the Kingdom has ever seen.
Thank you for that.
I heard rumors about it,
But I did not know
had achieved so much power.
It needs to be stopped.
I can not stop her,
unless they get over it.
I think I can help you.
Let me guide you
to the Spirit World.
Not at all.
I can not trust you.
Maybe not.
But if you had any other option
Would not be here,
is it?
We have been enemies
once, but now
Our interests are the same.
I came here.
What do you have to lose?
Concentrate on the sound of my voice
And empty your mind.
- Let her go.
- I can not!
You can.
Accepted what happened to you.
Do not fear what could have happened
.
- I have no control.
- Do not be afraid. Hold on!
I got.
And you brought me
far.
Do you know where is the Jinora
and the others are?
No, but I know.
Raava, missed you.
Where were you?
Always been within
you.
Can you help me find the
Jinora?
How do
freed their spirits?
You must master your inner energy.
But I have powers
in the Spirit World.
No.
You are more powerful here.
In the spiritual world,
Are you connected with every spiritual energy.
I'm all in a spiritual way.
Father!
I'm so glad you are doing well.
What happened?
How did you escaped?
The Korra saved us.
So... How do you feel yourself?
I feel...
whole again.
I feel good.
Do you think you will be able
to forget what Zaheer did?
No.
But finally I can
to accept what happened,
And I think it will strengthen me.
Where are you going?
We have family business
to treat.
Okay, listen.
Before you left,
Just want to tell you that
understand how you feel.
I know there is nothing I can do
Or no action to correct my mistakes, but...
That does not mean I'll stop trying to recover
you when you return.
Because...
I love you.
Thank you for saying all this.
There is one thing you can do to regain
me.
What is it?
Yes, do anything.
Come undercover
us.
- Where?
- Zaofu.
We will rescue my family.
Translation En United4ever and MundoAvatar
pTpT Adaptation - Arodri
www.tvsubtitles.net