Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all four elements
...
And bring balance to the world.
After Kuvira spoon
spiritual vines swamp,
The Republic City
vine reacted kidnapping people
Korra saved everyone,
but all is not well.
Varrick and Bolin
warned everybody
On the superweapon
of Kuvira.
Now, Raiko want to ride
a defense against the Empire Earth.
However Bolin, Opal and Lin are on a mission
To rescue Su Beifong
and his family,
Being held captive
.
BALANCE BOOK 4 CHAPTER 10
"BEIFONG OPERATION"
Let's do this
Save the Beifongs
and our love,
Because I promised to repair the space that emerged between us
And turn us into one.
Shut up now.
- I got tired of you all the way.
- Yes ma'am.
Kuvira dropped
all vials.
Why you do it?
Has a battalion of troops
stationed there.
We will not see anything useful here.
We have to look more closely.
Do not worry, all prisoners
have been changed.
- Hello, sir.
Grandmother Toph!
You'd make me the waist
Last time
met.
My God!
It can not be!
Can not be true!
What?
You need to pee?
No.
Now, maybe.
It is my hero!
My name Bolin.
Flirt with her granddaughter.
I mean, sort of.
I screwed up,
but that's why I'm here.
And it is my hero.
I have said it.
Also won a hug?
- What does he have?
- Is an actor.
I've scoured the city
behind the Su?
How do you know
she was captured?
I'm living in the swamp
And watching Zaofu
through the vines.
Of course, it makes sense.
I had already gone when I got here
.
I went to town
and I heard that were taken
Into a prison camp
around here.
Where would that be?
There is a factory with
rehabilitation facilities not far from here.
- How do you know that?
- The Bolin worked for Kuvira.
How do you just dating
An idiot type
working for Kuvira?
Worked!
There is the sharp tongue,
I can guarantee.
Tell me that this attitude
is not hereditary.
Grandma, this is Juicy.
And I thought
that Appa was smelly.
Why did you choose
this disgusting thing?
Do not choose our bison,
it is that chooses us.
And after chosen,
you can not go back.
Believe me, already checked.
Secure borders,
troops to guard the entrances to the city.
What geniuses thought
to defeat Kuvira?
It is a flying mega-suit.
Asami had the idea to see
dragonfly-hummingbirds.
You can wear it and fly
in any direction.
And where is coming out
the spiritual ray?
Do not have any.
I'm telling you what I said to Kuvira
,
This technology should not be used.
It is already being used by
Kuvira!
I need weapons of spiritual vines,
and need them now.
There was the Kuvira
harvest in the swamp
Gone crazy the vines
and catch all those people.
You should be the bridge between the two worlds
.
- Why you can not reap some?
- I will not.
But perhaps because the spirits
enjoy it as much of Republic City
Can convince them to help us
to defend the place.
Perhaps as the Genie of arms
And the bridge of spirits
prepare for battle,
Should be to evacuate
ordinary citizens
So that if Kuvira attack,
not hurt.
It is a good idea.
Prince Wu, go with the police
coordinate the evacuation.
Now all the work.
I want daily reports.
Good job there.
I am proud.
You're starting to sound like a King
- For whom I work.
- Thank you.
What if Korra believe that
the "man of the people"
Perhaps even can go out with her.
- You always have to spoil everything.
- Come on!
Why do you think that men
do some good things?
To engage girls.
Every art, every song, every
evacuation of the city,
All the girls.
Okay, guys, let's test
the core of energy.
I want everything ready for the demonstration
For Kuvira tomorrow.
Carry the capsule
energy.
Zhu Li, boot phase one.
The condenser is in trouble,
is to regress.
Turns it.
I can not.
The control does not.
They need to get out of here,
it will explode!
Everyone, get out!
We will Baatar.
It's too late.
This ring was broken.
That's what supercharged
the reaction.
Let's dismantle it all today
And check all parts.
Nothing is too small.
This has to be ready
tomorrow.
How long are they not together?
For some time now.
A few years.
It's more like 20 years.
Time flies when you're my age.
I'm surprised you came to save Su.
I thought not give
well.
Su and I finally made peace
.
Good, I'm glad we left
everything in the past.
"Leave". It's ok.
Okay, there's the factory.
God,
it is a huge...
Thing.
I think I know where they are.
Do you feel that cave
some rooms below?
It seems empty, but is saved by a
horrible robots.
Okay.
Why it took
soldiers to defend an empty cave?
Should be in some sort of suspended prison
,
So you can not use
the field of earth.
Someone is coming.
Hide yourselves!
I did not expect you until tomorrow
.
Just wanted to make sure
me that all is well.
- It looks wonderful.
- We had some breakdowns,
But we must be ready for the test tomorrow.
You worked on it from the beginning, Zhu Li.
What do you think
that was the problem?
It is a very complex
machine.
It is normal to have some bugs to fix
.
But are you doing everything you can
to fix them, right?
Of course, His Eminence.
She is lying.
Warns troops and workers
To come to the demonstration tomorrow.
I want everyone to witness
this incredible new weapon into action.
We should think of a way
To overthrow the Kuvira
as we hypothesis.
Or at least
destroy the cannon.
If taken to Republic City,
can destroy everything.
I did not come to fight with the Kuvira
or destroy a cannon.
I'm here to save my family.
It will cost all we have
only to escape alive.
The Kuvira want
that all staff
See the test
gun tomorrow
Then the plant will be
practically empty.
This is our best chance to get
And release the Su
without being seen.
Good thinking, Bolin.
Thank you.
I got a headache now.
Excuse spirit?
Can I speak to...
And you disappeared.
Like all other spirits.
Are to leave the city.
Let me ask a question
on the metal domain.
The Su tried to teach me,
but could not.
Had a gym to train the metal domain.
Even covered as you can
with the right instruction.
It is even
a sensitive teacher.
I learned to dominate the lava.
Really?
It is a very rare skill.
Maybe even thou some talent.
I do not think they think I'm talented.
It means a lot to me,
to come from my hero.
Yes, it is very encouraging
.
Hey, I'm blind, I'm not deaf.
So here's something
I always had curiosity.
Who is the father of Lin?
It was a type called Kanto.
A good man,
but did not go well between us.
E...
Okay.
Lin, I can feel your breath
angry here.
Just say what you have to say
and we will finish this.
Do away with this?
Okay, let's not focus on the fact
that grew up without a father.
You need not be so sentimental
.
Just one of those things,
okay?
Hey, I forgave thee all thine
blunders
Long,
and Su and I made up.
You're the only
you want to stay
This family drama
meaningless for life.
Forgiven me for what?
And do not know my father
is meaningless to you?
It was very important for me.
And so far,
never said anything about it.
You know, after the Su and I
solve our problems,
I thought, "Maybe I should
contact my mother."
But now that we're together again,
Remembered why
stop talking to us.
Will you let me furious,
and not even know why.
And when I tell you,
I do not want to know.
When we save the Su,
you and I are finished.
If that's your decision
and makes you happy, then fine.
The test is about to begin.
They'll blow that town
empty that flew yesterday.
Can move forward.
Understood.
Come on.
The guards are
the other side of that door.
We must be silent.
Throw me over the cage,
and I can bring them by my cable.
Bolin, you'll have to catch them
since the mother can not see them.
Ready?
Let's take them one at a time.
Let's go.
I got you!
Congratulations on all your hard work
.
This weapon is proof
that Empire Earth
Is the strongest nation
the world.
And believe me,
this is just the beginning!
Shoot the gun.
- What's going on?
- Probably some minor problem.
I must be able to find the problem.
The pin distributor disappeared.
I swear I left
in place yesterday.
There is no possibility to have fallen.
That may cause trouble
system-wide gun?
Can cause it to explode.
What do you know about it?
Nothing.
Swore me loyalty,
And I gave you a chance
of magnitude.
That's how recompense?
You're a monster.
I do not regret anything.
Holds it in the target city.
It will be able to see how the weapon works
personally.
No.
Honey, it's okay.
The Lin will not let you fall,
and Bolin will catch you.
No, no.
Just go...
Let me.
I stay here.
Sorry, but I have
to do this.
Prison.
Go already there.
We must postpone the test?
I Do not come this far to stop now
.
Shoot when you're ready.
I want to see this city destroyed.
I'll get them.
We are leaving.
Mother! Dad!
Thank you.
Let's go.
The Kuvira picked up the Zhu Li
and held it in the city.
- What? I have to save her.
- You can not go there, boy.
It is suicide.
The Kuvira goes looking for us.
We went through a lot together.
I can not leave her.
Toph, said that Zhu Li
lied about fixing the cannon.
She should be trying
stop it.
From what you know, it could just
Be to get away,
to have made a mistake.
No.
The Zhu Li makes no mistakes.
Can go. If we survive
arrange way to go to town.
No, Bolin!
Can go.
I have to go with Bolin.
It might be our best chance of stopping
Kuvira.
And maybe take that gun.
We can not let
Opal be good.
If you want to be caught
again, or worse,
This is a problem of yours.
I'm tired.
It takes account of the Baatar and Huan.
And then,
how are you, mother?
I told you never to call me that.
Spirits is the Avatar.
Please listen to me...
Since I opened the gates,
Spirits and humans lived together happily
In Republic City.
That's all
could wait.
I know you felt the effects
The Kuvira to cut
spiritual vines.
But now is not the time
fleeing the city.
It's time to help me
to save her from Kuvira,
Whatever the power of the spirits
For use as a weapon
against other humans.
We are not involved in human
wars.
The spirits helped Unalaq.
He used the power of Vaatu
during the Harmonic Convergence
To force the spirits to fight against you.
- Is that what you want?
- No, but as Avatar,
Hope will help me,
To save the new
world we share.
Would you exactly the same as Kuvira.
Use the spirits
as a weapon in a war of humans.
The answer is no.
Wait!
Please listen.
If the spirits and human
will live together,
We have to work together.
Opal?
No.
We have to stop the test.
Give bad name to
metal rulers!
Thank you for coming to save us, mother.
Yes. Thank you, boss.
I'm sorry for what I said yesterday.
I just... You know
.
Look, I know not
was a great mother,
But either way,
finished with two great kids.
Good enough to risk
my old ass for you.
If they can find a way
not hate me,
May be enough,
at least for me.
For me too.
You know, I never had a family
besides my brother
Until a few years ago
And meet with them
made me realize how special...
That's enough.
Enjoy the return to the city
that flying beast.
You will not return to Republic City
us, grandmother?
No, my days of struggle
over.
Do not say to Korra, the
my back is killing me.
That's why
not come to Katara
To meddle with these things
civil war.
The right time,
we have to leave that to the kids.
I want to thank you for returning
to save me.
And are not hard to Bolin
to work with Kuvira.
His heart was in the right place
.
I think the Bolin managed
away with it is this.
Yes...!
We should go.
I have bad news to bring
to Republic City.
The Kuvira will attack
within two weeks.
Translation En United4ever and MundoAvatar
pTpT Adaptation - Arodri
www.tvsubtitles.net