Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all four elements
...
And bring balance to the world.
Empire Earth
invaded the United Republic!
After Kuvira demonstrate the power of its spiritual weapon
,
President Raiko
gave the city
But the Avatar refused
to give up without a fight.
Korra did Baatar hostage Jr.,
waiting for Kuvira
Back off, but the plan failed
,
Because shot the
under the Avatar team.
Does something or someone
may stop Kuvira
And its mecca giant?
BALANCE BOOK 4 CHAPTER 11
"COLOSSUS OF THE DAY"
Go ahead,
unhurried.
I'm just hold
a monstrous thing.
For the love of Raava,
a lot of people here.
They all came out?
Kuvira is coming. With a squad
mecca-suits.
- What do you do?
- This is my hometown
I hate to say, but there is no reason to take a chance the lives
Fight it.
Let's leave the city now
We think of something
and returned.
E
people that have not been evacuated?
If Kuvira
know that Wu is with them
Can use that gun on him,
and kill everyone.
I have not been able to prevent
Kuvira taking Zaofu,
I will not let her take
Republic City.
The world will not be safe
as she possess that weapon.
I agree.
Rid of that giant today.
- Lin!
- I'm glad you are well.
You bother me.
You, rulers,
will have to fight alone.
It destroyed our factory
with all mecca-suits.
Not all.
There are prototypes in my office.
If we make them fly, we will be able
To offer some air support.
Su takes Baatar and other
for the Asami office.
Try to put these costumes to work
as soon as you can.
The rest, will face
the Kuvira to us.
Please calm down everyone!
Trains shall return soon
to take you.
Tell that idiot mecca-
to calm down.
It is he who is destroying
the whole city!
I hate to be the bearer of more bad news
,
I heard on the radio that the
Kuvira Army
Destroyed the tracks of the train.
We will not leave town
the train.
Staff, was in the tower observation
And saw a group of soldiers
mecca-with costumes to come here!
How wonderful!
The giant is not enough?
Over!
Let's be transformed into dust!
Listen, folks.
I can get us out
to calm down.
You can come off the bench, please?
It is tight.
Course.
I'm just the driver.
No one needs me
on the bench.
Stay calm.
I'll be back. Come on!
- Where are you going?
- I'll get help.
Can you handle this crowd
unmanageable for some time?
I created the Meelo.
I can deal with anything.
One paint store?
That's it!
What are you doing, Meelo?
I have an idea of how
stop the giant!
Now everyone gather up a can of paint
and arrange me some balloons!
Dominators air
approaching.
I can see them.
Spears bombs!
Clean the glass.
Now!
The joints also are
platinum.
I could not bend it!
You are about to warm
feet, metal girl!
Attack now!
Opal!
Everybody, withdraw.
Take the injured to the offices of Asami.
Meeting you there.
I will see if I can find help.
Okay.
Let's try to turn it back on.
I can not stabilize!
I thought that you had repaired
- Hydraulic system.
- And I fixed it!
Twists harder!
I hope you something
You can take down a squad
mecca-suits.
's Troops Kuvira
are coming in this direction!
I know how to end
with some mecca-suits,
And this may end well
with that giant!
Asami, off
everything is electric here,
Until we get back.
Zhu Li, come on.
Where am I?
- Mother?
- Just rest, son.
- I'm here.
- Mom, I'm sorry.
I betrayed you...
betrayed the whole family.
I gave my life to Kuvira,
And it just shot
that gun at me.
How could you?
I do not know, honey.
It is a complicated person.
Wing and Wei will never forgive me.
And Opal...
Yeah, maybe they take a while to accept it
,
But we will solve this,
as a family.
Do you really think this plan will work
, Lord?
I know I can stop
the mecca-costumes
With a pulse electromagnetic
,
So it is logical that can
stop a giant Mecca-costume
With a giant electromagnetic pulse.
- Zhu Li, I was thinking.
- Is always, Lord.
Yes, but lately,
I was thinking about you.
Maybe we not survive
to this, and I feel I must
- Tell you some things.
- "Some things"?
I remember when I was a kid,
I had a horse-ostrich,
and called her Mrs. Beaks.
I grew up on a farm.
I have told you this, Zhu Li?
That was before
Men Circus take me.
Anyway, I loved Mrs. Beaks,
but did not give him value.
You'll need to finish
his story later.
The troops
of Kuvira are close.
Okay.
I hope this works.
Good!
All are defeated.
Yikes!
It remains to come.
Zhu Li, is the thing!
I'm afraid there is nothing else to do
.
- What was that?
- An electromagnetic pulse.
Hung the mecca-costumes, but
not our source of energy.
Located the source of the wrist.
Must be where the Varrick is.
3rd and 4th platoon,
follow and continue cleaning.
Track down anyone who ever left this city.
Varrick,
how your electric thing
Hung up smaller outfits
but not great?
Because it uses energy
spiritual vines.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could help you,
but that thing is unstoppable.
It's not.
Father?
Withdrew the chain
to help us.
I figured we were going to need
all geniuses we can.
If the prison still exists
after all this,
- We put it back there.
- I know what you must think of me,
But I love Republic City
And would do anything to save her.
You think you know
how to stop this thing?
Should act as if they were
an infection:
Penetrate the skin and then
attacking vital organs.
Turn off the heart and brain,
And this beast will not survive.
But how do we get?
The Industries of the Future
have plasma saws
To cut platinum.
With a saw in Mecca-costume...
But the mountains are huge.
We will never bring you down.
Perhaps if we add an electric element
The welding torch
in fact, and convert it
A plasma saw.
So just cut the giant,
And make a big hole
enough for someone to enter.
As a metal mosquito.
You know what happens
with mosquitoes that land on me?
Crush them!
We will have to tackle together
To try to keep them safe
in costumes hummingbird.
It seems
are our only hope.
First you eat fruit
and then eating leaves
The little hungry lemur
ate all my trees
Okay.
Good job guys.
Who has another song
for us?
We can not stand here and sing songs
the air rulers
Until being captured,
or worse.
We must play the play button?
Who has a button?
Where did these moles-badger
come from?
From the zoo! The Mako always hated
my corner, but they love it!
What do we do with these moles
-badger?
It's the best
land domineering!
You can make us a tunnel
out of town
Without troops Kuvira
see us.
Are you sure that this
is the best plan?
Let's follow the moles!
Moles badger-digging holes in Republic City
We need to get away from Kuvira today
Although yet to find beautiful
Meca-platoons report.
3rd platoon. There is no sign
people so far.
4th platoon.
On the way to the train station.
I think we found the source of the electromagnetic pulse
.
Come tower
of Future Industries.
Is that the place.
The Kuvira is coming
in our direction.
How long will it take
to the mountains be ready?
Just a few minutes.
Go to the giant
as well as they can.
If you can get,
searching the engine room.
There are two emergency levers.
If the two  activate it
while
- You will be able to cut the power.
- Thanks.
We may not be able to stop it
,
But we can delay it.
Come on!
Jinora!
Yin...
Are the displaced of war
sweetest I know
I want to thank you for having
been so kind
While living under your roof
Stop.
Turn it slowly, and please
stop with the singing.
Are all prisoners
Earth Empire.
Come with us and no one will be hurt.
You do not need these people.
They are just innocent civilians caught in the crossfire
,
But I'm the Prince Wu
Right by leading
Earth Kingdom.
Take me to Kuvira.
She and I have issues
solve.
- No! Do not do that, Wu!
- I need to do.
But before you go,
I like to sing you a song.
If not respeitares
the ferret
Do not you respect me for me
No, no, no, no, no
There are
better than a giant cockroach?
But I'm royal
I have my moles-badger me
In fact,
your music is so bad,
The moles-badger your
abandoned you.
Do not know
What are you saying
Moles-badger
I love them, love them
I want, I want...
Stroking your noses
If we stop that mecca giant,
Will be because of you.
You do projectaste
these amazing costumes.
It's great to be working together again
.
I love you, Dad.
I love you.
- Zhu Li?
- Yes?
There's something I want to put
before descolarmos.
Put what?
I need to put this ring on your finger
.
Zhu Li Moon,
accepted to do the thing
For the rest of our lives?
I accept.
Good...!
Let's put these buckets
rust malfunctioning
Murdering a giant machine!
It's exactly as imagined
our engagement.
Ready to scratch
in the middle of the back,
- In place ever reach!
- Got it.
Let's get out of here.
Wow!
I liked to have that flexibility.
Hang on!
I need more power!
They are cut to enter!
More energy!
- We have to leave.
- I'm almost.
- We have to leave now.
- Almost. Almost.
- Father! Now!
- Goodbye, Asami.
I love you.
Father!
Hiroshi
plan worked.
There's our opening.
Translation En United4ever and MundoAvatar
pTpT Adaptation - Arodri
www.tvsubtitles.net