Earth.
Fire.
Air.
Water.
Only the Avatar can
master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Kuvira threatens to take Zaofu by force.
After tensions flared between Su Beifong
and her former protege,
Korra brokered a truce.
But it was too late.
Su and her sons were already on their way
to put an end to Kuvira.
Meanwhile, Bolin and
Varrick learned of Kuvira's
true tyrannical intent
and deserted her army.
But they were captured
and betrayed by Zhu Li.
Now they're being held against their will.
Are you sure this will work?
Even without Kuvira,
they could still crush us.
Most of this army has been forced
into service by Kuvira.
If we take her out, they'll
have no reason to fight.
Tonight we end her reign of terror.
She's alone in there.
Now's our chance.
- Don't hurt me!
- Zhu Li?
I knew you'd try a sneak attack.
You were afraid to step up
and lead the earth kingdom
when you had the chance,
you were afraid to join me
when I became the leader,
and now you're afraid of a fair fight.
You've always been a coward.
Take them.
Korra, you have to go stop Su
before she does something terrible.
Stop her? We should be helping her!
We have no idea where your
mom is or what her plan is.
If we go charging into Kuvira's camp,
we could get them all captured or worse.
All we can do now is wait.
Attention, citizens of Zaofu.
Your leader, Su Beifong,
attempted to attack me
tonight while I slept,
ignoring the terms of our truce.
Luckily, I now have her and
her assault team in custody.
No.
Rest assured that I will not take revenge
on the peaceful citizens of Zaofu,
as long as your remaining representatives
meet me outside the city at dawn to offer
the full and unconditional
surrender of your city.
That is all.
Korra, you can't let
Kuvira get away with this.
We have to go break
out mom and my brothers.
You swore an oath of nonaggression
when you became an airbender.
You can't just attack Kuvira.
I don't care about the oath.
I have to save my family.
No, Jinora is right.
Your mom attacked the camp.
Kuvira was just defending herself.
Defending herself?
She was going to attack our city!
I can't believe you're refusing to fight.
Why is that loudspeaker lady talking
when I'm trying to sleep?
Korra, what are we going to do?
Jinora and I will go
talk to Kuvira at dawn,
and maybe we can work something out.
I promise I'll do everything
I can to keep the peace.
I'll go with you.
- We'll go, too.
- No.
Dad told us to find
Korra, and we found her.
Now you need to stay safe.
Come on, let us help.
I can't risk anyone else being captured.
You can stay with Baatar and Huan
while I work this out with Kuvira.
Make sure they get back to Tenzin safely
if anything goes wrong.
Aw, man.
When am I gonna see some action?
Cookie jar empty.
No hot towels.
Waxy buildup.
Zhu Li!
Aw, she really is gone.
Up and at 'em, Varrick. Time to go to work.
We have another lab set up for you.
Kuvira wants the spirit
vine weapon operational
as soon as possible.
Zhu Li always greeted me in the morning
with a... a hot cup of tea.
You'll get your tea when you start working.
Well, I'm really only productive
for about 15 minutes a day,
usually in the afternoon around 3:45.
You'll work now.
I want you to show me how the device works.
What's going on?
Go back to sleep. We only need Varrick.
You'll need your energy when
you get to the reeducation camp.
I can't be expected to
work without an assistant.
Without Zhu Li, I'm helpless.
One of the guards will be your assistant.
I'll be supervising.
Well, I guess he'll be fine,
as long as he doesn't
need his hands afterwards.
What's he talking about, sir?
The last time we worked
with the spirit vines,
it created an uncontrollable blast
that burned through a
wall and could still be
blowing up comets in
space, as far as I know.
I wouldn't want to assist me if I were you.
Maybe we should just
let the kid help him out.
Fine. Bolin can assist.
Wait, what? I need my hands! Uh, hold on.
Can we get breakfast first?
While we still have hands?
Release them now!
If Su agrees to bow to
me and turn over Zaofu,
she and the rest of your
family will not be harmed.
Never! I'll never bow to you!
There must be some way
for us to resolve this.
I've already laid out my terms,
and I think they're very reasonable.
After all, Su did try to take me out
during our peaceful negotiations.
You call bringing an army to
threaten our city peaceful?
Where's Bolin?
I know he would never go along with this!
Bolin is with my fiance,
working on something very important,
but I assure you he's
on board with my plans.
You two have been apart for some time.
I guess you don't realize
how much Bolin has grown up.
Now turn over Zaofu.
I can't just let you take the city.
Avatar Korra, you are interfering
with internal earth empire business
and letting your personal feelings
get in the way of reason.
Zaofu cannot continue to rule itself.
They have been hoarding their riches
and technology too long.
I'm here to distribute
those resources fairly
throughout the nation.
This is about equality.
You don't care about equality!
This is about control!
Just take her down.
You know it's the right thing to do.
You have to stop this!
The only way you're going
to keep me from marching
into Zaofu is if you physically stop me.
Now what are you going to do?
It looks like you're
not giving me a choice.
Fine.
I want you all to know that I would never
ask any of you to do something
that I'm not willing to do myself.
So rather than risk your lives,
I will fight the
Avatar one-on-one.
Korra, if you win,
then you can do whatever
you want with Zaofu.
But after I beat you,
I want you out of my business for good.
I'm the one who brought peace
to the earth empire, not you.
You're not relevant here anymore.
Fine. You want to fight the Avatar?
Then let's finish this
right here, right now!
Are you really ready to fight her?
Just stay back and let me handle this.
It's been a while,
but I got a lot of pent-up rage.
Don't mess around. Kuvira is too good.
Just go into the Avatar
state and get it over with.
No, I'm only going to
use that as a last resort.
Be careful.
Use whatever you want, all the elements,
the Avatar state, anything you need.
I know you're a little rusty.
Enough talk.
Looks like the Avatar
is a little off her game.
Don't let her get you frustrated!
She wants you to make a mistake!
Bolin, do the thing.
- What thing?
- The thing!
I never had to tell Zhu Li what thing!
I'm not Zhu Li, okay?
Pretend I don't know anything
about anything that's happening here.
Also pretend I don't want
to build a super weapon
or get my hands blown off.
Walk me through what you're doing.
I want to know every detail of your work.
You know, when I started
working with the vines,
the point was to find a clean,
unlimited source of energy,
not develop some spirity death ray.
Clean energy, sounds great!
Who doesn't like that
stuff? Let's do that instead.
Quiet.
You're here to help, not talk.
And you of all people should realize
that once a discovery is made,
it is our responsibility as scientists
to pursue it as far as
we can, wherever it leads.
How would you know?
You couldn't discover a wolf-bat
if it was building a nest in your butt.
Ooh.
You're pathetic.
Wolf-bats don't build nests.
Ooh, you got me there, Dr. science.
You'll never know how it
feels to give birth to genius,
only to have it kidnapped
and raised by fools.
Are you done with your rambling,
or do the guards need to encourage you
to continue your work?
Okay, okay, okay.
The last time we ran the
current through the vine,
we couldn't control the power.
So I'm trying something new
to see if I can direct it.
Come on, Avatar.
Get up.
Show me what you've got.
We have to help her.
No. Stay back.
I can handle this.
So I see how the current
interacts with the vine,
and here is a kind of directional tube,
but this baffling here at the base...
It looks like that would
only redirect the energy
right back where it came from.
And what's that piece of
equipment you're fiddling with
now on the power source?
Hand me the
screw-turn-thingy, would ya?
Ugh, I can't believe you're helping them.
You know this isn't right.
Funny story, Bolin.
I first got the idea for
harnessing spirit power
when I watched that giant Unalaq monster
attack the city from my jail cell.
That giant monster set me free.
Trust me, kid. I know what I'm doing.
That ought to do it.
Huh.
Okay, stand back.
There we go.
What's that ticking?
That's the timer.
The timer for what?
For the bomb, of course!
What? What bomb?
The bomb that's going to
explode in five minutes
and destroy this entire
train, all of the spirit vines,
and everything else
within a few hundred yards.
You know what, I'd get
out of here if I were you.
This is the first time I've built a timer,
and it might run a little fast.
Bolin and I are ready to
go down with the ship...
or train in this case...
but you seem like you
have a lot to live for.
No, no, no, no!
I'm not ready to go down
with the ship or the train!
You're bluffing.
Stick around five minutes,
and you'll find out who's bluffing.
You'll be sorry you left me, Zhu Li!
When they write the history books,
your name will be synonymous with betrayal!
People will say, "hey,
what happened to that guy?"
"Oh, didn't you hear,
he Varrick'd himself because
some girl Zhu Li'd him!"
Enough.
What makes you think we'd
let you blow yourself up?
You're working for Kuvira.
You don't get to quit.
Grab him.
You try to pull me away from this thing,
and I'll hit this remote
and blow it immediately.
Why do you have a timer and a remote?
Well, first I built the
timer, but then I thought
you could drag me off the
train, so then I built a remote.
But then I thought, "well, now",
"do I really need the timer anymore?
Because I got a remote in my"...
whatever! I'm covering all my bases!
The point is, you're
leaving. We're staying.
You have to go into the Avatar state!
Do it!
I don't understand.
We got the poison out.
What's wrong with her?
I knew you were weak.
You broke our agreement!
Attack!
Keep them back! I'm calling for help.
Stunning work, Ikki.
It hurts my eyes with
its raw emotional power.
Ah, pedestrian.
I already know what you
look like on the outside.
I want you to show me the inner Meelo.
Help!
You have to get Korra and the rest of us
out of here now!
Hurry!
Finally! Let's get it on!
This is everyone. Our
half of the train is clear.
That's good. We're almost out of time.
You're insane.
You knew that when you hired me.
Bolin, do the thing.
Uh...
Unhook the cars!
Oh, come on, that was an easy one!
Man, that was great.
I gotta admit, you had me
going there for a while.
I really thought you
were going to blow us up.
Now, how do we turn this thing off?
Oh, we can't turn it off.
We're going to blow up.
But we had a pretty good run, right?
What are you talking about, a good run?
I'm still running! I like running!
I'll see you on the other side, Zhu Li.
I want you to know, I hate you.
I can't believe he
actually blew himself up.
That man was crazier than
a sewer-pipe elephant rat.
Let's get back to Zaofu.
Yes! You did it, Bolin.
You did the thing.
Mwah!
I can't believe
Zhu Li worked for you as long as she did.
Dive, pepper! Dive!
Here comes a hurricane!
You can't handle all this Meelo!
We've got her! Go!
We have to save them!
Opal, get out of here!
We'll be fine!
Just go!
I'll be back for you! I love you!
Zaofu is ours!
Bring the citizens of Zaofu to kneel
before the Great Uniter.
All who pledge their loyalty to me
will keep their freedom
and be dealt with fairly
as full citizens of the earth empire.
The rest will be imprisoned as traitors,
like Su Beifong and her sons.
Now bow.
Bow to her! Do it!
She is your rightful leader!
I'm so disappointed in you, junior.
Take them away!
Get your hands off me.
You're crushing my individuality.
All hail the Great Uniter!
Are you sure there's no way they survived?
Positive, but I think
I can replicate his work
with the spirit vines
and get us back on track.
I'll just need an assistant.
How would you like to help Baatar build
the most powerful weapon
the world has ever seen?
It would be my honor, Great Uniter.
Begin dismantling the domes.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net