Earth
Fire
Air
Water
Only the Avatar can master all four elements
...
And bring balance to the world.
Bolin, Opal and Lin
rescued the Beifong
And Zhu Li Kuvira.
Now rushing to Republic City
want to warn all
About the impending attack
Earth Empire.
Meanwhile, the Avatar team
preparing for such an event.
The Prince Wu is leading
the evacuation plan.
Asami and Varrick are creating
flying mecca-suits.
But as Kuvira plans
attack within 2 weeks.
Is there time?
BALANCE BOOK 4 CHAPTER 11
"The KUVIRA OF ruse"
Today, we will
to the story.
Over the past three years, we fought side by side
To unify the Empire Earth.
E
proved that no one can stand against us.
Not even the Avatar.
But our mission
is not over.
There is a great injustice that must be corrected
.
As you know,
after the War of the Hundred years
The Avatar Aang and Fire Lord, Lord Zuko
,
Stolen lands of the Earth Empire
And founded the United Republic.
These lands belong
to the Empire Earth.
It's time to get them back.
Republic City
will be ours!
Long live the Great Unifying!
Are you ready to show
than the super weapon is capable of?
I am. It will be an honor
march through the city at your side.
I love you, Kuvira.
I could never
this without your help.
After clamoring victory
Finally we can get married
and rule the Empire together.
How is the course
evacuation?
Could be better.
Already evacuated nearly...
- 18 families.
- Only 18?
There are millions of people
in this city.
He said he could be going better.
The problem is that
evacuation is voluntary.
And there are not many
volunteers.
The population does not feel
no imminent danger.
Guys, great!
They're all here.
What is the idea of stopping
all my meetings?
Su?
What...
Are you well.
I'm sorry for Zaofu.
- How did you escaped?
- Opal, Beifong and I
Rescued everyone.
But we flee from Kuvira.
We have seen the super spiritual weapon
closely.
Type... Very close.
Very close to it.
She will use it against
Republic City?
Yes, I found that it will attack
within two weeks.
The Zhu Li is on our side now.
In fact, always been,
And I'll let her explain everything.
Zhu Li?
Intended to be loyal to Kuvira
to sabotage the weapon.
He went well.
But I know their plans.
I knew she was not going to stop
in Zaofu.
I suppose
come by way of the railroad.
It is the only way to transport
that gun.
So let's cut
lines.
I agree.
We evacuate as many people as possible.
Communicate the radio. Now
evacuation is mandatory.
We'll treat it.
Do not worry, Mr. President
,
Not let Kuvira
take our city.
Faster!
Time is running!
We have just two weeks to have these costumes
Working.
Varrick, thankfully,
you're here!
- Can we talk for a minute?
- What is it? I'm busy
To inspire my employees.
Well, I went to Zaofu,
save Su and her family
And guess whom we met?
- Zhu Li?
- There is not anything you wanna say?
Please
let me speak first.
I know I said terrible things
thee ahead of Kuvira.
But I want you to know I did not mean any of it
.
When was caught
thought the only way
Save you
was joining me to it.
Every day
dreamed to see you again
And tell you the truth.
Varrick, significas
everything to me.
And I'm sorry if I hurt you
anyway.
Do not be so hard on yourself
.
Apology accepted.
Now, be a good assistant
and starts working.
Do not!
I am no longer your assistant!
If I want to close by
Raisins to treat me
as equals.
We are connected to the emergency broadcast.
Will you speak for all the radios
city.
Attention, citizens of Republic City.
This is not a test.
An attack to our town
is imminent.
The President Raiko ordered
all citizens to evacuate.
Open the book evacuation
subsection 1.26
There will find the instructions for your neighborhood.
For example, if you live in northwestern sector
Look at our primary location
What is the library entry
Water Tribe.
Then elect a leader
as stated in Subsection 1:28
Chief?
No one is to understand nothing.
I think the Mako
is creating panic.
What is it confusing?
I'm being very specific.
Great!
That's all we need.
I solve this.
Hello, everyone.
Here is the Prince Wu.
I know you're scared.
Believe me,
I know what it is to be scared.
I could not go to the bathroom alone.
But if we let the fear
take care of us,
None of us will be able to go to the bathroom.
So, we will all be losers
.
But the citizens of Republic City
Are no losers!
We are winners!
Winners who will leave this town
Calmly and order.
I want to pick up
in your families,
Pick up in your neighbors
Catch that homeless
that not know...
And enter a
any available means of locomotion.
Let's get them out of here!
Safe and sound.
Good job, kid.
Maybe it's not a bad king,
the end of the day.
Rohan is with others.
They've got a boat
ready to go.
Why have not packed their bags
?
The kids and I talked,
and decided that we will stay.
This is our town
and we need all the help possible.
That's right!
Face the domain of air in your faces!
Thank you.
Prince Wu
should need you
For evacuation.
And the three of you help them
other air rulers
Keep the troops of the Empire
away.
The Kuvira will repent of the day
that stirred the Meelo!
Do not feel good to leave
my office.
The Air Temple Island
is the ideal location for your base.
E will be safe here.
There's something I want to discuss with you
.
- What is it?
- We talked and...
We want to destroy the super weapon Kuvira
Before you approach
city.
This is a risk
we do not need to run.
The evacuation is already underway.
And General Iroh is ready.
I know Iroh can handle the same
to-toe against Kuvira,
- But that gun...
- is very powerful.
- Can destroy the city.
- Do not we let get here.
Let's try to go behind enemy lines
and destroy the weapon.
If it works,
will save us on the battlefield.
- But if they are caught...
- It's worth the risk.
I agree.
Our best weapon can be
avoid this war.
- Good luck.
- We leave tonight.
Is there anything out there.
It is the Kuvira Army.
Are one week earlier.
Warns the commander.
And alert Republic City.
Personally, I see something!
Down there.
- What's that?
- Kuvira.
It is already in the territory of the United Republic
.
- It is early one week.
- This makes no sense.
There is no train line
here.
How does it carried
that super weapon?
Apparently
a giant Mecca-costume.
Did you know that Kuvira
was building this thing?
Does forgot to mention?
Of course I did not know!
There is a flying bison
nearby.
A Avatar.
I know what happens next!
We have to leave now!
Now!
We must go after them?
They will warn Republic City.
Let them go.
No one can stop us.
Korra, are you okay?
Why did you come back so soon?
It Kuvira. Our information
was wrong.
She should know that Zhu Li
on to say.
- What do you mean?
- The army of Kuvira
- It is just a few hours.
- It can not be.
- We are not prepared.
- And the super weapon
Is connected to a giant Mecca-costume.
It's the size of a building
25 floors.
Contact the General Iroh and tell him
that the attack will take place today.
- We need to lock the city.
- Pema, is the Wu
And tell him we need to evacuate
immediately.
We can not lose
innocent lives.
- What do we do?
- Come to my factory
Maybe some costume
ready for use.
Let's you.
I go to the front line
warn the General Iroh.
Kuvira,
this is President Raiko.
I order you to retreat.
Get in his army
and turn around.
Not in
position to give orders.
Step back or attack.
I think it has no concept of the
power I possess.
Let me show you.
It is because of this that would not
construct the weapon.
Mr. President,
we are waiting for your orders.
Has 3/2,
or make disappear your army.
- I have no choice.
- The time is over!
Stop!
We surrender ourselves.
Republic City is yours.
Good.
Give me your army and Avatar
And tells Baatar
its location.
It will introduce you to the
our conditions.
I will not surrender.
Back to city
before she sees you.
And Korra...
Find a way to overthrow it.
I'll find out.
There, Kuvira.
I'm meeting with the Raiko
on Air Temple Island.
On my way.
Raiko surrendered.
It's up to us now.
How do we fight against an army
,
A giant Mecca-costume
and that crazy gun?
We can not fight,
but maybe we can sabotage it.
Zhu Li,
when you were spying on Kuvira,
Did you know anything about that
giant monster?
I did not know they were
to build it.
It seems that Baatar Jr.
is better than I thought.
Do not say you
I said that.
That's it! Baatar Jr. built it.
He knows how to destroy it.
I say that we must capture
and make him talk.
I know it's a long shot.
But it's the only chance we have.
- If not...
- Korra. Align.
We need rulers air to enter discreetly
The airship Baatar.
Tenzin, Bumi, Jinora, Kai,
go.
- What about me?
- Sorry, kid.
It's mission requires
maximum silence.
And I'm not much
such.
I can be silent!
Okay.
Note noted.
Is everyone ready?
Made a terrible mistake.
When Kuvira discover that disappeared
,
- You are finished.
- So before it discover
're Going to tell us how to stop
that mecca Giant
- Or not...
- Otherwise what?
You will not hurt me.
I know that is an empty threat
when I see one.
It was this, your better idea?
Lost.
Just have not yet accepted it.
Let me talk to him.
- You sure?
- Did you check it?
What is happening?
It's all right?
Just a minute, sir.
I'm saying, I checked everything.
Okay!
Enough gossip.
I am ready to discuss the conditions
With Baatar Jr.,
where is he?
In fact,
I'm not sure.
- Baatar?
- If you think I'm going
Tell you my secrets, mother...
- You are terribly mistaken.
- Why are you doing this?
I know planeavas
help the world
But this is crazy.
Madness is to let others
take what is yours
And accept blindly.
The United Republic
belongs to us.
- And we'll take it back.
- At what cost?
How many people will need to die
Kuvira be satisfied?
You do not have to cost any life
to surrender.
Whatever Kuvira and I want
is to unite the Empire Earth.
I do not know what it was that made
to hurt you.
But whatever it is,
I am very sorry.
When you left Zaofu,
broke my heart.
And our family
never been the same since.
Please Baatar, stop it
and back home.
We want you back with us
.
Kuvira now is my family.
Understand all wrong.
You're right.
I will physically hurt you
if not speak.
But there is one thing I can do
What is even more painful.
I'll take what you
more you care this life
Kuvira.
- What do you mean?
- The Kuvira can even win
Can even take this city
But thou shalt not
enjoy the victory.
Because wherever I go,
I'm taking you with me.
I make it my mission in life.
I never allow you to see your loved one again
.
If you take this city is better than losing
Kuvira forever?
- You can not.
- I can.
Unless convenças the Kuvira
to retreat.
We will continue with the Empire Earth.
Just let the United Republic
alone.
It Kuvira.
She wants to talk to the Baatar.
What should I tell you?
For God's sake,
give me that radio,
Let me talk to her.
Kuvira, here is the Raiko.
What kind of trap
is up to?
You said you were going to send the Baatar
with thy borders,
And now
it does not appear.
What do you mean,
"it does not appear"?
According to your staff,
it is not in the airship.
If he is not in the airship,
where is he?
Kuvira, is Baatar.
I was captured.
My airship was ambushed
and was taken by force.
Korra refuses to release me, let's descend unless
And leave the city.
- Are you hurt?
- I am fine.
- The Avatar is with you now?
- Yeah, they're all here.
Find out where is this signal
is coming.
Listen to me...
If you take Republic City
The Avatar
never let me see you again.
And I refuse to live
that way.
Forget the United Republic,
already have the Empire Earth.
We fear each other.
Let's go home and get married
.
The only thing that matters is
be together forever.
We have already identified the position.
You're right.
This town is not worth the risk
to sacrifice our future.
I love you, Baatar.
So we make an agreement with Kuvira,
We'll release it here.
Guys, she discovered
our location.
You're pointing a gun at us
.
No. It would not.
Everybody out. Already.
Now!
- No
-. Keep safe chairman.
I'm going to look for survivors.
Translation En United4ever and MundoAvatar
pTpT Adaptation - Arodri
www.tvsubtitles.net